<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE glossary>
<glossary><movie><title>The Mask</title><category>tv series</category><year>1995-1997</year><rating>7.2</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>The Jeff Foxworthy Show</title><category>tv series</category><year>1995-1997</year><rating>4.9</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Notaufnahme</title><category>tv series</category><year>1995</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>The Maxx</title><category>tv series</category><year>1995</year><rating>8.9</rating><plot>Maxx is a purple-clad superhero living in a cardboard box. His only friend is Julie Winters, a freelance social worker. Maxx often finds himself shifting back and forth between the "real" world and a more primitive outback world where he rules, and protects Julie. Mr. Gone, a self-proclaimed "student of the mystic arts" seems to know more about Maxx and Julie and their strange relationship than they could ever guess, but he's not exactly telling all....not yet, anyway.</plot></movie><movie><title>Choriki sentai Orenja</title><category>tv series</category><year>1995-1996</year><rating>8.4</rating><plot>600 million years ago, ancient mankind created a rebellious robot named Bacchus Wrath. Riki (Kingranger) banished Bacchus Wrath from earth. In year 1999, He returns to earth with the intention of wiping out all human life and bring about machine rule. Chief Counsellor Miura revived super energies that have been given birth by the lost civilization on Pangaea 600 million years ago. Assembling pieces of a stone plate uncovered three years ago, the secrets of "superpower" has been revealed. Miura builds a pyramid that generates Tetrahedron power-power that allows five U.A. officers to transform into Ohrangers.</plot></movie><movie><title>Spellbinder</title><category>tv series</category><year>1995</year><rating>8.2</rating><plot>When a prank at a school camp goes drastically wrong, 15-year-old Paul Reynolds is blasted into an alternative reality and has to try to find a way home.</plot></movie>