<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE glossary>
<glossary><movie><title>Lost Civilizations</title><category>tv series</category><year>1995</year><rating>7.6</rating><plot>Never before could you get this close to 7,000 years of history. Digital effects technology and dramatizations re-create rituals and events, from the bloodletting of Maya kings and a pharaoh's last journey to the secret pleasures of a Roman empress. Original location cinematography in 25 countries takes you from Cuzco in Peru to Petra in Jordan, from ancient Mesopotamia to modern Tibet. Computer graphics restore Egypt's pyramids and the Great Wall of China. Part 1: Mesopotamia: return to Eden. Part 2: Ancient Egypt: quest for immortality. Part 3: Aegean: legacy of Atlantis. Part 4: Greece: a moment of excellence. Part 5: China: dynasties of power. Part 6: Rome: the ultimate empire. Part 7: The Maya: the blood of kings. Part 8: The Inca: secrets of the ancestors. Part 9: Africa: a history denied. Part 10: Tibet: the end of time.</plot></movie><movie><title>Die Harald Schmidt Show</title><category>tv series</category><year>1995-2003</year><rating>7.9</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Laila Gov</title><category>tv series</category><year>1995-1998</year><rating>7.1</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>The Adventures of Hyperman</title><category>tv series</category><year>1995-1996</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Extreme</title><category>tv series</category><year>1995</year><rating>6.3</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Stockinger</title><category>tv series</category><year>1996-1997</year><rating>6.2</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Aeon Flux</title><category>tv series</category><year>1991</year><rating>8.1</rating><plot>Aeon Flux is a mysterious and amoral secret agent from the country of Monica. Her motives or background are left unexplained, as are those of her antagonist/love, Trevor Goodchild. On her missions, she deals swift, bloody "justice" to all that oppose her. The second season episodes of this series were unique in that Aeon died at the end of every single episode.</plot></movie><movie><title>Gabrielle</title><category>tv series</category><year>1995-1996</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Happily Ever After: Fairy Tales for Every Child</title><category>tv series</category><year>1995-2000</year><rating>5.3</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Ghostbusters of East Finchley</title><category>tv series</category><year>1995</year><rating>6.1</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Ik ben je moeder niet</title><category>tv series</category><year>1995-1996</year><rating>8.4</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>The Hanging Gale</title><category>tv series</category><year>1995</year><rating>8.5</rating><plot>The four brothers of the Phelan family battle to save their farm and their family from the ravages of the Irish Potato Famine in 1846, and from an English land agent who takes a dislike to them.</plot></movie><movie><title>Crown Prosecutor</title><category>tv series</category><year>1995</year><rating>4.0</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Lille lordag</title><category>tv series</category><year>1995-1996</year><rating>7.1</rating><plot>"Lille Lørdag" is a TV-series consisting of many different parts, mainly parodying older NRK (and general TV) productions and stars (Erik Bye), and previous prime ministers (Einar Gerhardsen). It does so by pretending that they are heroes. The programs usually end with a short series. In the second production year, this was a comedy called "Min Drømmeserie" and took place in Arendal, generally parodying the Arendal dialect. In the third year, it was a so-called horror story based on old Sami religion.</plot></movie><movie><title>Pointman</title><category>tv series</category><year>1995</year><rating>7.8</rating><plot>Connie Harper is living the good life as the owner of Spanish Pete's, a beach resort. Occasionally his services as bodyguard are called upon by people who have nowhere else to turn.</plot></movie><movie><title>Vanishing Son</title><category>tv series</category><year>1995</year><rating>8.5</rating><plot>13 episodes of this syndicated show were produced in 1994 and 1995 and first aired in January 1995. Jian-Wa comes to America from Beijing with his brother Wago to find freedom. Wago, who is hot-headed, falls in with a gang and he and two federal agents are murdered. Jian-Wa is determined to find the culprits who are lead by the mysterious "The General" a Vietnamese who is making millions of dollars. Compounding the problem, Federal Agent Sandler is pursuing Jian-Wa because he thinks Jian-Wa killed the agents; Agent Phillips, who works for Sandler, is keeping an open mind about Jian-Wa's guilt or innocence.</plot></movie><movie><title>Double Rush</title><category>tv series</category><year>1995</year><rating>6.2</rating><plot>Johnny Verona is trying to hold together his struggling bike messanger service. Standing in the way of success are his smart-alec slacker riders, cutthroat competitors, and a whiny executive-wannabe constantly telling everyone within earshot that she shouldn't really be doing this job because she's a Harvard grad.</plot></movie><movie><title>Land's End</title><category>tv series</category><year>1995</year><rating>7.8</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>KLMs vorspiel</title><category>tv series</category><year>1995</year><rating>7.2</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>10-07: L'affaire Zeus</title><category>tv series</category><year>1995</year><rating>5.3</rating><plot></plot></movie></glossary>
