<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE glossary>
<glossary><movie><title>Fur alle Falle Stefanie</title><category>tv series</category><year>1995-2004</year><rating>2.4</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Echt Harder</title><category>tv series</category><year>1995</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Scheidungsgericht</title><category>tv series</category><year>1995</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Downwardly Mobile</title><category>tv series</category><year>1994</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>The Damnation of Harvey McHugh</title><category>tv series</category><year>1994</year><rating>4.2</rating><plot>Harvey McHugh just wants a permanent job in the civil service. Unfortunately, he works for a minister who thinks nothing of resorting to corruption, murder, terrorism, and using Harvey as a guinea pig in illegal medical experiments to cure his long-term fatal illness. What-is-more, Harvey is so innocent and trusting that he doesn't realise any of this is going on.</plot></movie><movie><title>Blue Heelers</title><category>tv series</category><year>1994-2006</year><rating>6.5</rating><plot>The most popular local production on Australian television, Blue Heelers is a weekly police drama based on a fictional bush town called Mount Thomas. Every week there is a different case for Sergeant Tom Croydon, Senior Constable Nick Schultz, Senior Detective PJ Hasham, and Constables Maggie Doyle, Dash McKinley and Adam Cooper to solve. Continuing storylines about the personal lives and relationships of these characters filter into each episode.</plot></movie><movie><title>The Secret World of Alex Mack</title><category>tv series</category><year>1994-1998</year><rating>8.1</rating><plot>A teenage girl, just starting junior high and living in a modern corporate community is accidentally contaminated by a secret chemical product of The Plant. She acquires mysterious abilities that allow her to change her shape, move objects with her mind, and zap people and objects with small electrical charges. The owners of The Plant continually seek to find out which of the local kids has been contaminated so they can experiment on her, but their employees are less than competent and the search is comedic and futile.</plot></movie><movie><title>Muddling Through</title><category>tv series</category><year>1994</year><rating>5.8</rating><plot>After two years in jail for shooting her cheating husband Sonny in his behind, Connie Drego returns home, to the motel she owns and which her oldest daughter Madeline kept open in her absence. Connie desperately wants to pick up the pieces of her life and try to do it right this time, but that's not going to be easy with her daughter Kerri well into puberty, Sonny still living in one of her rooms, and her bright Madeline married to Duane Cooper, the naive state trooper who arrested her.</plot></movie><movie><title>Wycliffe</title><category>tv series</category><year>1994</year><rating>8.0</rating><plot>Supt. Wycliffe keeps the Cornish coastline crime free as he tackles arsonists, kidnappers and the odd psycho. Jack Shepherd plays the eponymous hero in the one hour TV adaptations of W. J. Burley's creation.</plot></movie><movie><title>Sky Trackers</title><category>tv series</category><year>1994</year><rating>6.6</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Something Wilder</title><category>tv series</category><year>1994-1995</year><rating>7.5</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Fascht e Familie</title><category>tv series</category><year>1994-1995</year><rating>6.0</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Snowy River: The McGregor Saga</title><category>tv series</category><year>1993-1996</year><rating>6.9</rating><plot>Based on Banjo Paterson's poem "Man From Snowy River", this series takes place in Paterson's Ridge, a small town set in the mountains near Melbourne, during the late 19th century. It tells the story of Matt McGregor, one of the richest and most influential man in town, as well as widower father of three children: Colin, who's the town preacher, Rob and Danni, the tomboy youngest daughter. Unresolved sexual tension comes in the shape of Matt's childhood independent, free-spirited friend, the recently widowed Kathleen O'Neil, who's returned to Paterson's Ridge with her son after having spent many years in England.</plot></movie><movie><title>Maigret</title><category>tv series</category><year>1992</year><rating>8.1</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Tribeca</title><category>tv series</category><year>1993</year><rating>6.9</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Ein Mann am Zug</title><category>tv series</category><year>1993</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Flodder</title><category>tv series</category><year>1993-1997</year><rating>6.1</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Talk Soup</title><category>tv series</category><year>1991-2002</year><rating>7.7</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Running the Halls</title><category>tv series</category><year>1993</year><rating>5.3</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Dangerous Curves</title><category>tv series</category><year>1992</year><rating>5.6</rating><plot></plot></movie></glossary>
