<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE glossary>
<glossary><movie><title>Xena: Warrior Princess</title><category>tv series</category><year>1995-2001</year><rating>6.7</rating><plot>Xena, a mighty warrior and healer, once led a band of outlaws that terrorized all of Greece. She has come to regret the harm she caused and, with her companion Gabrielle, now travels the countryside seeking adventure and fighting the forces of evil.</plot></movie><movie><title>Bless This House</title><category>tv series</category><year>1995</year><rating>4.8</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Freakazoid!</title><category>tv series</category><year>1995-1997</year><rating>8.5</rating><plot>Computer Geek Dexter Douglas turns into an uncontrollable, unpredictable superhero donning red long underwear, blue skin and weird hair. The transformation occurs while Dexter surfs on the Internet. As a superhero, he fights crime whenever he sees it perpetrated by goofy villains with his friends Stephanie and Cogrove.</plot></movie><movie><title>All That</title><category>tv series</category><year>1994-2005</year><rating>7.3</rating><plot>A combination sketch comedy/musical performance show in the tradition of "Saturday Night Live", this program starred an teenage cast and was targeted at younger viewers. The show featured a number of repeating characters, including Baggin' Saggin' Barry, Super Dude, and the misfit fast food employees of Good Burger, which spawned a movie of the same name.</plot></movie><movie><title>Drei Mann im Bett</title><category>tv series</category><year>1994</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Kanzlei Burger</title><category>tv series</category><year>1995</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Kenny Kingston Psychic Hotline</title><category>tv series</category><year>1995-1996</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Familie Heinz Becker</title><category>tv series</category><year>1992-2004</year><rating>8.1</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Wax Cracks Cannes</title><category>tv series</category><year>1995</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Kaitou Saint Tail</title><category>tv series</category><year>1995</year><rating>6.9</rating><plot>Meimi's a bright and cheerful girl, who inherited her father Genichiro's magic powers and her mother Eimi's abilities as a thief. Now at night she turns into the mysterious thief Saint Tail and sets about town righting wrongs (usually stealing back things that innocent victims have been cheated out of), with the help and council of her friend Seira, who's also a nun in training who listens to people's stories. She tells the stories to Meimi, who turns to Saint Tail to settle the problem. But, although her objectives are good, to steal is a crime and Asuka Jr has dedicated himself to catching Saint Tail. But Meimi/Saint Tail likes Asuka, and this complicates matters a bit.</plot></movie><movie><title>The Bonnie Hunt Show</title><category>tv series</category><year>1995-1996</year><rating>6.7</rating><plot>Bonnie Hunt plays Bonnie Kelly, a reporter for the news station WBDR. She is joined by her best friend Holly, a hairdresser at WBDR, her limo driving neighbor Keith, her cameraman Tom, her boss Mr. Kirkland, whom she is in love with, and assorted co-workers whom she pals around with at work. Every episode also contains a real remote segment that Bonnie does for the news.</plot></movie><movie><title>Unser Lehrer Doktor Specht</title><category>tv series</category><year>1992-1999</year><rating>6.4</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Akazukin Chacha</title><category>tv series</category><year>1994</year><rating>8.5</rating><plot>Akazukin Chacha, or Red Hood Chacha, by Ayahana Min, is loosely (extremely loosely) based on Little Red Riding Hood. The main characters are: Chacha, a little red-hooded girl who is an incompetent magic user; Riiya, a werewolf boy and Chacha's best friend; and Shiine, a magic-using boy who wants Chacha. The stories revolve around the adventures of the three characters and, on a lesser scale, their love triangle. Chacha can also transform into a magical fighting girl for some reason...</plot></movie><movie><title>The Itsy Bitsy Spider</title><category>tv series</category><year>1994</year><rating>5.5</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Jimeoin</title><category>tv series</category><year>1994-1995</year><rating>9.0</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Die Wache</title><category>tv series</category><year>1994- </year><rating>5.1</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>In the Name of Love</title><category>tv series</category><year>1994-1995</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Chef!</title><category>tv series</category><year>1993-1996</year><rating>8.4</rating><plot>A comedy, conceived by Lenny Henry, playing the *finest* chef in England, possibly the world. Chef! is set in the kitchen of _Le Chateau Anglais_, the finest French restaurant in England. Gareth Blackstock, the aforementioned chef, embodies all the worst qualities of someone at the top of their profession...</plot></movie><movie><title>Knowing Me, Knowing You with Alan Partridge</title><category>tv series</category><year>1994-1995</year><rating>8.8</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Tonde Buurin</title><category>tv series</category><year>1994</year><rating>7.7</rating><plot></plot></movie></glossary>
