<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE glossary>
<glossary><movie><title>Vovkulakiya, ili zagadka doktora Nikodima</title><category>tv series</category><year>1996</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Moesha</title><category>tv series</category><year>1996-2001</year><rating>4.3</rating><plot>"Moesha" is a sitcom (which, in later years, took more of a dramatic turn) that follows the life and times of a black teenager living in the Leimert Park section of Los Angeles, CA. For years since her mother died, Moesha Mitchell has taken care of her father Frank and younger brother Myles. So when a teacher at her school, Dee, marries Frank, Moesha feels her territory being encroached upon by a new step mother. As time went on, the two females of the house would learn to appreciate and cherish each other's presence. Moesha's boy-crazy best friends Kim and Niecy as well as her eternally hungry neighbor and pal Hakeem are there to support Mo throughout all of the drama she finds herself in--and there's always plenty. Andell, a local smoothie shop owner, is another close confidante of Moesha's, lending her wisdom to the teen when needed. Over the years, it was Frank who Moesha would clash with most. He has quite a hard time witnessing his "pumpkin" grow up, and often hates her boyfriends, most notably Q. After graduating from high school, Moesha attends classes at "Cal U" with Hakeem and Niecy, and back at home, the entire family struggles with a startling revelation about Moesha's cousin, Dorian.</plot></movie><movie><title>Men Behaving Badly</title><category>tv series</category><year>1996-1997</year><rating>6.1</rating><plot>Kevin and Jamie are two roommates. Kevin is irresponsible and sloppy, but compared to super-slob and slacker Jamie, Kevin looks almost anal-retentive. While both are content to wallow in their immaturity, Kevin must contend with his girlfriend Sarah's attempt to "improve" him. Jamie is always ready to provide immoral support.</plot></movie><movie><title>Friedemann Brix - Eine Schwache fur Mord</title><category>tv series</category><year>1996-1997</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>The Burning Zone</title><category>tv series</category><year>1996-1997</year><rating>6.7</rating><plot>Dr. Daniel Cassian is appointed by the White House to lead a small top secret federal biological task force of leading scientists to investigate and prevent potential biological disasters. The team also adopt Cassian's secret agenda to track down and identify the scientists and others behind the ultra secret, pernicious organisation known only as 'The Dawn' whose objective is to rid the planet of its most virulent infestation, the human race!</plot></movie><movie><title>Project G.e.e.K.e.R.</title><category>tv series</category><year>1996-1997</year><rating>4.9</rating><plot>Mr. Moloch is a rich industrialist that wants to conquer the world. In order to do it he needs the help of an artificially created "humanoid". The humanoid is created by Dr. Maston; it's powers are almost infinite. However, project G.K.R. is stolen by Lady Macbeth and an intelligent dino named Noah. The thing is, G.e.e.K.e.R. hasn't been fully programmed yet and he doesn't know how to use his powers. Anyway, Mr. Moloch wants him badly and is willing to do whatever it takes to get the ever optimistic Geeker...</plot></movie><movie><title>Lara att simma</title><category>tv series</category><year>1997</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>King of the Hill</title><category>tv series</category><year>1997- </year><rating>7.6</rating><plot>Hank Hill is an old fashioned, hardworking, beer drinking man who is trying to live in a modern Texas world. His wife is opinionated, his son is a disappointment, his friends are losers, and his Father is oppressive. But through it all, Hank keeps a level head, a strong sense of morality, and by doing so keeps himself "King of the Hill."</plot></movie><movie><title>Chicago Sons</title><category>tv series</category><year>1997</year><rating>6.5</rating><plot>The life of Mike, newly divorced from his wife, Billy, always between get-rich-fast scams, and Harry, desperately in love with co-worker Lindsay, three brothers living together in a Chicago building surrounding Wriegley Field.</plot></movie><movie><title>Spawn</title><category>tv series</category><year>1997-1999</year><rating>8.4</rating><plot>A government trained assassin in life, A vengeful hellspawn in death. Brought back from the dead to join Hell's army and release his carnage on anyone that may get in his way. Heaven and Hell battle for his already torn soul, while he wanders the alleys protecting the innocent and destroying the corrupt who disrupt the lives of the innocent. In the meantime he faces the tragedy of his death and the fact that he has been sent to Hell and he must also face the reality of losing his wife to an old friend.</plot></movie><movie><title>Space Cadets</title><category>tv series</category><year>1997</year><rating>6.4</rating><plot>Insane comedy quiz show, played purely for laughs, with the winners irrelevant. Comedian Greg Proops is the host; team captains are Craig Charles (Red Dwarf) and comedian Bill Bailey. Each team's 3 members are generally filled out with one comedian and one star each from a classic TV science-fiction series: eg Walter Koenig and Claudia Christian (Babylon 5), Sophie Aldred and Sylvester McCoy (Dr Who), or Armin Shimerman and Max Grodenchik (Deep Space 9).</plot></movie><movie><title>Spy Game</title><category>tv series</category><year>1997</year><rating>8.1</rating><plot>The Cold War is over and the world's biggest threat is the growing amount of unemployed (mostly laid off) spies. A retired secret agent is pulled back into service by a young rookie working for E.C.H.O.. He is constantly amazed by the changing rules of the spy game...</plot></movie><movie><title>"Der Bulle von Tolz" Bauernhochzeit</title><category>tv series</category><year>1997</year><rating>7.3</rating><plot></plot></movie>