<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE glossary>
<glossary><movie><title>Queridas e Maduras</title><category>tv series</category><year>1995-1996</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>The Parent 'Hood</title><category>tv series</category><year>1995-1999</year><rating>5.9</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Bringing Up Jack</title><category>tv series</category><year>1995</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>The Outer Limits</title><category>tv series</category><year>1995-2002</year><rating>7.9</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Echt Harder</title><category>tv series</category><year>1995</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Sirens</title><category>tv series</category><year>1993-1995</year><rating>6.5</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Frasier</title><category>tv series</category><year>1993-2004</year><rating>8.4</rating><plot>Eminent Boston Psychiatrist, Frasier Crane, last seen gracing the bars of Cheers has left his life there to start afresh in Seattle. He now has a spot as a popular radio Psychiatrist, giving him the chance to spread words of wit and wisdom to the masses. He shares his apartment with his retired cop father, Martin, and his father's physical care assistant, Daphne Moon. Add in brother Niles, Eddie the dog, some bizarre situations and plenty of humour and you've got all the ingredients for an excellent show and worthy successor to Cheers.</plot></movie><movie><title>Cracker</title><category>tv series</category><year>1993-1996</year><rating>9.0</rating><plot>This mystery series from the U.K. outlines the adventures of a psychologist employed by the police to aid them in profiling and questioning suspects. "Fitz" (Robbie Coltrane), an avowed drunkard and gambler, has an uncanny knack for boring directly into the hearts and minds of his subjects, many of whom may in fact be saner than he is...</plot></movie><movie><title>Denei shoujo Ai</title><category>tv series</category><year>1992</year><rating>8.1</rating><plot>Yota's heart is thoroughly broken one afternoon, when Moemi, the love of his life confesses her love for his best friend Takashi. With a hope of cheering himself up, he rents a video, "Video Girl Ai" from a strange rental shop called "Gokuraku" ("Paradise"), which he's never noticed before on his way home. While playing it on his dad's broken VCR, the girl in the video practically jumps out of the screen into his world. Her mission; to cheer up Yota at all cost and eventually, bring him closer to Moemi. However, as a result of the the faulty VCR, Ai begins to experience feelings forbidden to a "Video Girl," and ends up falling in love with Yota himself. Now, Yota must choose between the girl, who till this point, he thought was the love of his life, or the girl who's sole purpose was to bring him happiness, joy and love into his life. A great romantic comedy with beautiful original artwork with a stunning soundtrack.</plot></movie><movie><title>Johnny Bago</title><category>tv series</category><year>1993</year><rating>7.6</rating><plot>After a Federal faux pas, small-time mobster John Tenuti flees West across the U.S., pursued by bumbling goons from his Jersey outfit plus his rabid ex-wife, a Fed herself (Rose Abdoo). As pompadoured Johnny Bago, he sees the USA in his Winnebago, cranks up the tune-age to remind him of dear old Hoboken, and each episode lands in a bizarre back-roads situation with locals as flaky as he is (including Elvis). Unfortunately neither Johnny nor this summer replacement series from the producers of Seabiscuit and The Polar Express, with music by Jimmy Buffett, made it to Fall.</plot></movie><movie><title>Notes and Queries with Clive Anderson</title><category>tv series</category><year>1993</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Class of '96</title><category>tv series</category><year>1993</year><rating>7.4</rating><plot>"Class of '96" is the FOX series directed by Peter Horton (of "thirtysomething" fame). The show deals with the story of 7 friends who attend Havenhurst College, a fictitious Ivy League school located in New England. The show was first introduced in January of 1993 and was canceled in May at the end of the show's first season.</plot></movie><movie><title>Secrets</title><category>tv series</category><year>1993</year><rating></rating><plot>"Secrets" follows four university graduates who have been recruited into a top-secret intelligence organization. Starting at the initial training and screening process, we follow these green recruits as they stumble their way through their probation and initial assignments. The series examines the spy business from a unique angle: that of the new recruit.</plot></movie><movie><title>Where in the World Is Carmen Sandiego?</title><category>tv series</category><year>1991-1996</year><rating>7.9</rating><plot>One of Carmen Sandiego's many henchmen has stolen a rare cultural object. The Acme Crime Detective Agency hires three gumshoes (contestants) to find the crook and recover the loot. The gumshoe who captures the crook is then given the chance to locate and capture Carmen Sandiego by locating countries on a large map of a continent placed on the floor. The host, The Chief and a variety of other guests help the gumshoes by supplying clues. A cappella music is performed at the beginning of the show, between game segments and at the end by Rockapella.</plot></movie><movie><title>Mysteries of the Bible</title><category>tv series</category><year>1994-1998</year><rating>8.2</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Big Girl's Blouse</title><category>tv series</category><year>1994</year><rating>6.7</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>One West Waikiki</title><category>tv series</category><year>1994-1996</year><rating>7.3</rating><plot></plot></movie>