<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE glossary>
<glossary><movie><title>Florida Lady</title><category>tv series</category><year>1994- </year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Doppelter Einsatz</title><category>tv series</category><year>1994-2007</year><rating>6.6</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Law and Disorder</title><category>tv series</category><year>1994</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Exosquad</title><category>tv series</category><year>1993-1995</year><rating>8.6</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Hall huvet kallt</title><category>tv series</category><year>1994</year><rating>5.6</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Wesenstund</title><category>tv series</category><year>1994-2000</year><rating>5.1</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>MMC</title><category>tv series</category><year>1989-1994</year><rating>6.9</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Outside Edge</title><category>tv series</category><year>1994-1996</year><rating>9.0</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Family Passions</title><category>tv series</category><year>1993</year><rating>5.7</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>The 5 Mrs. Buchanans</title><category>tv series</category><year>1994-1995</year><rating>7.6</rating><plot>Set in fictional Mercy, Indiana, this comedy centers around four completely different women who have only two connections to each other: they each are married to a Buchanan boy, and they each cannot stand their mother-in-law. Alex, married to Roy, is a Jewish feminist from New York City. Vivian, married to Ed, is a frumpy Hoosier housewife with two children from hell, twins Lyndon and P.J. Delilah, married to preacher Charles, is a somewhat ditzy former stripper from Corpus Christi, Texas. Bree, newly married to Jesse, is a perky Californian who used to work with her mother. They constantly are trading barbs with the cruel but hilarious Mother Buchanan, who tries as hard as she can to make their lives a living hell through meddling and manipulating, her two specialties.</plot></movie><movie><title>Bassie en Adriaan en de reis vol verrassingen</title><category>tv series</category><year>1994</year><rating>8.2</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Gargoyles</title><category>tv series</category><year>1994-1996</year><rating>8.3</rating><plot>In the Dark Ages, there was a race of heroic Warrior monsters known as Gargoyles. These creatures existed as stone in the day, but become flesh and blood at night. One Scottish clan made an alliance with humans to help protect a castle by night if the humans would protect their stone forms by day. The uneasy alliance was shattered when human prejudice provoked a betrayal that allowed the castle to be sacked and most of the resident clan destroyed, leaving only six adult survivors and a rookery of unhatched eggs. A further misunderstanding during the Clan's retaliation on the invaders and rescue of their hostages left the clan frozen in stone by a magic spell that would only be broken when the "Castle rises above the Clouds." For a thousand years, the castle laid abandoned and the clan condemned by this curse. In 1994, a wealthy multibillionare named David Xanatos, bought the castle and transported the whole structure to Manhattan where he placed it on top of the Eyrie building which he owned. It is high enough to be above the clouds, thus the conditions of the spell were met and the Gargoyles were revived. Now, this clan must adjust to this new age and gain friends like Detective Elisa Masa who reveals that Xanatos revived them to exploit them for his unscrupulous ends. This is coupled by the fact that another Gargoyle comrade, Demona, is alive from their age, and is now a insane renegade bent on the extermination of humanity. Rebelling against them, the clan abandon the castle and pledge to protect New York like they protected the castle in the past.</plot></movie><movie><title>Down to Earth</title><category>tv series</category><year>1995- </year><rating>3.2</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>The Adventures of Dudley the Dragon</title><category>tv series</category><year>1994</year><rating>6.8</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Zwei alte Hasen</title><category>tv series</category><year>1994</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Toen was geluk heel gewoon</title><category>tv series</category><year>1993- </year><rating>7.1</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Weird Science</title><category>tv series</category><year>1994-1997</year><rating>6.9</rating><plot>88 episodes of this USA network show were made. Gary Wallace and Wyatt Donnelly create their dream woman, Lisa, on their computer. Lisa had extraordinary powers and could grant the boys their wishes for short periods of time.</plot></movie><movie><title>Der Havelkaiser</title><category>tv series</category><year>1994</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Friends</title><category>tv series</category><year>1994-2004</year><rating>9.0</rating><plot>When we start the show, Rachel Green comes in wearing a wedding dress after leaving her fiancée at the altar. Rachel worked at Central Perk for a while and finally gets a job at Bloomingdale's and later Ralph Lauren. She has a baby with Ross Geller and they decide to keep the baby. Ross Geller is a paleontologist, and has had three wives. His first wife, Carol, finds out she is a lesbian and is pregnant with his baby. His second wife, Emily, is crushed when he calls this new wife Rachel instead of Emily. His third wife, Rachel, happens when they get drunk and decide to get married. Ross's sister, and Rachel's best friend, Monica Geller-Bing is a chef, and finally marries Chandler Bing. Chandler Bing is Ross's best friend, and secretly dated his sister for about 6-7 months. Monica and Chandler want to have a baby after Rachel has hers, but they can't have any. They decide to adopt a baby. They are shocked to find out that the pregnant mother is having twins. Chandler's former roommate, Joey Tribbiani, is a not so bright, but sweet actor. We played on Days of Our Lives has Dr. Drake Ramoray. Monica's other former roommate, Phoebe Buffay, is a masseuse, and a singer. Her most famous song is "Smelly Cat." Phoebe at the end marries a guy named Mike Hannigan. Phoebe was also was a surrogate mother for her brother's triplets. Ross and Rachel find out that they love each other when Rachel is assigned to live in Paris for a job that pays a lot. Monica and Chandler decide to move to a suburban house to raise the babies. The show ends when Monica and Chandler are moving to their new house, Ross and Rachel are living together again,and Phoebe is married to Mike.</plot></movie><movie><title>Madison</title><category>tv series</category><year>1993-1997</year><rating>4.8</rating><plot>Madison is about a group of teenagers in high school. The show deals with their everyday problems and concerns. We see the kids grow from high school students to fully grown adults. It is a well written Canadian show, somewhat better then Degrassi Jr. High.</plot></movie></glossary>
