<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE glossary>
<glossary><movie><title>Slayers</title><category>tv series</category><year>1995</year><rating>8.0</rating><plot>In a medieval sword and sorcery world, there is one mage who is notorious for her power and grace (at least that's how she likes to put it), Lina Inverse. In reality, she is a teenage mage with a penchant for collateral damage, obnoxiousness and gluttony. This series chronicles her adventures with companions, such as the powerful but dumb swordsman Gourry Gabriev as she quests for gold and finds a heck of a lot trouble along the way.</plot></movie><movie><title>Arzte</title><category>tv series</category><year>1994</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Agony Again</title><category>tv series</category><year>1995</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Deadly Games</title><category>tv series</category><year>1995-1996</year><rating>6.3</rating><plot>To take his mind off his divorce, antimatter physicist Gus Lloyd started programming an action video game where he was the hero, his ex-wife Lauren Ashborne was the sidekick, and his father Jordan Kenneth Lloyd was Sebastian Jackal, a satanic figure who wanted to destroy the world with an army of thugs based on the people who made Gus' life a living hell. The antimatter experiments Gus and his friend Peter Rucker were running went haywire, reading the game's villain file and sending them into the real world to act out their programming. Gus, Lauren, and Peter are then forced to play the game for real.</plot></movie><movie><title>The Adventures of Timmy the Tooth</title><category>tv series</category><year>1995</year><rating>6.0</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Coogan's Run</title><category>tv series</category><year>1995</year><rating>7.2</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Und tschuss!</title><category>tv series</category><year>1995- </year><rating>4.3</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Politically Incorrect</title><category>tv series</category><year>1994-2002</year><rating>6.5</rating><plot>Political talk show based on the idea that debate is stifled by too much seriousness. Guests are chosen from the worlds of politics and entertainment, often with the goal of creating conflict (ultra-sensitive special-interest groups matched with outrageous comedians). Nevertheless, a relatively friendly atmosphere is maintained, with none of the swearing or chair-throwing common on 'shock-talk' shows. Regular features have included the "Get Over Yourself" award, given to the week's most self-absorbed public figure.</plot></movie><movie><title>Rebel Highway</title><category>tv series</category><year>1994</year><rating>5.8</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>"Due South" Pilot</title><category>tv series</category><year>1994</year><rating>7.1</rating><plot>After the murder of his father in the Yukon, Fraser, a RCMP constable, follows the killer's tracks all the way to Chicago where he meets Ray, a Chicago PD detective. Together they continue their search for the truth and justice.</plot></movie><movie><title>Mitt sanna jag</title><category>tv series</category><year>1995</year><rating></rating><plot>Sanna Sohlman is a singer with her own TV show. Her husband Lasse is an airline pilot, and they have two children, Flisan and Alex. Lasse is usually confused by jet-lag. Sanna's a pianist, Melin is a "sober alcoholic", and the rest of the show crew are also a bit odd in their own ways: Kjell is homosexual, Kemal has linguistic problems, Max is over-ambitious, and Malin's only advantage (next to being the object of Max' courtship) is that she is the daughter of the big boss.</plot></movie>