<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE glossary>
<glossary><movie><title>Der Mond scheint auch fur Untermieter</title><category>tv series</category><year>1995</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Faust</title><category>tv series</category><year>1994-1997</year><rating>2.8</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Moving Story</title><category>tv series</category><year>1994-1995</year><rating>7.7</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Cinema 3</title><category>tv series</category><year>1984- </year><rating>5.5</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Correlli</title><category>tv series</category><year>1995</year><rating>8.1</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Pinky and the Brain</title><category>tv series</category><year>1995-1998</year><rating>8.5</rating><plot>A genetically engineered mouse (who sounds like Orson Welles) and his insane cohort make nightly attempts to take over the world.</plot></movie><movie><title>Partners</title><category>tv series</category><year>1995-1996</year><rating>6.5</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Glam Metal Detectives</title><category>tv series</category><year>1995</year><rating>7.8</rating><plot>A sketch show that had the effect that you were channel surfing, with each sketch being a spoof programme on different fake channels. Regular items included Colin Corleone - a man who thought he was The Godfather, a 1950's serial 'Betty's Mad Dash', an American talk show, movie paradies, plus the eponymic Glam Metal Detectives who would fight crime and play sell-out concerts every week. You'd dip in and out of these and other sketches as if you were hopping around different TV channels.</plot></movie><movie><title>Alle meine Tochter</title><category>tv series</category><year>1995-2001</year><rating>5.1</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Sliders</title><category>tv series</category><year>1995-2000</year><rating>7.7</rating><plot>Quinn Mallory, while working on an anti-gravity machine, accidentally creates a portal to a parallel universe. Eventually, his friends and an unwilling participant accidentally get stuck traveling among parallel worlds, trying to survive, and learning that sliding can lead to fatal results. Meanwhile, among many changes in their group, they try to rescue the multiverse from the Kromagg Dynasty.</plot></movie><movie><title>Get Smart</title><category>tv series</category><year>1995</year><rating>5.9</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>MADtv</title><category>tv series</category><year>1995-2009</year><rating>6.8</rating><plot>Late night sketch-comedy show based on the humor of MAD magazine. Material includes impersonations, fake commercials, mock movie trailers, and even Spy vs. Spy segments. Competes against Saturday Night Live in it's time slot, but aimed at a younger adult audience.</plot></movie><movie><title>Clueless</title><category>tv series</category><year>1996-1999</year><rating>5.3</rating><plot>A television series, based on the popular movie of the same name. Many of the actors from the movie appear in the television series, including Dion, Mr. Hall, Miss Giest, Amber, and Murray.</plot></movie><movie><title>7th Heaven</title><category>tv series</category><year>1996-2007</year><rating>4.5</rating><plot>This weekly television series follows the Camden family as the minister father and stay-at-home mother deal with the drama of having seven children, ranging from toddlers to adults with families of their own. The friends, neighbors, and love interests of the various members of the family weigh heavily on the plot of the series, which seeks to address a real-life issue with each episode.</plot></movie>