<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE glossary>
<glossary><term><lable>301, 302</lable><define>Two obsessive-compulsives, a chef and an anorexic writer, are neighbors in an apartment building. The chef (301) tries to entice her neighbor to eat with fabulous meals. The writer (302) refuses to eat, and this refusal begins a turbulent relationship that forces both women to delve into their pasts of torment.</define></term><term><lable>The Box</lable><define>Norma and Arthur Lewis, a suburban couple with a young child, receive a simple wooden box as a gift, which bears fatal and irrevocable consequences. A mysterious stranger delivers the message that the box promises to bestow upon its owner $1 million with the press of a button. However, pressing this button will simultaneously cause the death of another human being somewhere in the world, someone they don't know. With just 24 hours to have the box in their possession, Norma and Arthur find themselves in the cross-hairs of a startling moral dilemma and must face the true nature of their humanity.</define></term><term><lable>A Gnome Named Gnorm</lable><define>Gnorm is just an average Gnome. But he wants to impress the lady Gnomes by doing something heroic. So he steals the Gnome's magic stones to expose them to sunlight to recharge them. When he gets to the surface, (Gnome's live deep underground) he witnesses a murder, and the killer ends up with his stones. Detective Casey, who was working a sting operation with the murdered man, (another detective) is blamed for botching the sting, and causing the death. Wanting to catch the killer to clear his name, he teams up with Gnorm, who he accidentally discovers. He is going to need Samantha's help, but she thinks he is a nut. You see, no one else knows about Gnorm.</define></term><term><lable>A hetedik testver</lable><define></define></term><term><lable>AEon Flux</lable><define>400 years in the future, set in the year 2415, Aeon Flux is a mysterious assassin. Four centuries after a virus nearly decimated the human race, leaving only five million survivors in a utopian city called Bregna. Aeon is struggling to destroy the Goodchild regime led by its namesake, Trevor Goodchild, the ruler of Bregna and a descendant of the man who found a cure for the deadly virus. As instructed by the Handler, Aeon is assigned to assassinate Goodchild, but there are deeper secrets to be discovered, and conspiracies to be foiled.</define></term><term><lable>All Men Are Liars</lable><define>Mick's father, Barry, sells the family piano, causing Mick's mother, Irene to leave. In order to raise enough money to buy the piano back, Mick dresses in his mother's clothes and becomes Michelle to join an all-girl band that has come into town for the annual harvest festival. Angela, the leader of the band, starts to question her sexuality when she begins to fall in love with Mick/Michelle.</define></term><term><lable>Andaz Apna Apna</lable><define>Amar and Prem are two rivals who belonging to middle-class families with no scope of future advancement. Both individually, without the knowledge of the other decide to take matters into their hands and find ways to get rich quickly. Chaos and acrimony result when both find each other at loggerheads when both arrive to win the hand of the daughter of multi-millionaire Ram Gopal Bajaj amidst considerable upheavals when Shyam, the twin brother of Ram, decides to do away with Ram and assume his identity and thus take over the estate of the Bajaj family.</define></term><term><lable>Angel Baby</lable><define>Two schizophrenics meet during therapy and fall passionately in love. Ahead of them lies the inevitable road to disaster...one they share to the end.</define></term><term><lable>Angel Heart</lable><define>Harry Angel has a new case, to find a man called Johnny Favourite. Except things aren't quite that simple, and Johnny doesn't want to be found. Let's just say that, amongst the period detail and beautiful scenery, it all gets really, really nasty.</define></term><term><lable>Anglagard - andra sommaren</lable><define></define></term><term><lable>Iron Man 2</lable><define>With the world now aware of his dual life as the armored superhero Iron Man, billionaire inventor Tony Stark faces pressure from the government, the press, and the public to share his technology with the military. Unwilling to let go of his invention, Stark, along with Pepper Potts, and James "Rhodey" Rhodes at his side, must forge new alliances - and confront powerful enemies.</define></term><term><lable>Another Froggy Evening</lable><define></define></term><term><lable>Antonia</lable><define>In an anonymous Dutch village, a sturdy, strong-willed matriarch looks back upon her life, the generations of family and friends gathered around her table, and ponders the cyclical nature of time.</define></term><term><lable>Apollo 13</lable><define>Based on the true story of the ill-fated 13th Apollo mission bound for the moon. Astronauts Lovell, Haise and Swigert were scheduled to fly Apollo 14, but are moved up to 13. It's 1970, and America have already achieved their lunar landing goal, so there's little interest in this "routine" flight.. until that is, things go very wrong, and prospects of a safe return fade.</define></term><term><lable>Art for Teachers of Children</lable><define>Jennifer, an intelligent but insecure 14-year-old student at a boarding school, seduces her married dormitory counselor, a photographer who has offered to teach her about his art and winds up shooting her in the nude. She is naive, and he manipulates her into an affair that eventually is discovered. Years later, as the photographer is being investigated by the FBI, the adult woman remembers her first love as a case of herself watching the artist who watched her.</define></term><term><lable>Atolladero</lable><define></define></term><term><lable>Aurora: Operation Intercept</lable><define>There have been two mysterious plane crashes in only 48 hours. The aircraft suddenly lose control and crash, killing everyone aboard. A woman of Russian descent, Francesca Zaborszin, the daughter of a slain Federal investigator, claims responsibility for the crashes. She believes her father was killed by the FBI as part of a cover-up operation and wishes to avenge his death by threatening to down more aircraft using the same electromagnetic pulse method. She also intends to crash a stolen military jet into the White House. There's no time to ground the planes: just enough time to try to stop her.</define></term><term><lable>The Discreet Charm of the Bourgeoisie</lable><define>Several bourgeois friends planning to get together for dinner experience a succession of highly unusual occurrences that interfere with their expected dining enjoyment.</define></term><term><lable>Barsaat</lable><define>Badal (Bobby Deol) is a naive but intelligent young man who comes from a small village to the big city. He is introduced to city life by Damru (Harish Patel) who now calls himself Danny. When Badal attends college, he meets with pretty and percocious, Tina Oberoi (Twinkle Khanna), and after a few misunderstanding and misadventures, both fall in love. This is not taken well by Tina's dad, (Raj Babbar), who hopes to marry Tina with his friend's (Bharat Kapoor) son. Tina's dad complains to the college principal (Vijay Kashyap), but Tina testifies in favour of Badal. Tina's dad then asks a corrupt cop, Neghi, who is the city's Assistant Commissioner of Police, for assistance. Neghi arrests Badal on trumped up charges and imprisons him. Badal's dad (Mukesh Khanna) also comes to the big city to try and make sense of why Badal ended up in prison. Tina's dad gives a contract to Neghi to have Badal killed, to which Neghi agrees and hires a gang of ruthless outlaws to hunt and kill Badal. He also pressurizes Tina not to acknowledge and meet Badal anymore, and Tina reluctantly agrees. Will Badal survive? Will Tina and Badal's love be fated to end tragically?</define></term><term><lable>Bastard Out of Carolina</lable><define>Difficult tale of poor, struggling South Carolinian mother &amp; daughter, who each face painful choices with their resolve and pride. Bone, the eldest daughter, and Anney her tired mother, grow both closer and farther apart: Anney sees Glen as her last chance.</define></term><term><lable>Beach Babes 2: Cave Girl Island</lable><define>Xena, Luna, and Sola leave Malibu but return to earth unexpectedly when Xena sneezes and crash lands them on a desert isle. After being threatened by dinosaurs and having a few close encounters with some primitive stud muffins, they tangle with the evil James T. Renford II, who has some sinister profit-making plans for the babes from space.</define></term><term><lable>Best of the Best 3: No Turning Back</lable><define></define></term><term><lable>Between the Teeth</lable><define></define></term><term><lable>Bikini Drive-In</lable><define>Kim Taylor inherits her grandfather's drive-in theatre. She must raise $25,000 over one weekend or the bank will take the property from her. She also has to deal with pesky capitalist J.B. Winston. This is a fun, not politically correct movie.</define></term><term><lable>Black Rose of Harlem</lable><define>A tragic love story set against the turbulent backdrop of the 1920's Chicago jazz clubs. Georgia, a beautiful black singer catches the eye of mobster Johnny Varona. But Johnny is betrothed to the daughter of mob boss Costanza, a man you don't say no to... and live! Can Johnny and Georgia find a way to fulfill their love -and- stay alive? Or will the mob prove to be an insurmountable force.</define></term><term><lable>Blank Cheque</lable><define>By accident, the 12-year-old Preston is given a blank check and when he fills in $1,000,000 - he is able to get it! He is having fun spending the money, but the gangsters who owned it want it back...</define></term><term><lable>Blondes Have More Guns</lable><define></define></term><term><lable>Rise</lable><define>The snoopy reporter Sadie Blake is called by her nerd colleague Ethan Mills that has deciphered a code and found an address in Koreatown from information of the Goth Tricia Rawlins about a bloody cult. Sadie does not give attention to Ethan, but when she sees on the front page of the news that Tricia has been found dead in a dumpster in Koreatown, she decides to visit the address. She finds an abandoned house with a gruesome basement full of blood and she immediately drives to Ethan's apartment. She finds the place in a complete mess and is abducted by a stranger and taken to Bishop, who wants to know what Tricia has told her. Then, Bishop and his mate Eve kill Sadie and they have a necrophilic threesome with her body. Later, Sadie awakes in the freezer of the morgue and sooner she realizes that she is a vampire and promises revenge to her sire.</define></term><term><lable>Blood and Wine</lable><define>Bob Rafelson has stated that this is the final part of an informal trilogy he started with "Five Easy Pieces" and continued with "The King Of Marvin Gardens". In the three, Nicholson has now played son, brother and father. In this one, Nicholson is a wealthy wine dealer who has distanced himself from his wife with his philandering and from his son with his negligence. After he steals a diamond necklace with the help of a safecracker partner, Victor, things start coming apart. His wife sets out to interrupt what she thinks is another one of his weekend dalliances, but is really his trip to pawn the jewels.</define></term><term><lable>Blue in the Face</lable><define>Wayne Wang's follow-up movie to Smoke presents a series of improvisational situations strung together to form a pastiche of Brooklyn's diverse ethnicity, offbeat humor, and essential humanity. Many of the same characters inhabiting Auggie Wren's Brooklyn Cigar Store in Smoke return here to expound on their philosophy of smoking, relationships, baseball, New York, and Belgian Waffles. Most of all, this is a movie about living life, off-the-cuff.</define></term><term><lable>Breaking Free</lable><define>When troubled, cynical teen Rick chooses service at a camp for the blind over serving time at a correctional facility, he thinks he's found the easy way out. Instead, it's the way to a new life. Friendship. Step by step, as Rick helps a blinded Gymnast rediscover the joys of competition through equestrian show jumping, they begin to take control of the most important journey of all... a journey called life.</define></term><term><lable>Broadcast Bombshells</lable><define>At WSEX, a local television broadcasting station in New Jersey, Kendall Saranski is the beautiful blond anchorwoman and the object of desire for all men working at the station including the libidos sportscaster Brian Kilgore and the station owner Mr. Buel. But Kendall is only interested in a kind-hearted stage hand named Neil whom is an old friend from her school days. Meanwhile, the conniving and ambitious brunette associate producer Amanda Cross, jealous of Kendall's rising fame, plots to further her career by having her tech boyfriend Gordon plot to bring Kendall and Brian's downfall using her seductive charms to go after Brian and have Gordon videotape it for future leverage against Brian. Other subplots include a mad bomber in the neighborhood blowing up various public places, a legendary grue sponsor named Frank Friendly holding onto his secret "three little words" as his motto, and a climatic fund-raiser telethon which brings all parties together for a final confrontation.</define></term><term><lable>Butterfly Kiss</lable><define>Eunice is walking along the highways of northern England from one filling station to another. She is searching for Judith, the woman, she says to be in love with. It's bad luck for the women at the cash desk not to be Judith, because Eunice is eccentric, angry and extreme dangerous. One day she meets Miriam, hard of hearing and a little ingenuous, who feels sympathy for Eunice and takes her home. Miriam is very impressed by Eunice's fierceness and willfulness and follows her on the search for Judith. Shocked by Eunice's cruelty she tries to make her a better person, but she looses ground herself.</define></term><term><lable>Down with Love</lable><define>An homage to the early 1960s sex comedies that starred Rock Hudson and Doris Day. The story follows a best-selling female advice author who has all the answers until a sly journalist playboy starts asking the questions.</define></term><term><lable>Cachito</lable><define></define></term><term><lable>Caged Heat 3000</lable><define>It's the year 3000 AD. The world's most dangerous women are banished to a remote asteroid 45 million light years from earth. Kira Murphy doesn't belong; wrongfully accused of a crime she did not commit, she's thrown in this interplanetary prison and left to her own defenses. But Kira's a fighter, and soon she finds herself in the middle of a female gang war; where everyone wants a piece of the action... and a piece of her! "Caged Heat 3000" takes the Women-in-Prison genre to a whole new level... and a whole new galaxy!</define></term><term><lable>Captured Alive</lable><define></define></term><term><lable>Miss Congeniality</lable><define>Undercover FBI agent Gracie Hart shows no signs of having any femininity in her demeanor or appearance. Generally a bright and capable agent, she is in trouble at work when she makes an error in judgment in a case which results in a near disaster. As such, one of her by-the-books colleagues, Eric Matthews, who has never shown any inclination of thinking outside the box, is assigned to lead the high profile case of a terrorist coined The Citizen instead of her, while she is facing possible disciplinary action. Gracie pieces together the evidence to determine that The Citizen's next target will be the Miss United States beauty pageant. The pageant represents everything that Gracie abhors. Despite Gracie's mannish demeanor, Eric, with no other undercover female agent remotely fitting the demographic, assigns her to go undercover as a pageant contestant to see if she can flush out The Citizen, who is perhaps one of the other contestants. Although the pageant administration, led by former winner Cathy Morningside and long time host Stan Fields, provide the FBI with access to the pageant, Cathy in particular is less than thrilled to have a non-credible Gracie posing as a contestant which she feels will ruin the pageant. The FBI enlist the assistance of former pageant contestant coach Victor Melling, who is facing his own disgrace associated with the pageant, to do the near impossible task of transforming Gracie, not only into a woman, but a credible beauty pageant contestant. As Gracie proceeds in the transformation, she gets to know the other contestants, not only as potential criminals, but also as real people. She also discovers that another sinister element is present at the pageant. She will do whatever it takes to quash that element and protect her new friends, namely the other innocent contestants. But now displaying some femininity, Gracie begins to have more womanly feelings herself and in turn attracts the attention of men, one in particular about who she is happy.</define></term><term><lable>Chamane</lable><define>A Yakut shaman and a Muscovite violinist escape a Soviet gulag on horseback. The shaman, Anatolia, promises to guide Dimitri, but Tolia is shot during the escape and dies. His spirit seems to guide Dimitri as the musician begins the arduous journey home across the snowbound taiga. In towns and settlements, Tolia's name seems magic, securing help for Dimitri. The horse, too, becomes savior and companion. When Dimitri finally reaches Irkutsk, he sells the horse to a Gypsy for train fare. While waiting overnight for the train, he meets a woman and they go dancing. After sex, in the dark of a freezing night, Dimitri makes a decision. The music of Tolia's trump is in his soul.</define></term><term><lable>The Station Agent</lable><define>When his only friend and co-worker dies, a young man born with dwarfism moves to an abandoned train depot in rural New Jersey. Though he tried to maintain a life of solitude, he is soon entangled with an artist who is struggling with a personal tragedy and an overly friendly Cuban hot-dog vendor.</define></term><term><lable>Chess Kids</lable><define></define></term><term><lable>CIA II: Target Alexa</lable><define>Alexa is one of the best, but her handiwork is done for terrorists. When she is finally captured, it is up to CIA agent Graver to turn her against her latest employer who has diplomatic immunity. Graver is one of the best at the CIA, but since the chip has been stolen, he has to use Alexa to find it. Alexa is too tough to turn on her own, so Graver must find the key to unlock her conviction. While he is working on Alexa, his boss is working on Graver.</define></term><term><lable>Clerks.</lable><define>Dante Hicks is a clerk at a local convenience store in New Jersey. On one particular Saturday morning, he gets called in on his day off. Once there, he must deal with multiple problems. The shutters outside won't open. His ex-girlfriend, whom he is still in love with, is getting married. His girlfriend, who bugs him about starting college, has revealed certain, uh...stuff about her past. His boss hasn't come in to take his place. He has a hockey game at 2 o'clock. Another ex has died, and today's the last day he can go to her wake. He must deal with customers that aren't so intelligent. His friend, Randal, a clerk at the video store next door, is even less dedicated to his job than Dante, and is always bothering Dante's customers. And the biggest problem of them all: HE'S NOT EVEN SUPPOSED TO BE THERE TODAY!! Can Dante manage it all?</define></term><term><lable>By Dawn's Early Light</lable><define>The crew of a nuclear bomber attack the Soviet Union while the President of the United States tries desperately to regain control of his military after his helicopter crashes during a limited nuclear exchange in this film with a scenario similar to _Fail Safe_ and _Dr. Strangelove_. Originally a made for cable movie, it concentrates on the relationship between a veteran pilot and his female co-pilot and the president's attempt to wrest control away from a war-mongering successor.</define></term><term><lable>Congo</lable><define>A megalomaniac C.E.O. sends his son into the dangerous African Congo on a quest for a source of diamonds large enough and pure enough to function as powerful laser communications transmitters (or is it laser weapons?). When contact is lost with his son and the team, his sometime daughter- in-law is sent after them. She is a former CIA operative and, accompanied by gee-whiz gadgetry and a few eccentric characters (including a mercenary, a researcher with a talking gorilla, and a a nutty Indiana-Jones-type looking for King Solomon's Mines), sets out to rescue her former fianc?. What they all discover is that often what we most want turns out to be the source of our downfall.</define></term><term><lable>Captain Corelli's Mandolin</lable><define>In 1941, Italy allies with Germany and ruthlessly conquers the much weaker country of Greece. On a remote Greek island, an Italian artillery garrison is established to maintain order. One Italian officer, Captain Corelli, adopts an attitude of mutual co-existence with the Greeks and engages in such activities as music festivals and courting the daughter of a local doctor. In 1943, however, after Italy surrenders to the Allies and changes sides in the war, Captain Corelli must defend the Greek island against a German invasion.</define></term><term><lable>Cosmic Voyage</lable><define></define></term><term><lable>Criminal Hearts</lable><define></define></term><term><lable>Crying Freeman</lable><define>A lethal assassin for a secret Chinese organisation, who sheds tears of regret each time he kills, is seen swiftly and mercilessly executing three Yakuza gangsters by a beautiful artist. She is captivated by the grace of his kill and later falls in love with him. An intense power struggle for the leadership of the Yakuza Clans ensues as they seek vengeance for the death of their leader. They soon realise the fatal mistake of underestimating the deadly skills of the Crying Freeman.</define></term><term><lable>Cyber Bandits</lable><define>A navigator aboard a millionaire's yacht, Jack Morris discovers that the millionaire's mistress has stolen the data for his secret Virtual Reality. To escape, they encrypt, miniaturize, and tattoo the data onto Jack's PL:back. The pair share a VR adventure on the run from the Millionaire's thugs, meeting up with a wild series of characters.</define></term><term><lable>Cyber Vengeance</lable><define>The year is 2005. The prison system is run by the private sector. Business tycoon R.D. Crowley, has created a virtual reality prison. The prisoner's bodies are locked in suspended animation while their minds traverse the lethal labyrinth of games Crowley designed for them. Crowley allows wealthy sportsmen to participate, for a price, in deadly VR combat with the prisoners. Will breaks into the prison and attempts to eradicate the VR technology. Seduced by his VR girlfriend he becomes addicted to VR. Will is caught and thrown into the lethal time-traveling web of Crowley's virtual hunt. With their lives at stake, Will and the prisoners must escape certain death, and destroy the VR prison.</define></term><term><lable>Cyborg 3: The Creation</lable><define>Prepare yourself for the all too deadly future. Cash, the heroine of Cyborg 2, is living safe in the free zone. But not for long. Biomechanical problems are taking down her systems and a visit to a doctor in Silica confirms her worst fears. She is more then a marvel of cyborg technology. She is the first of her kind to become a creator-she is pregnant.</define></term><term><lable>Dai lao bai shou</lable><define></define></term><term><lable>Dark Side of Genius</lable><define>Julian Jons is a talented but troubled young artist. He has just been released from an asylum, where he has spent the last seven years for the murder of Anna, his girlfriend/model. Attempting to start painting again, he is pursued by journalist Jennifer Cole, who is intrigued by this complex, brooding man. Against the backdrop of the modern art world, she begins to dig into the past, fully aware that it holds painful memories for Julian, and perhaps danger for herself.</define></term><term><lable>Das grosse Spiel des Lebens</lable><define></define></term><term><lable>Dead Man Walking</lable><define>A convicted murderer on Death Row and the nun who befriends him. Through the portrayal of finely drawn characters and their interactions as the days, hours, and minutes tick down to the condemned man's execution, powerful emotions are unleashed. While Matthew Poncelet and Sister Prejean desperately try to gain a stay of execution from the governor or the courts, scenes are intercut from the brutal crime, gradually revealing the truth about the events that transpired. In addition to her temporal help, the nun also tries to reach out spiritually and assist as a guide to salvation.</define></term><term><lable>Deadly Outbreak</lable><define>A terrorist group lead by Colonel Baron has taken over an Israeli biochemical weapon laboratory. Colonel Baron wants to get his hands on a new secret weapon developed by Dr. Allie Levin. Dutton Hatfield from the U.S. embassy must help Dr. Levin keep her invention away from the bad guys.</define></term><term><lable>Decoy</lable><define>Gangster Frank Olins is to die in the gas chamber much to the dismay of his girlfriend Margot Shelby as he is carrying the secret of the location of $400,000 with him. Margot seduces gangster Jim Vincent to get him to engineer the removal of Olins' body from the prison immediately after he dies in the gas chamber. She takes prison doctor Craig away from his nurse/girl friend and gets him to administer an antidote for cyanide gas poisoning. During the removal of Olins' body, the hearse driver is killed by Tommy. The revived Olins gives Margot half of a map showing the money location and Vincent, in a fit of jealousy, kills Olins and takes the other half. Because the doctor's plates on his car will get them through the police roadblocks, Vincent and Margot take him with them on the money hunt.</define></term><term><lable>Denise Calls Up</lable><define>A group of friends in New York, working away at their PCs and laptops, keep in touch exclusively by phone and fax. They are all too busy to meet face to face. Gale plays matchmaker, by phone, to Jerry and Barbara who, in turn, hit it off beautifully...via phone and fax. Martin gets a telephone call from someone he's never met. It's Denise, with some extraordinary news. Tapping away at his computer all the while, he develops a sort of friendship with Denise...via phone. And so it goes as the friends, tap, tap, tapping away, share news, hopes, and dreams...via phone and fax. Finally Gale has an unfortunate encounter with a phone, Denise has some more news for Martin, and Frank plans a gala New Year's Eve party, but will he answer the door?</define></term><term><lable>Desert Winds</lable><define>Jackie and Eugene are joined by a mystical wind tunnel which enables them to speak across a 500-mile desert. Believed by the Indians to be an omen of good luck, the wind inspires both characters to face their fears and follow their hearts.</define></term><term><lable>Devil in a Blue Dress</lable><define>It is 1948 in LA and Ezikeal "Easy" Rawlins, an African-American World War II veteran, is looking for work. At his friend's bar, he is introduced to a white man, DeWitt Albright, who is looking for someone to help him find a missing white woman assumed to be hiding somewhere in LA's Black community. This woman, Daphane Monet, happens to be the fianc?e of a wealthy "blue blood," Todd Carter, who is currently the favorite in the city's mayoralty race. Daphane Monet is known to frequent the Black jazz clubs in LA. Easy, innocently, accepts Albright's offer; however, he quickly finds himself amidst murder, crooked cops, ruthless politicians, and brutalizing hoodlums. This is a Chandler-esque "who-done-it" with an African-American theme.</define></term><term><lable>Di xia cai jue</lable><define></define></term><term><lable>Die Hard: With a Vengeance</lable><define>John McClane is now almost a full-blown alcoholic and is suspended from the NYPD. But when a bomb goes off in the Bonwit Teller Department Store the police go insane trying to figure out what's going on. Soon, a man named Simon calls and asks for McClane. Simon tells Inspector Walter Cobb that McClane is going to play a game called "Simon Says". He says that McClane is going to do the tasks he assigns him. If not, he'll blow off another bomb. With the help of a Harlem electrician, John McClane must race all over New York trying to figure out the frustrating puzzles that the crafty terrorist gives him. But when a bomb goes off in a subway station right by the Federal Reserve (the biggest gold storage in the world) things start to get heated up.</define></term><term><lable>Die Sturzflieger</lable><define>Rio Kowalski is a merchant and runs a starship along with his cyborg Max. As times aren't well he must take passengers on his freighter. When the undestroyable and multi-million dollar insured starship Titanius is stranded Rio sees his time has come. He would just have to manage to be the first to find the Titanius. However first he has to get rid of his passengers...</define></term><term><lable>Dr. Jekyll and Ms. Hyde</lable><define>In New York in 1995 Dr. Richard Jacks is a creator of perfumes. Thus he spends his days inventing new colorful and well smelling potions and certainly caring for his girlfriend Sarah Carver. But when he discovers that his greatgrandfather, called Dr. Jekyll, was a scientist with revoluntionary discoveries, he tries to follow the footsteps of his ancestor and creates more and more delicate potions until one of them converts him into a spectacular superwoman: Helen Hyde. Knowing that Richard has no clue of her existence Helen enforces a professional career at the back of her "creator".</define></term><term><lable>Driftwood</lable><define>Blaire Farrow has grown tired of her job as a client liaison for a wish granting foundation. She and her coworker Jimmy bicker every day, and she hasn't had a date in what feels like centuries. When Blaire decides to take in a handsome amnesiac, she thinks she's found everything she's ever wanted. But are there strings attached? AFI's Directing Workshop for Women presents a new take on an old tale about the search for love, the pain of longing, and the surprising power of a wish.</define></term><term><lable>Dukhovnye golosa. Iz dnevnikov voyny. Povestvovanie v pyati chastyakh</lable><define></define></term><term><lable>Dypets ensomhet</lable><define></define></term><term><lable>Eat Drink Man Woman</lable><define>Senior Master Chef Chu lives in a large house in Taipei with his three unmarried daughters, Jia-Jen, a chemistry teacher converted to Christianity, Jia-Chien, an airline executive, and Jia-Ning, a student who also works in a fast food restaurant. Life in the house revolves around the ritual of an elaborate dinner each Sunday, and the love lives of all the family members.</define></term><term><lable>Eight O'Clock, at Your Place</lable><define>Javiera and Antonio are a young couple with two daughters and another on the way. But beneath the superficial tranquillity of their marriage hides a passionate relationship between Antonio and his wife's sister, Antonieta. The love triangle begins to lose its delicate balance when Antonieta loses her purse. A mysterious voice on the telephone extorts the lovers, moving them to take unusual actions and to confront one another with blame and doubt, ultimately forcing them to explore the true value of their relationship.</define></term><term><lable>Ilektra</lable><define>A powerful rendering of the tragedy of Elektra by Euripides. The film begins with a summary treatment without dialogue of the action of the preceding play in the trilogy, The Agamemnon, in which the wicked Queen Clytemnestra and her lover Aesgisthes murder her husband Agamemnon upon his return from the Trojan War.</define></term><term><lable>England, My England</lable><define></define></term><term><lable>Eno nakano bokuno mura</lable><define>Tells of the childhood of two nine-year-old twins in a rural village in Japan after World War 2. Includes the boys relationships with their schoolteacher mother, civil servant father, elderly landlord, a rough new boy at the school, and three mysterious spirits in the form of old women.</define></term><term><lable>Terminator 2: Judgment Day</lable><define>Nearly 10 years have passed since Sarah Connor was targeted for termination by a cyborg from the future. Now her son, John, the future leader of the resistance, is the target for a newer, more deadly terminator. Once again, the resistance has managed to send a protector back to attempt to save John and his mother Sarah.</define></term><term><lable>Fallen Angels</lable><define>A disillusioned killer embarks on his last hit but first he has to overcome his affections for his cool, detached partner. Thinking it's dangerous and improper to become involved with a colleague he sets out to find a surrogate for his affections. Against the sordid and surreal urban nightscape (set in contemporary Hong Kong), he crosses path with a strange drifter looking for her mysterious ex-boyfriend and an amusing mute trying to get the world's attention in his own unconventional ways.</define></term><term><lable>Feast of July</lable><define>This romantic story, based on a novel by H.E. Bates and set in late 19th century England, rests on sibling rivalry for the affections of a woman who comes to live with their family by happenstance. In time, she decides to accept the marriage proposal of the youngest of the three sons, to the surprise of all. However, a man whom she had once loved and who had abandoned her (after making false promises) comes back into her life. The appearance of this scoundrel sets into motion a tragic series of events that eventually engulfs everyone.</define></term><term><lable>Felidae</lable><define>After his owner relocates, the cat Francis in involved in a series of cat murders in the new neighborhood. Francis tries to solve the murder cases with others - including Claudandus, a very knowledgable and old cat.</define></term><term><lable>Firestorm</lable><define>Firefighter Jesse Graves has to save ornithologist Jennifer and other people caught in a forest fire, which was set up by the lawyer of convicted killer Earl Shaye, who escaped from the prison with several of his inmates posing as firefighters to recover $37,000,000 in stashed loot.</define></term><term><lable>Frank and Ollie</lable><define></define></term><term><lable>Charlie's Angels: Full Throttle</lable><define>The Angels--Natalie, Dylan, and Alex are back again but this time they're preparing for a strike without even warning as they go undercover to retrieve two missing silver bands. These are no ordinary rings. They contain valuable encrypted information that reveal the new identities of every person in the Federal Witness Protection Program. When witnesses start turning up dead, only the Angels, using their expertise as masters of disguise, espionage and martial arts can stop the perpetrator, a mysterious "fallen" Angel. Aided by their trusty colleague, Jimmy Bosley, the Angels' adventure begins at a remote Mongolian outpost and ends only after Dylan is forced to face a dark secret from her past--a secret that puts the lives of her two best friends in danger.</define></term><term><lable>Genesi: La creazione e il diluvio</lable><define>An all-enveloping darkness. Suddenly, a child's voice, frightened, questioning, pierces the darkness... The first flickering rays of light begin to sculpt mysterious shapes out of the darkness ... Among them, a very old man. He reassures the child, exhorting him to see the wonders of the earth. And it is with this child's eyes that we will witness the creation of the world. Nature comes to life at the first light of dawn, recreating the seven days of the Creation. Adam appears, and is soon joined by Eve. Paradise could be theirs, but as time goes by, they grow restless, inquisitive... They approach the Tree of Knowledge - and discover pain, suffering and mortality. Their sons Cain and Abel play out a story that will continue to darken the Creation until the end of time. And angered by the corruption of Cain's progeny, by the lust and greed ruling the cities, God vows to wipe away his creatures and begin anew. With Noah and his family. The ark is built, the animals led into their pens, and the rain begins beating on the timbers, flooding the land, bringing fear and death. When the rains have devastated the world, the waters recede, the ark touches ground, and the dove sent out by Noah returns with an olive branch - the sign of new life and of a new pact with God.</define></term><term><lable>God and Gun</lable><define>God and Gun is a film on contemporary events A daringly different film. It bringsforth authentically the inside realities of today's politics. God and Gun advocates the truth that power lies in the hands of people and not politicians. The voice of the people is the voice of god.</define></term><term><lable>The Player</lable><define>A studio script screener gets on the bad side of a writer by not accepting his script. The writer is sending him threatening postcards. The screener tries to identify the writer in order to pay him off so he'll be left alone, and then in a case of mistaken identity gone awry, he accidentally gives the writer solid ammunition for blackmail. This plot is written on a backdrop of sleazy Hollywood deals and several subplots involving the politics of the industry.</define></term><term><lable>Gospel According to Harry</lable><define>The film is a biblical soap-opera whose action unfolds in the Californian desert. Karen and Wes's marriage is crumbling apart - like a sandcastle. Karen can't even make love to her husband any more - the sand has managed to get everywhere. Harry, a tax collector, is a witness to this marriage falling apart. As a civil servant he hears Wes confession. However he isn't able to help him. The omnipotent eye of television glitters above the desert - that raw allegory of America where neither the white nor the black have it good. If Samuel Beckett and Joan Collins had a romance, then their child would look like this film.</define></term><term><lable>Grid Runners</lable><define>Scientist brings virtual reality characters to life. Two are women from the cybersex game site. The third is a warrior who wants to unleash the rest of the bad guys from the virtual reality underworld. A border cop must defeat the virtual reality warrior while learning to relate to one of the cybersex babes.</define></term><term><lable>Hikayatul jawahiri thalath</lable><define>A Palestinian boy becomes entranced with a beautiful Gypsy girl and a fairy tale world she weaves amidst conflict in Gaza. The children explore nature, mysticism and what their future holds, while learning to live with the surrounding brutality c. 1990. Yusef's family scrapes by in a seaside camp while his father's in prison and his heavily-armed brother's on the run, parrying with Israeli troops. Salah, Yusef's schoolmate from a well-off Arab family strives faithfully to assist them, while Yusef helps an elderly, blind neighbor escape from his lonely abandonment into the North American dreamworld he's waited so long for.</define></term><term><lable>Hollow Reed</lable><define>Following the break-up of his marriage after revealing his homosexuality, GP Martin Wyatt loses custody of his son Oliver to his now ex-wife Hannah and her new partner Frank. It is not long, however, until Oliver appears at the house of Martin and his new lover Tom claiming to have been beaten up by boys in the park. After another incident, Martin puts two and two together and comes to the conclusion that Frank has been beating Oliver without Hannah's knowledge. Martin then begins a long courtroom custody battle to win back his son.</define></term><term><lable>How to Make an American Quilt</lable><define>Finn is a young graduate student, finishing a master's thesis, and preparing for marriage to her fiance Sam. But thoughts of the end of the free life, and a potential summer fling, intrude. She goes home to her grandmother, where, over the making of her wedding gift by a group of quilting-bee friends, laughter, bickering, love, and advice lead her toward a more open-eyed examination of her course.</define></term><term><lable>Hubungan jenayah</lable><define>Ray is a Rambo-like Manila cop who travels to Hong Kong on assignment. He searches for his girl friend Lina, and finds her - addicted to drugs. Heung Lan, his ex-partner, is an undercover Hong Kong cop investigating weapons smuggling. She provokes the smugglers by intercepting several shipments in Hong Kong, leading to several good, although brief fights. The drug smuggler kills Lina, and Ray swears vengeance. The head of the gang then returns to the Philippines, and with him, the action shifts back to the Philippines. The lady cop gets more than what she hoped for.</define></term><term><lable>In the Army Now</lable><define>Two misguided youths join the reserves to make some money for their entrepreneurial dreams. No sooner than they finish basic training are they called up to do their part to save the free world.</define></term><term><lable>The Philadelphia Story</lable><define>Philadelphia socialites Tracy Lord and C.K. Dexter Haven married impulsively, with their marriage and subsequent divorce being equally passionate. They broke up when Dexter's drinking became excessive, it a mechanism to cope with Tracy's unforgiving manner to the imperfect, imperfections which Dexter admits he readily has. Two years after their break-up, Tracy is about to remarry, the ceremony to take place at the Lord mansion. Tracy's bridegroom is nouveau riche businessman and aspiring politician George Kittredge, who is otherwise a rather ordinary man and who idolizes Tracy. The day before the wedding, three unexpected guests show up at the Lord mansion: Macaulay Connor (Mike to his friends), Elizabeth Imbrie - the two who are friends of Tracy's absent brother, Junior - and Dexter himself. Dexter, an employee of the tabloid Spy magazine, made a deal with its publisher and editor Sidney Kidd to get a story on Tracy's wedding - the wedding of the year - in return for Kidd not publishing a salacious story with accompanying photographs of Tracy's father, Seth Lord, with a New York showgirl named Tina Marra. In reality, Mike and Liz are the reporter and photographer respectively for Spy. Mike and Liz don't particularly like this assignment or working for Kidd, but they need to make a living as their chosen other fields as serious writer and painter don't pay the bills. A suspicious Tracy is onto them, the entire truth which Dexter admits to her. Tracy decides to turn the tables on Mike and Liz. However, hours before the wedding, as the more self-assured Dexter and Liz get to work on how to get the Lords out from under Spy's threats, Tracy and Mike, both inebriated, go on a journey of self-discovery with Tracy ultimately coming to her realizations a little faster than Mike.</define></term><term><lable>From Hell</lable><define>It is 1888 in London, and the unfortunate poor lead horrifying lives in the city's deadliest slum, Whitechapel. Harassed by gangs and forced to walk the streets for a living, Mary Kelly and her small group of companions trudge on through this daily misery, their only consolation being that things can't get any worse. Yet things somehow do when their friend Ann is kidnapped and they are drawn into a conspiracy with links higher up than they could possibly imagine. The kidnapping is soon followed by the gruesome murder of another woman, Polly, and it becomes apparent that they are being hunted down, one by one. Sinister even by Whitechapel standards, the murder grabs the attention of Inspector Fred Abberline, a brilliant yet troubled man whose police work is often aided by his psychic abilities. Abberline becomes deeply involved with the case, which takes on personal meaning to him when he and Mary begin to fall in love. But as he gets closer to the truth Whitechapel becomes more and more dangerous for Abberline, Mary, and the other girls. Whoever is responsible for the grisly acts is not going to give up his secret without a fight....will they be able to survive the avenging force that has been sent after them from hell?</define></term><term><lable>Jeffrey</lable><define>Jeffery, a young gay man in New York, decides that sex is too much and decided to become celibate. He immediately meets the man of his dreams and must decide whether or not love is worth the danger of a boyfriend dying.</define></term><term><lable>Jin yu man tang</lable><define>Kit is a gangster looking to start a new life as a chef in Canada, so he can be closer to his girlfriend. But in his struggle to learn the fine art of cuisine, he runs across a red-headed beauty who will change his plans, and soon finds himself off in search of the retired master who can teach him how to win in the ultimate cooking challenge.</define></term><term><lable>La Ceremonie</lable><define>Sophie, a quiet and shy maid working for the upper-class family Lelievre, hides her illiteracy under the cloak of a perfect household and obedience. She finds a friend in the energetic and uncompromising postmaster Jeanne, who encourages her to stand up against her bourgeois employers. Things start to escalate as the Lelievres find out that Sophie can't read and has brought Jeanne into their house against their wish.</define></term><term><lable>La cite de la peur</lable><define>Odile Deray est attach? de presse pour le film "Red is Dead". Mais au festival de Cannes, personne ne veut regarder un tel navet. Pourtant, les gens changent d'avis au moment o? les projectionnistes meurtent les un apr?s les autres, assassin? par le m?chant de "Red is Dead". Serge Kazamarov est envoy? sur place pour prot?ger la victime suivante. Quelques jours plus tard, la salle est comble et m?me le gratin de Cannes est sur place...</define></term><term><lable>Le bonheur est dans le pre</lable><define>Francis, the boss of a small plumbing supply company, is harassed by tax collectors, striking employees, and an impossible wife and daughter. His only joy is sharing lunch with his friend Gerard. Then a TV show called "where are you?" shows a woman from Gers who is searching for her husband who disappeared 28 years ago. The lost husband looks like an identical twin of Francis...</define></term><term><lable>The New World</lable><define>Captain Smith is spared his mutinous hanging sentence after captain Newport's ship arrives in 1607 to found Jamestown, an English colony in Virginia. The initially friendly natives, who have no personal property concept, turns hostile after a 'theft' is 'punished' violently on the spot. During an armed exploration, Smith is captured, but spared when the chief's favorite daughter Pocahontas pleads for the stranger who soon becomes her lover and learns to love their naive 'savage' way of harmonious life. Ultimately he returns to the grim fort, which would starve hadn't she arranged for Indian generosity. Alas, each side soon brands their own lover a traitor, so she is banished and he flogged as introduction to slavish toiling. Changes turn again, leading Smiyth to accept a northern-more mission and anglicized Pocahontas, believing him dead, becoming the mother of aristocratic new lover John Rolfe's son. They'll meet again for a finale in England.</define></term><term><lable>Le vent du Wyoming</lable><define></define></term><term><lable>Lunarcop</lable><define>A cop from the moon is sent to the Earth, now possessed by motorcycle-riding "Mad Max"-like inhabitants, to stop a serum from being released that he believes is going to destroy the Earth...</define></term><term><lable>Lurking Fear</lable><define>The town of Leffert's Corners has been plagued by unearthly beings for decades, and now there is only a few people left, including the local priest and a woman traumatised by the death of her sister. But when John Martense turns up to claim his illicit family fortune, with bad guys in pursuit, the last stand had become a lot more complicated. Supposedly based on the writings of H P Lovecraft.</define></term><term><lable>Ma ma fan fan</lable><define></define></term><term><lable>Mallrats</lable><define>Brodie Bruce, a Sega and comic book obsessed college student, and his best friend, TS Quint, are both dumped by their girlfriends on the same day, and to deal with their loss, they both go to the local mall. Along the way, they meet up with some friends, including Willam, a guy who stares at Magic Eye pictures, desprately trying to see the hidden image; Gwen, one of TS's ex-girlfriends; and Jay &amp; Silent Bob, of Clerks fame. Eventually, they decide to try and win back their significant others, and take care of their respective nemesises (TS's girlfriend's father, and a store clerk who hates the two for not having any shopping agenda).</define></term><term><lable>Man with a Plan</lable><define>Fred Tuttle, faced with his father's impending hip operation and his failing farm, needs to make a six-digit salary with a fourth-grade education. So he runs for U.S. Representative from Vermont with a markedly bizarre campaign. Will he triumph over incumbent Bill Blachly?</define></term><term><lable>Men of War</lable><define>Nick Gunar (Dolph Lundgren) is a burnt-out, jaded and hard-up former mercenary who is having a difficult time adjusting to civilian life. At the end of his rope, he is hired by the Nitro Mine Corporation to strong-arm the natives of a South China Sea island into giving up their rights to its valuable mineral resources. Nick loathes the thought of another mission, but this seemingly easy job will earn him enough money to get back with his estranged family. He recruits some of his former mercenary buddies to help him with the job. The island people refuse to give up their land and Nick decides to help them fight the greedy corporation that hired him. The island and its people bring Nick back to life. He finally finds something worth fighting for and a place to call home. As greed and treachery begin to unravel, Nick's band of mercenaries choose sides. Some are with him and others, still working for the corporation, will stop at nothing to destroy him.</define></term><term><lable>Midaq Alley</lable><define>Based on the Nobel Prize Winner's novel, the Egyptian Naguib Mahfouz. The story, translated from El Cairo to Mexico City's downtown, narrates the life of the members of the neighbourhood and the connection between them Don Ru, the owner of the local pub; Eusebia, his wife; Chava, his son and Abel his friend, who emigrate to USA in search of fortune; Susanita, the single landtender always dreaming to marry a good man; Guicho, the pub's employee, who extracts the money when Don Ru is not there and finally marries Susanita; Alma, the very good looking girl, the Abel's dream, who becomes a luxury prostitute while he's away; Jimmy, the handsome young man Don Ru becomes infatuated with, etc. This movie won the Ariel (the Mexican Oscar) as best movie in 1995.</define></term><term><lable>Milk Money</lable><define>Young Frank and his pals get an idea for the ultimate in excitement. They decide to pool their savings, bicycle to the nearby Big City, and hire some woman of the streets to strip for them. Things do not work out that simply, but they do meet V, a Hooker With A Heart Of Gold, who ends up giving them a ride home. Soon she is living in Frank's treehouse, unbeknownst to Frank's widowed father Tom, who thinks she is one of Frank's teachers. Soon, however, the evil Waltzer comes looking for V.</define></term><term><lable>Mr. &amp; Mrs. Smith</lable><define>John and Jane Smith are a normal married couple, living a normal life in a normal suburb, working normal jobs...well, if you can call secretly being assassins "normal". But neither Jane nor John knows about their spouse's secret, until they are surprised to find each other as targets! But on their quest to kill each other, they learn a lot more about each other than they ever did in five (or six) years of marriage.</define></term><term><lable>Mommy</lable><define>An unofficial "sequel" to "The Bad Seed", Patty McCormack's "Mommy" is psychotically obsessed with her 12-year-old daughter Jessica Ann -- so much so that when she finds out Jessica didn't get the "Student of the Year" award again, she solves the problem by murdering the teacher who didn't recommend her for it. She dismisses the killing as inconsequential ("a minor accident"), but the homicide detective assigned to the case suspects her immediately, and an insurance investigator who also suspects her tries to get close to Jessica Ann to find out what really happened.</define></term><term><lable>Mortal Kombat</lable><define>Based on the popular video game of the same name "Mortal Kombat" tells the story of an ancient tournament where the best of the best of different Realms fight each other. The goal - ten wins to be able to legally invade the losing Realm. Outworld has so far collected nine wins against Earthrealm, so it's up to Lord Rayden and his fighters to stop Outworld from reaching the final victory...</define></term><term><lable>Murder in the First</lable><define>Henri Young stole five dollars from a post office and ended up going to prison - to the most famous, or infamous, prison of them all: Alcatraz. He tried to escape, failed, and spent three years and two months in solitary confinement - in a dungeon, with no light, no heat and no toilet. Milton Glenn, the assistant warden, who was given free reign by his duty-shirking superior, was responsible for Young's treatment. Glenn even took a straight razor and hobbled Young for life. After three years and two months, Young was taken out of solitary confinement and put with the rest of the prisoners. Almost immediately, Young took a spoon and stabbed a fellow prisoner in the neck, killing him. Now, Young is on trial for murder, and if he's convicted he'll go to the gas chamber. An eager and idealistic young attorney, James Stamphill, is given this impossible case, and argues before a shocked courtroom that Young had a co-conspirator. The true murderer, he says, was Alcatraz.</define></term><term><lable>Murdered Innocence</lable><define></define></term><term><lable>Music for the Movies: Toru Takemitsu</lable><define></define></term><term><lable>Mut ohne Befehl - Widerstand und Verfolgung in Stuttgart 1933-1945</lable><define></define></term><term><lable>Nico Icon</lable><define>A look into the many lives of Christa P?ffgen, otherwise known as Nico; from cutie German m?dchen to the first of the supermodels, to glamorous diva of the Velvet Underground, to cult item, junkie and hag. Many faces for the same woman, whom, you realize, just couldn't bring herself to care enough to live.</define></term><term><lable>No hoi wai lung</lable><define></define></term><term><lable>The Maltese Falcon</lable><define>Spade and Archer is the name of a San Francisco detective agency. That's for Sam Spade and Miles Archer. The two men are partners, but Sam doesn't like Miles much. A knockout, who goes by the name of Miss Wanderly, walks into their office; and by that night everything's changed. Miles is dead. And so is a man named Floyd Thursby. It seems Miss Wanderly is surrounded by dangerous men. There's Joel Cairo, who uses gardenia-scented calling cards. There's Kasper Gutman, with his enormous girth and feigned civility. Her only hope of protection comes from Sam, who is suspected by the police of one or the other murder. More murders are yet to come, and it will all be because of these dangerous men -- and their lust for a statuette of a bird: the Maltese Falcon.</define></term><term><lable>She's the Man</lable><define>Here's the thing Viola's soccer team at Cornwall got cut so she wanted to join the boys team, but they did not allow. So she thought "If you can't join them, beat them". And so she does, she disguises herself as her twin brother Sebastian, and goes out for the Illyria Boys Soccer Team. But she didn't plan falling in love with her roommate Duke. But the thing is Duke has his eye on Olivia. The thing that makes matters worse Olivia starts to fall for Sebastian who actually is a girl and she/he has a sensitive side. If things couldn't get more problematical the real Sebastian (who is in London working on his music) comes home early. He arrives on campus and has no clue that he was replaced by his twin sister.</define></term><term><lable>Pigalle</lable><define>In the seedy neon-lit underworld of the Pigalle district of Paris, animalistic survival obscures all moral codes. Rival drug dealers use three minor figures as pawns in their murderous manoeuvres. Divine is a transexual, a performer in a club, the lover of Fifi, a man who's a street hustler and petty thief. Fifi, in turn, loves Divine but flirts with V?ra, a striptease dancer and peep show attraction. When Divine is bullied into giving information to one drug dealer, the opposition uses V?ra as bait to enlist Fifi as a hitman.</define></term><term><lable>Poison Ivy II</lable><define>Lily is a sheltered art student from Michigan going to school in California. She finds an apartment and her roommates aren't quite normal. One day she finds a box of items belonging to a girl she's never met before. But in the box are nude pictures of the girl and her diary. Lily begins reading the diary and realizes that she's going to change her life and become a wild woman! She begins dating a guy and at the same time her art instructor begins to lust after her. The struggle begins when her boyfriend thinks she's unfaithful to him and her art teacher becomes obsessed.</define></term><term><lable>Pret-a-Porter</lable><define>A fashion show in Paris draws the usual bunch of people; designers, reporters, models, magazine editors, photographers. Lots of unconnected stories which all revolve around this show, and an all-star cast.</define></term><term><lable>Project Shadowchaser II</lable><define>Terrorists led by an android take over a nuclear plant and threaten to launch a missile at Washington. While the authorities desperately attempt to negotiate, the terrorists persue their real goal. A plant worker, her son and a tough-guy repair man have other ideas, and attempt to stop the terrorists from inside the plant.</define></term><term><lable>Below</lable><define>In the dark silence of the sea during World War II, the submarine U.S.S. Tiger Shark prowls on what should be a routine rescue mission. But for the shell-shocked crew, trapped together in the sub's narrow corridors and constricted spaces, this is about to become a journey into the sensory delusions, mental deceptions and runaway fear that lurk just below the surface of the ocean and deep inside the human psyche.</define></term><term><lable>Redheads</lable><define></define></term><term><lable>Restoration</lable><define>An aspiring young physician, Robert Merivel found himself in the service of King Charles II and saves the life of someone close to the King. Merivel joins the King's court and lives the high life provided to someone of his position. Merivel is ordered to marry his King's mistress in order to divert the queens suspicions. He is given one order by the king and that is not to fall in love. The situation worsens when Merivel finds himself in love with his new wife. Eventually, the King finds out and relieves Merivel of his position and wealth. His fall from grace leaves Merivel where he first started. And through his travels and reunions with an old friend, he rediscovers his love for true medicine and what it really means to be a physician.</define></term><term><lable>Richard III</lable><define>William Shakespeare's classic play is brought into the present with the setting as Great Britian in the 1930s. Civil war has erupted with the House of Lancaster on one side, claiming the right to the British throne and hoping to bring freedom to the country. Opposing is the House of York, commanded by the infamous Richard who rules over a fascist government and hopes to install himself as a dictator monarch.</define></term><term><lable>Clerks.</lable><define>Dante Hicks is a clerk at a local convenience store in New Jersey. On one particular Saturday morning, he gets called in on his day off. Once there, he must deal with multiple problems. The shutters outside won't open. His ex-girlfriend, whom he is still in love with, is getting married. His girlfriend, who bugs him about starting college, has revealed certain, uh...stuff about her past. His boss hasn't come in to take his place. He has a hockey game at 2 o'clock. Another ex has died, and today's the last day he can go to her wake. He must deal with customers that aren't so intelligent. His friend, Randal, a clerk at the video store next door, is even less dedicated to his job than Dante, and is always bothering Dante's customers. And the biggest problem of them all: HE'S NOT EVEN SUPPOSED TO BE THERE TODAY!! Can Dante manage it all?</define></term><term><lable>Sebastian - When Everybody Knows</lable><define>16 year old Sebastian behaves strangely. He stays alone in his room for hours thinking and doesn't talk to his parents as he used to. He refuses to explain to them what his problem is. The truth is that he slowly discovers that he feels stangely for his best friend Ulf. Soon he is going to accept his true self - that he is gay and that he is also in love with his best friend Ulf.</define></term><term><lable>Separate Lives</lable><define>The e-cop Tom Beckwith has just quit his police job in order to study psychology. But his professor, Lauren Porter, is more interested in his criminology abilities than in his progress in psychology. Because of traumatic circumstances during her childhood she is suffering from schizophrenia, and it looks like her other ego has just killed somebody. So Tom Beckwith tries to help her by observing her, combining his professional abilities as an ex-cop and his recently gained knowledge of psychology.</define></term><term><lable>Women in Revolt</lable><define>This film is a satire of the women's liberation movement, staring a trio of female impersonators. Candy is an aloof heiress caught in an unhappy relationship with her brother. Jackie is a virginal intellectual who believes women are oppressed in contemporary American society. And Holly is a nymphomaniac who has come to loathe men, despite her attraction to them. Together, they join a militant feminist group, P.I.G. (Politically Involved Girls), but their newfound liberation doesn't make them any happier.</define></term><term><lable>Shaolin Popey</lable><define></define></term><term><lable>Sherlock: Undercover Dog</lable><define>Billy, 10, a dreamer, wants to be taken seriously so he can live with his toy-designer father on Catalina Island. Billy's plans get seriously spoilt when Sherlock, a talking police dog, demands his help to rescue his police detective handler kidnaped by smugglers. But Sherlock likes to keep his talking a closely-guarded secret. So now no one will take Billy seriously until he rescues the kidnaped detective and catches the smugglers...</define></term><term><lable>Showgirls</lable><define>Nomi Malone, a mysterious young girl with the ambition to dance embarks on a journey to Las Vegas to become a showgirl in a high-class hotel show. There she meets Molly, a seamstress at the Stardust Hotel and the two quickly become good friends. She gets a job as a lap dancer at the seedy Cheetah Club but after a chance meeting with Cristal Connors, the star of Goddess, the current show at the hotel where Molly works, Nomi manages to secure an audition for a spot on the chorus line.However she soon realises that fame comes with a price as her friendships, her morals and her soul are put to the test as she works her way up the ladder and eventually becomes the star of the show, stealing Cristal's part. She begins to wonder if all of her work was for nothing and if she can reclaim her life back before it is too late.</define></term><term><lable>Sky Palace</lable><define></define></term><term><lable>Gamer</lable><define>Set in a future-world where humans can control other humans in mass-scale, multi-player online gaming environments, a star player from a game called "Slayers" looks to regain his independence while taking down the game's mastermind.</define></term><term><lable>Spawn</lable><define>An assassin named Al Simmons is double-crossed and murdered by his evil boss Jason Wynn. Al makes a deal with the devil and returns to earth as Spawn to see his wife. He is ordered by the devil's minion, The Clown, to kill Wynn. Wynn has made a deal with the clown too and is suppose to destroy the world with a deadly virus that will help start Armageddon and allow Hell to attack Heaven. Spawn must choose between Good &amp; Evil.</define></term><term><lable>Speechless</lable><define></define></term><term><lable>Surviving the Game</lable><define>Mason, who lives on the streets, wants to cease his life when on the same day his two best friends die: His dog and an older man with whom he shared his food and roof. Just in time Cole, from a charity organization, can prevent his suicide and also offers him a quite well paid job as servant for a hunting party in the Rocky Mountains. Mason accepts the job and flies with them to a hut in the wilderness where they prepare everything for the four rich businessmen who want to hunt something special. Mason does not yet know that he is the victim of their sports that should lead to the basic insticts of man, but they did not count with his cleverness...</define></term><term><lable>Teenage Exorcist</lable><define>Diane, a repressed, neurotic grad student, moves into a cursed mansion and is possessed by the house's demonic master.Transformed into a raven-haired, leather and lingerie-clad seductress, Diane seeks a virgin sacrifice for her master while her sister, brother-in-law, a priest, and a pizza boy try to rescue her and avoid his wrath.</define></term><term><lable>Teresa's Tattoo</lable><define>Mathematician Teresa just wanted to study during the College spring break. But her friends, who want her to live a little, drag her out to parties. The next thing she knows, she has been drugged, kidnapped, made a redhead, tattooed, and wearing leather?!? Her captors seem to be the most inept crooks ever. They seem to have a plan, if only she could figure out why it involves her.</define></term><term><lable>The Amazing Panda Adventure</lable><define>Children's action-adventure about a young boy who, while on a visit to China to see his father, tries to save a baby panda from poachers.</define></term><term><lable>The Brady Bunch Movie</lable><define>Mike Brady and his wife Carol Brady have just only one week to come up with $20,000 in back taxes or their house is sold and they'll have no choice but to move. And it's up to the Brady kids to secretly raise money and save the homestead before they lose their house to their scheming neighbor Mr. Larry Dittmeyer.</define></term><term><lable>The Brothers McMullen</lable><define>This angst-filled tale of three Irish-Catholic brothers explores men's relationships with women. Three different situations are set up on parallel plotlines, with each brother facing a different kind of crisis. Their common bond as family, as well as close lifelong friends, allows them to express their feelings frankly and intimately, as they talk and discuss their concerns among each other. Jack finds himself in a marriage gone stale and under pressure to start a family that he does not yet feel ready for. Barry, dedicated to his film career and almost pathologically averse to any type of commitment in a relationship, is suddenly artistically successful and finds true love, both for the first time and both pulling him in opposite directions. Patrick is torn between his love for his religion and ethnic heritage and his love for Susan, his longtime Jewish girlfriend. Ultimately, they are all asked to resist temptation of one sort or another, with various poignant outcomes.</define></term><term><lable>The Champagne Safari</lable><define></define></term><term><lable>The City of Lost Children</lable><define>Krank (</define></term><term><lable>The Client</lable><define>A street-wise kid, Mark Sway, sees the suicide of Jerome Clifford, a prominent Louisiana lawyer, whose current client is Barry 'The Blade' Muldano, a Mafia hit-man. Before Jerome shoots himself, he tells Mark where the body of Senator Boyd Boyette is buried. Mark escapes, and Clifford shoots himself. Mark is found at the scene, and both the FBI and the Mafia quickly realize that Mark probably knows more than he says. Mark decides he needs a lawyer, and goes looking for one. He finds Reggie Love, who also becomes convinced that Mark knows more than he says, but Mark isn't talking...</define></term><term><lable>The Cloud Door</lable><define>A very clever parrot lives in a hindu palace, surrounded by many beautiful girls, but the parrot escapes, and is trapped far from the palace. One day, when it's new owner is sleeping, the bird convinces a young boy to open the cage door. In return, it shows the boy a secret passage to get into the palace.</define></term><term><lable>The Crude Oasis</lable><define>Lonely Kansas housewife Karen Webb despondent about her love life, her husband Jim Webb coldness and philandering, has a strong urge to change her future. Karen discovers the truth about Jim and sets out to commit suicide by carbon monoxide poisoning in her garage, but her three dollar daily allowance for gasoline runs out before she expires. During one of her gas station refills, she spots a different type who catches her fancy in Harley Underwood and sets her sights on him.</define></term><term><lable>The Day of the Beast</lable><define>A basque priest finds by means of a cabalistic study of the bible that the anti-christ is going to be born on Christmas day in Madrid. Helped by a heavy-metal fan and by the showman of a TV esoteric program, he will try to invoke the devil to find out the place of birth and kill the baby.</define></term><term><lable>The Evil Inside Me</lable><define></define></term><term><lable>The Naked Gun 21/2: The Smell of Fear</lable><define>Lt. Frank Drebbin returns to save the day once again. This time he's out to foil the "big boys" in the energy business. A top scientist (Dr Mainheimer) is about to publish his report on energy supply for the future. Things don't look good for the traditional suppliers; oil, coal and nuclear. To save their industries, the suppliers kidnap Mainheimer and replace him with a decoy with a more favourable report. Jane, the Dr's secretary, is Drebbin's old flame; they're passionate love affair is thus rekindled.</define></term><term><lable>The Glimmer Man</lable><define>Jack Cole is a soft spoken, mystical, new age New York cop with a checkered past. He is transferred to Los Angeles to help Los Angeles cop Jim Campbell solve a series of brutal murders in which the victims are crucified. The murders that have happened since Jack arrived in Los Angeles just don't sit right with him. When the killer, known as the "Family Man", kills Ellen DunLeavy, who happens to be Jack's ex wife and the mother of his two kids, and Ellen's husband Andrew DunLeavy, it becomes personal - especially when Jack's prints are found on Ellen's body. Jack meets with his military mentor Smith, not knowing that Smith is in cahoots with local crime boss Frank Deverell.</define></term><term><lable>The Grotesque</lable><define>Sir Hugo is more interested in reconstructing dinosaur bones than in paying attention to his wife, Lady Harriet. He's not thrilled when daughter Cleo brings home her betrothed, Sidney, who aspires to be a poet. The new butler, Fledge, provides Lady Harriet with the attention she's been missing and then seduces Sidney. Did he have a role in Sidney's disappearance as well?</define></term><term><lable>The Lion King</lable><define>A young lion prince is born in Africa, thus making his uncle Scar the second in line to the throne. Scar plots with the hyenas to kill King Mufasa and Prince Simba, thus making himself King. The King is killed and Simba is led to believe by Scar that it was his fault, and so flees the kingdom in shame. After years of exile he is persuaded to return home to overthrow the usurper and claim the kingdom as his own thus completing the "Circle of Life".</define></term><term><lable>The Mask</lable><define>Stanley Ipkiss is a bank clerk that is an incredibly nice man. Unfortunately, he is too nice for his own good and is a pushover when it comes to confrontations. After one of the worst days of his life, he finds a mask that depicts Loki, the Norse night god of mischief. Now, when he puts it on, he becomes his inner, self: a cartoony romantic wild man. However, a small time crime boss, Dorian Tyrel, comes across this character dubbed "The Mask" by the media. After Ipkiss's alter ego indirectly kills his friend in crime, Tyrel now wants this green-faced goon destroyed.</define></term><term><lable>Rushmore</lable><define>Max Fischer is a precocious 15-year-old whose reason for living is his attendance at Rushmore, a private school where he's not doing well in any of his classes, but where he's the king of extracurricular activities - from being in the beekeeping society to writing and producing plays, there's very little after school he doesn't do. His life begins to change, however, when he finds out he's on academic probation, and when he stumbles into love with Miss Cross, a pretty teacher of the elementary school at Rushmore. Added to the mix is his friendship with Herman Blume, wealthy industrialist and father to boys who attend the school, and who also finds himself attracted to Miss Cross. Max's fate becomes inextricably tied to this odd love triangle, and how he sets about resolving it is the story in the film.</define></term><term><lable>The Nature of the Beast</lable><define>Jack meets Adrian out in Nevada. Adrian latches on to Jack, and won't go away. Jack tries to lose Adrian, but Adrian informs Jack not to mess with him, or he'll call the police because he knows Jack's secret. In the meantime, the car radio keeps blaring news reports of a serial killer in the area called "The Hatchet Man", as well as a theft of a huge sum of money from a local casino. Jack is concealing a briefcase, and wherever he and Adrian go, "The Hatchet Man" seems to strike within the vicinity!</define></term><term><lable>The Quick and the Dead</lable><define>Ellen, an unknown female gunslinger rides into a small, dingy and depressing prairie town with a secret as to her reason for showing up. Shortly after her arrival, a local preacher, Cort, is thrown through the saloon doors while townfolk are signing up for a gun competition. The pot is a huge sum of money and the only rule: that you follow the rules of the man that set up the contest, Herod. Herod is also the owner, leader, and "ruler" of the town. Seems he's arranged this little gun-show-off so that the preacher (who use to be an outlaw and rode with Herod) will have to fight again. Cort refuses to ever use a gun to kill again and Herod, acknowledging Cort as one of the best, is determined to alter this line of thinking ... even if it gets someone killed ...</define></term><term><lable>The Secret of Roan Inish</lable><define>10-year-old Fiona is sent to live with her grandparents in a small fishing village in Donegal, Ireland. She soon learns the local legend that an ancestor of hers married a Selkie - a seal who can turn into a human. Years earlier, her baby brother washed out to sea in a cradle shaped like a boat; someone in the family believes the boy is being raised by the seals. Then Fiona catches sight of a naked little boy on the abandoned Isle of Roan Inish and takes an active role in uncovering The Secret of Roan Inish. Written by John Oswalt.</define></term><term><lable>The Shawshank Redemption</lable><define>Andy Dufresne is a young and successful banker whose life changes drastically when he is convicted and sentenced to life imprisonment for the murder of his wife and her lover. Set in the 1940's, the film shows how Andy, with the help of his friend Red, the prison entrepreneur, turns out to be a most unconventional prisoner.</define></term><term><lable>The Soldier Boy</lable><define>A comedy centered around Irene, a mother driven by the need to conform to her traditional Greek culture. Her obsession becomes acute as she begins to communicate with the gods, her daughter Gina battles for independence and son Dimitri struggles with his own identity. Finally, an infestation of roaches convinces Irene that to rid her of her own problems, she must sacrifice her daughter to appease the gods.</define></term><term><lable>The Stream</lable><define>A young mother has been forced to flee her home carrying her husband's aged mother on her back. The old woman cannot walk. In addition, there are three small children to care for. There is no food in the middle of winter in the Bosnian mountains. Somehow she must get through the isolated mountain pass to a safe village. She cannot carry the old woman and the two smallest children as well. The young woman is faced with a terrible choice - either she sacrifices the old woman, or her children will die. We see that the old woman realizes this herself, and indicates to the daughter-in-law that she accepts her fate. The young woman then drowns the old woman in a mountain stream. The last image of the film is hopeful. We see the young woman, now carrying the children, arriving at a village. She knocks on the door of a house.</define></term></glossary>
