<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE glossary>
<glossary></movie><movie><title>Congo</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>4.6</rating><plot>A megalomaniac C.E.O. sends his son into the dangerous African Congo on a quest for a source of diamonds large enough and pure enough to function as powerful laser communications transmitters (or is it laser weapons?). When contact is lost with his son and the team, his sometime daughter- in-law is sent after them. She is a former CIA operative and, accompanied by gee-whiz gadgetry and a few eccentric characters (including a mercenary, a researcher with a talking gorilla, and a a nutty Indiana-Jones-type looking for King Solomon's Mines), sets out to rescue her former fianc?. What they all discover is that often what we most want turns out to be the source of our downfall.</plot></movie><movie><title>Man with a Plan</title><category>movie</category><year>1996</year><rating>7.8</rating><plot>Fred Tuttle, faced with his father's impending hip operation and his failing farm, needs to make a six-digit salary with a fourth-grade education. So he runs for U.S. Representative from Vermont with a markedly bizarre campaign. Will he triumph over incumbent Bill Blachly?</plot></movie><movie><title>Makusu no yama</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>5.9</rating><plot>A string of brutal murders are being committed around Tokyo. As a rebellious police officer tries to piece together the clues, the only connection he can find is the victim's membership in the same college club back in the 60's. Fighting against the bureaucratic ineptitude of his colleagues, he must figure out who could be connected to the victims, and what the killer's motivation could possibly be.</plot></movie><movie><title>The Soldier Boy</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating></rating><plot>A comedy centered around Irene, a mother driven by the need to conform to her traditional Greek culture. Her obsession becomes acute as she begins to communicate with the gods, her daughter Gina battles for independence and son Dimitri struggles with his own identity. Finally, an infestation of roaches convinces Irene that to rid her of her own problems, she must sacrifice her daughter to appease the gods.</plot></movie><movie><title>The Voyeur</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>3.5</rating><plot>The passion is gone from Brenda and James's ten-year marriage; he's into his corporate law career and she's a successful businesswoman, but she'd like the magic back. She takes the advice of her European aunt Lydia, and she books a weekend getaway at a Napa County resort. It takes her awhile, but she finally gets James to stop thinking about business. She asks him if he's had any fantasies, and he admits to thinking about watching her with a lover, so on the second night of their stay, she arranges for him to hide behind a mirror in the room while she goes in search of the inn's recreation director. Will it bring fire to their marriage, and what about her fantasy?</plot></movie><movie><title>Blood and Wine</title><category>movie</category><year>1996</year><rating>6.1</rating><plot>Bob Rafelson has stated that this is the final part of an informal trilogy he started with "Five Easy Pieces" and continued with "The King Of Marvin Gardens". In the three, Nicholson has now played son, brother and father. In this one, Nicholson is a wealthy wine dealer who has distanced himself from his wife with his philandering and from his son with his negligence. After he steals a diamond necklace with the help of a safecracker partner, Victor, things start coming apart. His wife sets out to interrupt what she thinks is another one of his weekend dalliances, but is really his trip to pawn the jewels.</plot></movie><movie><title>Bomgay</title><category>movie</category><year>1996</year><rating>6.5</rating><plot>Based on the gay poetry of R. Raj Rao, "BOMGaY" is a collection of six vignettes that depict the underground and twisted nature of the gay identity in urban India. Part Genet, part Bollywood this film combines acidic verse and insightful imagery to reveal the emerging gay community in post-liberalized India of the 1990's.</plot></movie><movie><title>The Glimmer Man</title><category>movie</category><year>1996</year><rating>5.0</rating><plot>Jack Cole is a soft spoken, mystical, new age New York cop with a checkered past. He is transferred to Los Angeles to help Los Angeles cop Jim Campbell solve a series of brutal murders in which the victims are crucified. The murders that have happened since Jack arrived in Los Angeles just don't sit right with him. When the killer, known as the "Family Man", kills Ellen DunLeavy, who happens to be Jack's ex wife and the mother of his two kids, and Ellen's husband Andrew DunLeavy, it becomes personal - especially when Jack's prints are found on Ellen's body. Jack meets with his military mentor Smith, not knowing that Smith is in cahoots with local crime boss Frank Deverell.</plot></movie><movie><title>Gray's Anatomy</title><category>movie</category><year>1996</year><rating>6.9</rating><plot>Spalding Gray has an eye condition that can be surgically corrected. He decides to seek alternate treatment and embarks on a journey that will take him to Christian Science, Native American sweat lodges and psychic surgeons, among others.</plot></movie><movie><title>Denise Calls Up</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>6.7</rating><plot>A group of friends in New York, working away at their PCs and laptops, keep in touch exclusively by phone and fax. They are all too busy to meet face to face. Gale plays matchmaker, by phone, to Jerry and Barbara who, in turn, hit it off beautifully...via phone and fax. Martin gets a telephone call from someone he's never met. It's Denise, with some extraordinary news. Tapping away at his computer all the while, he develops a sort of friendship with Denise...via phone. And so it goes as the friends, tap, tap, tapping away, share news, hopes, and dreams...via phone and fax. Finally Gale has an unfortunate encounter with a phone, Denise has some more news for Martin, and Frank plans a gala New Year's Eve party, but will he answer the door?</plot></movie><movie><title>The Day of the Beast</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>7.5</rating><plot>A basque priest finds by means of a cabalistic study of the bible that the anti-christ is going to be born on Christmas day in Madrid. Helped by a heavy-metal fan and by the showman of a TV esoteric program, he will try to invoke the devil to find out the place of birth and kill the baby.</plot></movie><movie><title>Captured Alive</title><title>Apollo 13</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>7.5</rating><plot>Based on the true story of the ill-fated 13th Apollo mission bound for the moon. Astronauts Lovell, Haise and Swigert were scheduled to fly Apollo 14, but are moved up to 13. It's 1970, and America have already achieved their lunar landing goal, so there's little interest in this "routine" flight.. until that is, things go very wrong, and prospects of a safe return fade.</plot></movie><movie><title>Eat Drink Man Woman</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating>7.7</rating><plot>Senior Master Chef Chu lives in a large house in Taipei with his three unmarried daughters, Jia-Jen, a chemistry teacher converted to Christianity, Jia-Chien, an airline executive, and Jia-Ning, a student who also works in a fast food restaurant. Life in the house revolves around the ritual of an elaborate dinner each Sunday, and the love lives of all the family members.</plot></movie><movie><title>Antonia</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>7.4</rating><plot>In an anonymous Dutch village, a sturdy, strong-willed matriarch looks back upon her life, the generations of family and friends gathered around her table, and ponders the cyclical nature of time.</plot></movie><movie><title>Words Upon the Window Pane</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating>5.8</rating><plot>This film is based on the one act play by W B Yeats and concerns another great figure from Irish literature, Jonathan Swift, whose spirit, with those of his two livers, Stella and Vanessa, emergrs in a series of seances held in Dublin in 1928. Their passion, Swift's torment and ultimately Stella's revenge are enacted. Thrown together by the crisis, those attending the seance are forced to confront the truths of their own lives ....</plot></movie><movie><title>Boy Crazy, Girl Crazier</title><category>movie</category><year>1996</year><rating>6.3</rating><plot>Celena and Charlie live together in L.A., and both of them want to make it in the movies. At a Hollywood party, Charlie manages to grab himself a part in a film, and he does it by stealing material from Celena. Then he discards her, like a used tissue. Not only does she get mad, she gets even.</plot></movie><movie><title>Croce e delizia</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>5.3</rating><plot>A Parigi una troupe italiana sta girando in economia un film sulla Traviata. A Rosa, la sarta del primo attore Alberto Sanna, piace molto il personaggio di Violetta, tanto da piangere ogni volta che ? in scena. Alcuni colleghi allora, guidati da Animamorta, decidono di farle uno scherzo e con l'aiuto di Harriette inscenano una finta seduta spiritica in cui rosa viene identificata da uno spirito come la reincarnazione di Violetta. Il film intanto, tra una serie di incidenti e l'altra, va lentamente avanti, mentre Rosa racconta a tratti la sua vita a Barbara, compagna di camera. Ogni tanto poi vede una donna misteriosa vestita in abiti ottocenteschi che poi scompare. Alberto intanto si trova un'amica, Juliette, della quale Rosa ? gelosa. E arriva il finale, dell'opera e del film.</plot></movie><movie><title>Cyber Vengeance</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>4.0</rating><plot>The year is 2005. The prison system is run by the private sector. Business tycoon R.D. Crowley, has created a virtual reality prison. The prisoner's bodies are locked in suspended animation while their minds traverse the lethal labyrinth of games Crowley designed for them. Crowley allows wealthy sportsmen to participate, for a price, in deadly VR combat with the prisoners. Will breaks into the prison and attempts to eradicate the VR technology. Seduced by his VR girlfriend he becomes addicted to VR. Will is caught and thrown into the lethal time-traveling web of Crowley's virtual hunt. With their lives at stake, Will and the prisoners must escape certain death, and destroy the VR prison.</plot></movie><movie><title>Gordy</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>3.6</rating><plot>This is the story of a talking cute piglet named Gordy, who gets involved in a big quest to save his family from the slaughterhouse, where no pigs have ever returned. And it's all up to Gordy to find and save his family before they turned into sausage!</plot></movie><movie><title>Jin yu man tang</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>6.9</rating><plot>Kit is a gangster looking to start a new life as a chef in Canada, so he can be closer to his girlfriend. But in his struggle to learn the fine art of cuisine, he runs across a red-headed beauty who will change his plans, and soon finds himself off in search of the retired master who can teach him how to win in the ultimate cooking challenge.</plot></movie><movie><title>Blue in the Face</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>6.5</rating><plot>Wayne Wang's follow-up movie to Smoke presents a series of improvisational situations strung together to form a pastiche of Brooklyn's diverse ethnicity, offbeat humor, and essential humanity. Many of the same characters inhabiting Auggie Wren's Brooklyn Cigar Store in Smoke return here to expound on their philosophy of smoking, relationships, baseball, New York, and Belgian Waffles. Most of all, this is a movie about living life, off-the-cuff.</plot></movie><movie><title>The Cloud Door</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating>6.0</rating><plot>A very clever parrot lives in a hindu palace, surrounded by many beautiful girls, but the parrot escapes, and is trapped far from the palace. One day, when it's new owner is sleeping, the bird convinces a young boy to open the cage door. In return, it shows the boy a secret passage to get into the palace.</plot></movie><movie><title>Barsaat</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>5.8</rating><plot>Badal (Bobby Deol) is a naive but intelligent young man who comes from a small village to the big city. He is introduced to city life by Damru (Harish Patel) who now calls himself Danny. When Badal attends college, he meets with pretty and percocious, Tina Oberoi (Twinkle Khanna), and after a few misunderstanding and misadventures, both fall in love. This is not taken well by Tina's dad, (Raj Babbar), who hopes to marry Tina with his friend's (Bharat Kapoor) son. Tina's dad complains to the college principal (Vijay Kashyap), but Tina testifies in favour of Badal. Tina's dad then asks a corrupt cop, Neghi, who is the city's Assistant Commissioner of Police, for assistance. Neghi arrests Badal on trumped up charges and imprisons him. Badal's dad (Mukesh Khanna) also comes to the big city to try and make sense of why Badal ended up in prison. Tina's dad gives a contract to Neghi to have Badal killed, to which Neghi agrees and hires a gang of ruthless outlaws to hunt and kill Badal. He also pressurizes Tina not to acknowledge and meet Badal anymore, and Tina reluctantly agrees. Will Badal survive? Will Tina and Badal's love be fated to end tragically?</plot></movie><movie><title>Barlach-Kantate - Es geht ein kraftiges Atmen</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating></rating><plot>A musical film based on Michael Baumgartl's cantata for solo tenor, chorus and instruments after texts by Ernst Barlach. The cantata is the foundation of a two-part film work that fits into no single genre. The first part documents the rehearsals of the cantata at the Luebeck musik academy. The second part leads with the music into a world of images that circles around Barlach's works and thoughts and relates them to the town of Guestrow and the Mecklenburg countryside where Barlach spent most of his life.</plot></movie><movie><title>Caged Heat 3000</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>3.8</rating><plot>It's the year 3000 AD. The world's most dangerous women are banished to a remote asteroid 45 million light years from earth. Kira Murphy doesn't belong; wrongfully accused of a crime she did not commit, she's thrown in this interplanetary prison and left to her own defenses. But Kira's a fighter, and soon she finds herself in the middle of a female gang war; where everyone wants a piece of the action... and a piece of her! "Caged Heat 3000" takes the Women-in-Prison genre to a whole new level... and a whole new galaxy!</plot></movie><movie><title>Boomerang</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>5.7</rating><plot>Two university researchers claim the existence of serious police brutality in Bergen, Norway, in the early 1980s. The film follows the public reactions to these allegations, the victimization of the researchers and the legal persecution of their informants.</plot></movie><movie><title>Eight O'Clock, at Your Place</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>3.1</rating><plot>Javiera and Antonio are a young couple with two daughters and another on the way. But beneath the superficial tranquillity of their marriage hides a passionate relationship between Antonio and his wife's sister, Antonieta. The love triangle begins to lose its delicate balance when Antonieta loses her purse. A mysterious voice on the telephone extorts the lovers, moving them to take unusual actions and to confront one another with blame and doubt, ultimately forcing them to explore the true value of their relationship.</plot><movie><title>Aurora: Operation Intercept</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>3.3</rating><plot>There have been two mysterious plane crashes in only 48 hours. The aircraft suddenly lose control and crash, killing everyone aboard. A woman of Russian descent, Francesca Zaborszin, the daughter of a slain Federal investigator, claims responsibility for the crashes. She believes her father was killed by the FBI as part of a cover-up operation and wishes to avenge his death by threatening to down more aircraft using the same electromagnetic pulse method. She also intends to crash a stolen military jet into the White House. There's no time to ground the planes: just enough time to try to stop her.</plot></movie><movie><title>Baja</title><category>movie</category><year>1996</year><rating>5.4</rating><plot>Alex and Bebe are camped out in Baja California, Mexico, after their disastrous first attempt at a drug deal. Impatiently awaiting forged passports, they are unaware that Bebe's father has convinced her estranged husband Michael to find her. Michael soon arrives in Baja California, where it appears he isn't the only foreigner trying to find Alex and Bebe.</plot></movie><movie><title>Wariko, le gros lot</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating></rating><plot>In the Ivory Coast, Ali (Toure) is a poor policeman who struggles to make ends meet for his wife, Awa (Kabore) and three children. Ali is excited and giddy When he learns that the lottery ticket that Awa bought him is a 3,000,000 winner. But after an extended, frantic search he cannot find the ticket anywhere and he starts to neglect his work. As his family and neighbors learn of his good fortune, they start to come to him with their hands out, and Ali is seen as a mark by others who learn of his winnings. When Ali at last finds the ticket, he realizes that he cannot meet everyone's wishes, even with ten Jackpots.</plot></movie><movie><title>Pigalle</title><category>movie</category><year>1992</year><rating>5.6</rating><plot>In the seedy neon-lit underworld of the Pigalle district of Paris, animalistic survival obscures all moral codes. Rival drug dealers use three minor figures as pawns in their murderous manoeuvres. Divine is a transexual, a performer in a club, the lover of Fifi, a man who's a street hustler and petty thief. Fifi, in turn, loves Divine but flirts with V?ra, a striptease dancer and peep show attraction. When Divine is bullied into giving information to one drug dealer, the opposition uses V?ra as bait to enlist Fifi as a hitman.</plot></movie><movie><title>Le bonheur est dans le pre</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>7.0</rating><plot>Francis, the boss of a small plumbing supply company, is harassed by tax collectors, striking employees, and an impossible wife and daughter. His only joy is sharing lunch with his friend Gerard. Then a TV show called "where are you?" shows a woman from Gers who is searching for her husband who disappeared 28 years ago. The lost husband looks like an identical twin of Francis...</plot></movie><movie><title>Dr. Jekyll and Ms. Hyde</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>4.2</rating><plot>In New York in 1995 Dr. Richard Jacks is a creator of perfumes. Thus he spends his days inventing new colorful and well smelling potions and certainly caring for his girlfriend Sarah Carver. But when he discovers that his greatgrandfather, called Dr. Jekyll, was a scientist with revoluntionary discoveries, he tries to follow the footsteps of his ancestor and creates more and more delicate potions until one of them converts him into a spectacular superwoman: Helen Hyde. Knowing that Richard has no clue of her existence Helen enforces a professional career at the back of her "creator".</plot></movie><movie><title>Feast of July</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>6.3</rating><plot>This romantic story, based on a novel by H.E. Bates and set in late 19th century England, rests on sibling rivalry for the affections of a woman who comes to live with their family by happenstance. In time, she decides to accept the marriage proposal of the youngest of the three sons, to the surprise of all. However, a man whom she had once loved and who had abandoned her (after making false promises) comes back into her life. The appearance of this scoundrel sets into motion a tragic series of events that eventually engulfs everyone.</plot></movie><movie><title>The Brady Bunch Movie</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>5.7</rating><plot>Mike Brady and his wife Carol Brady have just only one week to come up with $20,000 in back taxes or their house is sold and they'll have no choice but to move. And it's up to the Brady kids to secretly raise money and save the homestead before they lose their house to their scheming neighbor Mr. Larry Dittmeyer.</plot></movie><movie><title>Broadcast Bombshells</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>2.8</rating><plot>At WSEX, a local television broadcasting station in New Jersey, Kendall Saranski is the beautiful blond anchorwoman and the object of desire for all men working at the station including the libidos sportscaster Brian Kilgore and the station owner Mr. Buel. But Kendall is only interested in a kind-hearted stage hand named Neil whom is an old friend from her school days. Meanwhile, the conniving and ambitious brunette associate producer Amanda Cross, jealous of Kendall's rising fame, plots to further her career by having her tech boyfriend Gordon plot to bring Kendall and Brian's downfall using her seductive charms to go after Brian and have Gordon videotape it for future leverage against Brian. Other subplots include a mad bomber in the neighborhood blowing up various public places, a legendary grue sponsor named Frank Friendly holding onto his secret "three little words" as his motto, and a climatic fund-raiser telethon which brings all parties together for a final confrontation.</plot></movie><movie><title>Sex &amp; the Other Man</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>4.6</rating><plot>Look What the Wife Dragged Home Tonight! Arthur Wilkins is an unusual prisoner of love in this strangely romantic comedy. When Bill finds his girlfriend in bed with her boss, Bill's excitement goes further than just to his head. What follows is a strange cure for impotence as Bill and Jessica finally get it on while Arthur, their hostage, looks on.</plot></movie><movie><title>Jeffrey</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>6.2</rating><plot>Jeffery, a young gay man in New York, decides that sex is too much and decided to become celibate. He immediately meets the man of his dreams and must decide whether or not love is worth the danger of a boyfriend dying.</plot></movie><movie><title>Sebastian - When Everybody Knows</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>4.9</rating><plot>16 year old Sebastian behaves strangely. He stays alone in his room for hours thinking and doesn't talk to his parents as he used to. He refuses to explain to them what his problem is. The truth is that he slowly discovers that he feels stangely for his best friend Ulf. Soon he is going to accept his true self - that he is gay and that he is also in love with his best friend Ulf.</plot></movie><movie><title>Congo</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>4.6</rating><plot>A megalomaniac C.E.O. sends his son into the dangerous African Congo on a quest for a source of diamonds large enough and pure enough to function as powerful laser communications transmitters (or is it laser weapons?). When contact is lost with his son and the team, his sometime daughter- in-law is sent after them. She is a former CIA operative and, accompanied by gee-whiz gadgetry and a few eccentric characters (including a mercenary, a researcher with a talking gorilla, and a a nutty Indiana-Jones-type looking for King Solomon's Mines), sets out to rescue her former fianc?. What they all discover is that often what we most want turns out to be the source of our downfall.</plot></movie><movie><title>Man with a Plan</title><category>movie</category><year>1996</year><rating>7.8</rating><plot>Fred Tuttle, faced with his father's impending hip operation and his failing farm, needs to make a six-digit salary with a fourth-grade education. So he runs for U.S. Representative from Vermont with a markedly bizarre campaign. Will he triumph over incumbent Bill Blachly?</plot></movie><movie><title>Makusu no yama</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>5.9</rating><plot>A string of brutal murders are being committed around Tokyo. As a rebellious police officer tries to piece together the clues, the only connection he can find is the victim's membership in the same college club back in the 60's. Fighting against the bureaucratic ineptitude of his colleagues, he must figure out who could be connected to the victims, and what the killer's motivation could possibly be.</plot></movie><movie><title>The Soldier Boy</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating></rating><plot>A comedy centered around Irene, a mother driven by the need to conform to her traditional Greek culture. Her obsession becomes acute as she begins to communicate with the gods, her daughter Gina battles for independence and son Dimitri struggles with his own identity. Finally, an infestation of roaches convinces Irene that to rid her of her own problems, she must sacrifice her daughter to appease the gods.</plot></movie><movie><title>The Voyeur</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>3.5</rating><plot>The passion is gone from Brenda and James's ten-year marriage; he's into his corporate law career and she's a successful businesswoman, but she'd like the magic back. She takes the advice of her European aunt Lydia, and she books a weekend getaway at a Napa County resort. It takes her awhile, but she finally gets James to stop thinking about business. She asks him if he's had any fantasies, and he admits to thinking about watching her with a lover, so on the second night of their stay, she arranges for him to hide behind a mirror in the room while she goes in search of the inn's recreation director. Will it bring fire to their marriage, and what about her fantasy?</plot></movie><movie><title>Blood and Wine</title><category>movie</category><year>1996</year><rating>6.1</rating><plot>Bob Rafelson has stated that this is the final part of an informal trilogy he started with "Five Easy Pieces" and continued with "The King Of Marvin Gardens". In the three, Nicholson has now played son, brother and father. In this one, Nicholson is a wealthy wine dealer who has distanced himself from his wife with his philandering and from his son with his negligence. After he steals a diamond necklace with the help of a safecracker partner, Victor, things start coming apart. His wife sets out to interrupt what she thinks is another one of his weekend dalliances, but is really his trip to pawn the jewels.</plot></movie><movie><title>Bomgay</title><category>movie</category><year>1996</year><rating>6.5</rating><plot>Based on the gay poetry of R. Raj Rao, "BOMGaY" is a collection of six vignettes that depict the underground and twisted nature of the gay identity in urban India. Part Genet, part Bollywood this film combines acidic verse and insightful imagery to reveal the emerging gay community in post-liberalized India of the 1990's.</plot></movie><movie><title>The Glimmer Man</title><category>movie</category><year>1996</year><rating>5.0</rating><plot>Jack Cole is a soft spoken, mystical, new age New York cop with a checkered past. He is transferred to Los Angeles to help Los Angeles cop Jim Campbell solve a series of brutal murders in which the victims are crucified. The murders that have happened since Jack arrived in Los Angeles just don't sit right with him. When the killer, known as the "Family Man", kills Ellen DunLeavy, who happens to be Jack's ex wife and the mother of his two kids, and Ellen's husband Andrew DunLeavy, it becomes personal - especially when Jack's prints are found on Ellen's body. Jack meets with his military mentor Smith, not knowing that Smith is in cahoots with local crime boss Frank Deverell.</plot></movie><movie><title>Gray's Anatomy</title><category>movie</category><year>1996</year><rating>6.9</rating><plot>Spalding Gray has an eye condition that can be surgically corrected. He decides to seek alternate treatment and embarks on a journey that will take him to Christian Science, Native American sweat lodges and psychic surgeons, among others.</plot></movie><movie><title>Denise Calls Up</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>6.7</rating><plot>A group of friends in New York, working away at their PCs and laptops, keep in touch exclusively by phone and fax. They are all too busy to meet face to face. Gale plays matchmaker, by phone, to Jerry and Barbara who, in turn, hit it off beautifully...via phone and fax. Martin gets a telephone call from someone he's never met. It's Denise, with some extraordinary news. Tapping away at his computer all the while, he develops a sort of friendship with Denise...via phone. And so it goes as the friends, tap, tap, tapping away, share news, hopes, and dreams...via phone and fax. Finally Gale has an unfortunate encounter with a phone, Denise has some more news for Martin, and Frank plans a gala New Year's Eve party, but will he answer the door?</plot></movie><movie><title>The Day of the Beast</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>7.5</rating><plot>A basque priest finds by means of a cabalistic study of the bible that the anti-christ is going to be born on Christmas day in Madrid. Helped by a heavy-metal fan and by the showman of a TV esoteric program, he will try to invoke the devil to find out the place of birth and kill the baby.</plot></movie><movie><title>Captured Alive</title><title>Apollo 13</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>7.5</rating><plot>Based on the true story of the ill-fated 13th Apollo mission bound for the moon. Astronauts Lovell, Haise and Swigert were scheduled to fly Apollo 14, but are moved up to 13. It's 1970, and America have already achieved their lunar landing goal, so there's little interest in this "routine" flight.. until that is, things go very wrong, and prospects of a safe return fade.</plot></movie><movie><title>Eat Drink Man Woman</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating>7.7</rating><plot>Senior Master Chef Chu lives in a large house in Taipei with his three unmarried daughters, Jia-Jen, a chemistry teacher converted to Christianity, Jia-Chien, an airline executive, and Jia-Ning, a student who also works in a fast food restaurant. Life in the house revolves around the ritual of an elaborate dinner each Sunday, and the love lives of all the family members.</plot></movie><movie><title>Antonia</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>7.4</rating><plot>In an anonymous Dutch village, a sturdy, strong-willed matriarch looks back upon her life, the generations of family and friends gathered around her table, and ponders the cyclical nature of time.</plot></movie><movie><title>Words Upon the Window Pane</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating>5.8</rating><plot>This film is based on the one act play by W B Yeats and concerns another great figure from Irish literature, Jonathan Swift, whose spirit, with those of his two livers, Stella and Vanessa, emergrs in a series of seances held in Dublin in 1928. Their passion, Swift's torment and ultimately Stella's revenge are enacted. Thrown together by the crisis, those attending the seance are forced to confront the truths of their own lives ....</plot></movie><movie><title>Boy Crazy, Girl Crazier</title><category>movie</category><year>1996</year><rating>6.3</rating><plot>Celena and Charlie live together in L.A., and both of them want to make it in the movies. At a Hollywood party, Charlie manages to grab himself a part in a film, and he does it by stealing material from Celena. Then he discards her, like a used tissue. Not only does she get mad, she gets even.</plot></movie><movie><title>Croce e delizia</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>5.3</rating><plot>A Parigi una troupe italiana sta girando in economia un film sulla Traviata. A Rosa, la sarta del primo attore Alberto Sanna, piace molto il personaggio di Violetta, tanto da piangere ogni volta che ? in scena. Alcuni colleghi allora, guidati da Animamorta, decidono di farle uno scherzo e con l'aiuto di Harriette inscenano una finta seduta spiritica in cui rosa viene identificata da uno spirito come la reincarnazione di Violetta. Il film intanto, tra una serie di incidenti e l'altra, va lentamente avanti, mentre Rosa racconta a tratti la sua vita a Barbara, compagna di camera. Ogni tanto poi vede una donna misteriosa vestita in abiti ottocenteschi che poi scompare. Alberto intanto si trova un'amica, Juliette, della quale Rosa ? gelosa. E arriva il finale, dell'opera e del film.</plot></movie><movie><title>Cyber Vengeance</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>4.0</rating><plot>The year is 2005. The prison system is run by the private sector. Business tycoon R.D. Crowley, has created a virtual reality prison. The prisoner's bodies are locked in suspended animation while their minds traverse the lethal labyrinth of games Crowley designed for them. Crowley allows wealthy sportsmen to participate, for a price, in deadly VR combat with the prisoners. Will breaks into the prison and attempts to eradicate the VR technology. Seduced by his VR girlfriend he becomes addicted to VR. Will is caught and thrown into the lethal time-traveling web of Crowley's virtual hunt. With their lives at stake, Will and the prisoners must escape certain death, and destroy the VR prison.</plot></movie><movie><title>Gordy</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>3.6</rating><plot>This is the story of a talking cute piglet named Gordy, who gets involved in a big quest to save his family from the slaughterhouse, where no pigs have ever returned. And it's all up to Gordy to find and save his family before they turned into sausage!</plot></movie><movie><title>Jin yu man tang</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>6.9</rating><plot>Kit is a gangster looking to start a new life as a chef in Canada, so he can be closer to his girlfriend. But in his struggle to learn the fine art of cuisine, he runs across a red-headed beauty who will change his plans, and soon finds himself off in search of the retired master who can teach him how to win in the ultimate cooking challenge.</plot></movie><movie><title>Blue in the Face</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>6.5</rating><plot>Wayne Wang's follow-up movie to Smoke presents a series of improvisational situations strung together to form a pastiche of Brooklyn's diverse ethnicity, offbeat humor, and essential humanity. Many of the same characters inhabiting Auggie Wren's Brooklyn Cigar Store in Smoke return here to expound on their philosophy of smoking, relationships, baseball, New York, and Belgian Waffles. Most of all, this is a movie about living life, off-the-cuff.</plot></movie><movie><title>The Cloud Door</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating>6.0</rating><plot>A very clever parrot lives in a hindu palace, surrounded by many beautiful girls, but the parrot escapes, and is trapped far from the palace. One day, when it's new owner is sleeping, the bird convinces a young boy to open the cage door. In return, it shows the boy a secret passage to get into the palace.</plot></movie><movie><title>Barsaat</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>5.8</rating><plot>Badal (Bobby Deol) is a naive but intelligent young man who comes from a small village to the big city. He is introduced to city life by Damru (Harish Patel) who now calls himself Danny. When Badal attends college, he meets with pretty and percocious, Tina Oberoi (Twinkle Khanna), and after a few misunderstanding and misadventures, both fall in love. This is not taken well by Tina's dad, (Raj Babbar), who hopes to marry Tina with his friend's (Bharat Kapoor) son. Tina's dad complains to the college principal (Vijay Kashyap), but Tina testifies in favour of Badal. Tina's dad then asks a corrupt cop, Neghi, who is the city's Assistant Commissioner of Police, for assistance. Neghi arrests Badal on trumped up charges and imprisons him. Badal's dad (Mukesh Khanna) also comes to the big city to try and make sense of why Badal ended up in prison. Tina's dad gives a contract to Neghi to have Badal killed, to which Neghi agrees and hires a gang of ruthless outlaws to hunt and kill Badal. He also pressurizes Tina not to acknowledge and meet Badal anymore, and Tina reluctantly agrees. Will Badal survive? Will Tina and Badal's love be fated to end tragically?</plot></movie><movie><title>Barlach-Kantate - Es geht ein kraftiges Atmen</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating></rating><plot>A musical film based on Michael Baumgartl's cantata for solo tenor, chorus and instruments after texts by Ernst Barlach. The cantata is the foundation of a two-part film work that fits into no single genre. The first part documents the rehearsals of the cantata at the Luebeck musik academy. The second part leads with the music into a world of images that circles around Barlach's works and thoughts and relates them to the town of Guestrow and the Mecklenburg countryside where Barlach spent most of his life.</plot></movie><movie><title>Caged Heat 3000</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>3.8</rating><plot>It's the year 3000 AD. The world's most dangerous women are banished to a remote asteroid 45 million light years from earth. Kira Murphy doesn't belong; wrongfully accused of a crime she did not commit, she's thrown in this interplanetary prison and left to her own defenses. But Kira's a fighter, and soon she finds herself in the middle of a female gang war; where everyone wants a piece of the action... and a piece of her! "Caged Heat 3000" takes the Women-in-Prison genre to a whole new level... and a whole new galaxy!</plot></movie><movie><title>Boomerang</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>5.7</rating><plot>Two university researchers claim the existence of serious police brutality in Bergen, Norway, in the early 1980s. The film follows the public reactions to these allegations, the victimization of the researchers and the legal persecution of their informants.</plot></movie><movie><title>Eight O'Clock, at Your Place</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>3.1</rating><plot>Javiera and Antonio are a young couple with two daughters and another on the way. But beneath the superficial tranquillity of their marriage hides a passionate relationship between Antonio and his wife's sister, Antonieta. The love triangle begins to lose its delicate balance when Antonieta loses her purse. A mysterious voice on the telephone extorts the lovers, moving them to take unusual actions and to confront one another with blame and doubt, ultimately forcing them to explore the true value of their relationship.</plot></movie><movie><title>Aurora: Operation Intercept</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>3.3</rating><plot>There have been two mysterious plane crashes in only 48 hours. The aircraft suddenly lose control and crash, killing everyone aboard. A woman of Russian descent, Francesca Zaborszin, the daughter of a slain Federal investigator, claims responsibility for the crashes. She believes her father was killed by the FBI as part of a cover-up operation and wishes to avenge his death by threatening to down more aircraft using the same electromagnetic pulse method. She also intends to crash a stolen military jet into the White House. There's no time to ground the planes: just enough time to try to stop her.</plot></movie><movie><title>Baja</title><category>movie</category><year>1996</year><rating>5.4</rating><plot>Alex and Bebe are camped out in Baja California, Mexico, after their disastrous first attempt at a drug deal. Impatiently awaiting forged passports, they are unaware that Bebe's father has convinced her estranged husband Michael to find her. Michael soon arrives in Baja California, where it appears he isn't the only foreigner trying to find Alex and Bebe.</plot></movie><movie><title>Wariko, le gros lot</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating></rating><plot>In the Ivory Coast, Ali (Toure) is a poor policeman who struggles to make ends meet for his wife, Awa (Kabore) and three children. Ali is excited and giddy When he learns that the lottery ticket that Awa bought him is a 3,000,000 winner. But after an extended, frantic search he cannot find the ticket anywhere and he starts to neglect his work. As his family and neighbors learn of his good fortune, they start to come to him with their hands out, and Ali is seen as a mark by others who learn of his winnings. When Ali at last finds the ticket, he realizes that he cannot meet everyone's wishes, even with ten Jackpots.</plot></movie><movie><title>Pigalle</title><category>movie</category><year>1992</year><rating>5.6</rating><plot>In the seedy neon-lit underworld of the Pigalle district of Paris, animalistic survival obscures all moral codes. Rival drug dealers use three minor figures as pawns in their murderous manoeuvres. Divine is a transexual, a performer in a club, the lover of Fifi, a man who's a street hustler and petty thief. Fifi, in turn, loves Divine but flirts with V?ra, a striptease dancer and peep show attraction. When Divine is bullied into giving information to one drug dealer, the opposition uses V?ra as bait to enlist Fifi as a hitman.</plot></movie><movie><title>Le bonheur est dans le pre</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>7.0</rating><plot>Francis, the boss of a small plumbing supply company, is harassed by tax collectors, striking employees, and an impossible wife and daughter. His only joy is sharing lunch with his friend Gerard. Then a TV show called "where are you?" shows a woman from Gers who is searching for her husband who disappeared 28 years ago. The lost husband looks like an identical twin of Francis...</plot></movie><movie><title>Dr. Jekyll and Ms. Hyde</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>4.2</rating><plot>In New York in 1995 Dr. Richard Jacks is a creator of perfumes. Thus he spends his days inventing new colorful and well smelling potions and certainly caring for his girlfriend Sarah Carver. But when he discovers that his greatgrandfather, called Dr. Jekyll, was a scientist with revoluntionary discoveries, he tries to follow the footsteps of his ancestor and creates more and more delicate potions until one of them converts him into a spectacular superwoman: Helen Hyde. Knowing that Richard has no clue of her existence Helen enforces a professional career at the back of her "creator".</plot></movie><movie><title>Feast of July</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>6.3</rating><plot>This romantic story, based on a novel by H.E. Bates and set in late 19th century England, rests on sibling rivalry for the affections of a woman who comes to live with their family by happenstance. In time, she decides to accept the marriage proposal of the youngest of the three sons, to the surprise of all. However, a man whom she had once loved and who had abandoned her (after making false promises) comes back into her life. The appearance of this scoundrel sets into motion a tragic series of events that eventually engulfs everyone.</plot></movie><movie><title>The Brady Bunch Movie</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>5.7</rating><plot>Mike Brady and his wife Carol Brady have just only one week to come up with $20,000 in back taxes or their house is sold and they'll have no choice but to move. And it's up to the Brady kids to secretly raise money and save the homestead before they lose their house to their scheming neighbor Mr. Larry Dittmeyer.</plot></movie><movie><title>Broadcast Bombshells</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>2.8</rating><plot>At WSEX, a local television broadcasting station in New Jersey, Kendall Saranski is the beautiful blond anchorwoman and the object of desire for all men working at the station including the libidos sportscaster Brian Kilgore and the station owner Mr. Buel. But Kendall is only interested in a kind-hearted stage hand named Neil whom is an old friend from her school days. Meanwhile, the conniving and ambitious brunette associate producer Amanda Cross, jealous of Kendall's rising fame, plots to further her career by having her tech boyfriend Gordon plot to bring Kendall and Brian's downfall using her seductive charms to go after Brian and have Gordon videotape it for future leverage against Brian. Other subplots include a mad bomber in the neighborhood blowing up various public places, a legendary grue sponsor named Frank Friendly holding onto his secret "three little words" as his motto, and a climatic fund-raiser telethon which brings all parties together for a final confrontation.</plot></movie><movie><title>Sex &amp; the Other Man</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>4.6</rating><plot>Look What the Wife Dragged Home Tonight! Arthur Wilkins is an unusual prisoner of love in this strangely romantic comedy. When Bill finds his girlfriend in bed with her boss, Bill's excitement goes further than just to his head. What follows is a strange cure for impotence as Bill and Jessica finally get it on while Arthur, their hostage, looks on.</plot></movie><movie><title>Angel Baby</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>7.0</rating><plot>Two schizophrenics meet during therapy and fall passionately in love. Ahead of them lies the inevitable road to disaster...one they share to the end.</plot></movie><movie><title>Jeffrey</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>6.2</rating><plot>Jeffery, a young gay man in New York, decides that sex is too much and decided to become celibate. He immediately meets the man of his dreams and must decide whether or not love is worth the danger of a boyfriend dying.</plot></movie><movie><title>Sebastian - When Everybody Knows</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>4.9</rating><plot>16 year old Sebastian behaves strangely. He stays alone in his room for hours thinking and doesn't talk to his parents as he used to. He refuses to explain to them what his problem is. The truth is that he slowly discovers that he feels stangely for his best friend Ulf. Soon he is going to accept his true self - that he is gay and that he is also in love with his best friend Ulf.</plot></movie></glossary>
