<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE glossary>
<glossary><movie><title>Dukhovnye golosa. Iz dnevnikov voyny. Povestvovanie v pyati chastyakh</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>8.0</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Congo</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>4.6</rating><plot>A megalomaniac C.E.O. sends his son into the dangerous African Congo on a quest for a source of diamonds large enough and pure enough to function as powerful laser communications transmitters (or is it laser weapons?). When contact is lost with his son and the team, his sometime daughter- in-law is sent after them. She is a former CIA operative and, accompanied by gee-whiz gadgetry and a few eccentric characters (including a mercenary, a researcher with a talking gorilla, and a a nutty Indiana-Jones-type looking for King Solomon's Mines), sets out to rescue her former fiancé. What they all discover is that often what we most want turns out to be the source of our downfall.</plot></movie><movie><title>Shut Up and Listen!</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>5.1</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Love Street 5</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Man with a Plan</title><category>movie</category><year>1996</year><rating>7.8</rating><plot>Fred Tuttle, faced with his father's impending hip operation and his failing farm, needs to make a six-digit salary with a fourth-grade education. So he runs for U.S. Representative from Vermont with a markedly bizarre campaign. Will he triumph over incumbent Bill Blachly?</plot></movie><movie><title>Makusu no yama</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>5.9</rating><plot>A string of brutal murders are being committed around Tokyo. As a rebellious police officer tries to piece together the clues, the only connection he can find is the victim's membership in the same college club back in the 60's. Fighting against the bureaucratic ineptitude of his colleagues, he must figure out who could be connected to the victims, and what the killer's motivation could possibly be.</plot></movie><movie><title>Indiscretions</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>2.7</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>The Soldier Boy</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating></rating><plot>A comedy centered around Irene, a mother driven by the need to conform to her traditional Greek culture. Her obsession becomes acute as she begins to communicate with the gods, her daughter Gina battles for independence and son Dimitri struggles with his own identity. Finally, an infestation of roaches convinces Irene that to rid her of her own problems, she must sacrifice her daughter to appease the gods.</plot></movie><movie><title>The Voyeur</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>3.5</rating><plot>The passion is gone from Brenda and James's ten-year marriage; he's into his corporate law career and she's a successful businesswoman, but she'd like the magic back. She takes the advice of her European aunt Lydia, and she books a weekend getaway at a Napa County resort. It takes her awhile, but she finally gets James to stop thinking about business. She asks him if he's had any fantasies, and he admits to thinking about watching her with a lover, so on the second night of their stay, she arranges for him to hide behind a mirror in the room while she goes in search of the inn's recreation director. Will it bring fire to their marriage, and what about her fantasy?</plot></movie><movie><title>Statistically Speaking</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Reckless</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>4.7</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Streetlife</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>6.0</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Blood and Wine</title><category>movie</category><year>1996</year><rating>6.1</rating><plot>Bob Rafelson has stated that this is the final part of an informal trilogy he started with "Five Easy Pieces" and continued with "The King Of Marvin Gardens". In the three, Nicholson has now played son, brother and father. In this one, Nicholson is a wealthy wine dealer who has distanced himself from his wife with his philandering and from his son with his negligence. After he steals a diamond necklace with the help of a safecracker partner, Victor, things start coming apart. His wife sets out to interrupt what she thinks is another one of his weekend dalliances, but is really his trip to pawn the jewels.</plot></movie><movie><title>Alone</title><category>movie</category><year>1996</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Bomgay</title><category>movie</category><year>1996</year><rating>6.5</rating><plot>Based on the gay poetry of R. Raj Rao, "BOMGaY" is a collection of six vignettes that depict the underground and twisted nature of the gay identity in urban India. Part Genet, part Bollywood this film combines acidic verse and insightful imagery to reveal the emerging gay community in post-liberalized India of the 1990's.</plot></movie><movie><title>De e' ju dej jag vill ha!</title><category>movie</category><year>1996</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>The Glimmer Man</title><category>movie</category><year>1996</year><rating>5.0</rating><plot>Jack Cole is a soft spoken, mystical, new age New York cop with a checkered past. He is transferred to Los Angeles to help Los Angeles cop Jim Campbell solve a series of brutal murders in which the victims are crucified. The murders that have happened since Jack arrived in Los Angeles just don't sit right with him. When the killer, known as the "Family Man", kills Ellen DunLeavy, who happens to be Jack's ex wife and the mother of his two kids, and Ellen's husband Andrew DunLeavy, it becomes personal - especially when Jack's prints are found on Ellen's body. Jack meets with his military mentor Smith, not knowing that Smith is in cahoots with local crime boss Frank Deverell.</plot></movie><movie><title>Cosmic Voyage</title><category>movie</category><year>1996</year><rating>7.6</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Gray's Anatomy</title><category>movie</category><year>1996</year><rating>6.9</rating><plot>Spalding Gray has an eye condition that can be surgically corrected. He decides to seek alternate treatment and embarks on a journey that will take him to Christian Science, Native American sweat lodges and psychic surgeons, among others.</plot></movie><movie><title>Do Outro Lado do Tejo</title><category>movie</category><year>1996</year><rating>1.0</rating><plot></plot></movie>