<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE glossary>
<glossary><movie><title>Electra</title><category>movie</category><year>1996</year><rating>3.2</rating><plot>Billionaire named Roach desperately seeks for the secret serum which could turn an ordinary human into a superbeing. The serum is hidden in the body of young Billy Duncan. The serum can be transmitted via sexual intercourse, and that turns to be the basis of Roach's evil scheme.</plot></movie><movie><title>Carogne</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>6.6</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>4 maneras de tapar un hoyo</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>7.7</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Butterfly Kiss</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>6.4</rating><plot>Eunice is walking along the highways of northern England from one filling station to another. She is searching for Judith, the woman, she says to be in love with. It's bad luck for the women at the cash desk not to be Judith, because Eunice is eccentric, angry and extreme dangerous. One day she meets Miriam, hard of hearing and a little ingenuous, who feels sympathy for Eunice and takes her home. Miriam is very impressed by Eunice's fierceness and willfulness and follows her on the search for Judith. Shocked by Eunice's cruelty she tries to make her a better person, but she looses ground herself.</plot></movie><movie><title>Ao Sul</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Best of the Best 3: No Turning Back</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>4.4</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Betaaj Badshah</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating>6.3</rating><plot>Well known for his believes in fairness, justice, and fair play, Raja Prithviraj holds sway over a large rural territory in India. His word is the law, and no one would dare to cross swords with him. Prithviraj lives with his only daughter, Tejeshwani, in their exclusive palace. Years later, Tejeshwani has now grown up, attends college, on occasion with her pet cheetah, meets with handsome young fellow collegian, and after several misunderstandings and confrontations, both fall in love with each other. When Prithviraj comes to know of Arjun, he invites him to his palace, insults him, and asks him never to see Tejeshwani again. Watch what Arjun and Tejeshwani do to change her father's mind, knowing fully well that no one in their community will stand up against the Raja.</plot></movie><movie><title>Er nai cun zhi sha fu</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>God and Gun</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>4.3</rating><plot>God and Gun is a film on contemporary events A daringly different film. It bringsforth authentically the inside realities of today's politics. God and Gun advocates the truth that power lies in the hands of people and not politicians. The voice of the people is the voice of god.</plot></movie><movie><title>Irving</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>3.1</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Mortal Kombat</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>5.5</rating><plot>Based on the popular video game of the same name "Mortal Kombat" tells the story of an ancient tournament where the best of the best of different Realms fight each other. The goal - ten wins to be able to legally invade the losing Realm. Outworld has so far collected nine wins against Earthrealm, so it's up to Lord Rayden and his fighters to stop Outworld from reaching the final victory...</plot></movie><movie><title>Es lebe unsere DDR</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Cello</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Die Ameisenstrasse</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>7.0</rating><plot>In the middle of Vienna stands an old tenement building, and time has left its mark both on the house and its inhabitants. Here, time passes at a strange pace. Floor by floor, the visitor can discover small self-contained worlds: grousers, collectors, the forgotten, people with obsessions, concealed and exposed passions. Behind securely locked doors, each prepares his own heady brew. Then, however, death makes its entrance for the first time, sweeping through the stairwell. The owner of the house, a resident himself, dies. His nephew, an entrepreneur, inherits the building and acts immediately. He moves out, takes up lodgings, hands out notice to quit, renovates and devastates. One goal hovers before his eyes; to get rid of the tenants and make money out of the property. Gradually, the closed doors begin to open, and with each outrage committed by the new owner, the residents are drawn closer together. What comes to light thereby is an anthill full of life, and once it opens up, a flood of comical individuals streams out of it, all fighting for their own living space. A minor official, plagued by persecution mania, fears a dreadful end to the matter. Though the signs he sees of this are all wrong, nevertheless, in a furious finale, the outside world descends upon the house and his inhabitants.</plot></movie><movie><title>Alltagsrot in Europa</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Cuore cattivo</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>7.6</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Bu yi tang de ma ma</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>7.8</rating><plot>Referred to as Hong Kong's answer to "Misery", innocent-looking Bo-Bo Fung is an overprotective mother/nurse who is bent on revenge at all costs after the death of her son at the hands of policeman Lau Ching-Wan. Veronica Yip stars as a gambling addict who enlists Lau to protect her from loan sharks, and eventually returns the favor in order for him to survive Nurse Lam's relentless assault.</plot></movie><movie><title>Alpsee</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>6.6</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>De zwijgende reiziger</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating>6.1</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>William Christie et Les Arts Florissants, ou La passion du baroque</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie>