<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE glossary>
<glossary><movie><title>Am I in Another World?</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Dai lao bai shou</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>5.9</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>The Brothers McMullen</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>6.5</rating><plot>This angst-filled tale of three Irish-Catholic brothers explores men's relationships with women. Three different situations are set up on parallel plotlines, with each brother facing a different kind of crisis. Their common bond as family, as well as close lifelong friends, allows them to express their feelings frankly and intimately, as they talk and discuss their concerns among each other. Jack finds himself in a marriage gone stale and under pressure to start a family that he does not yet feel ready for. Barry, dedicated to his film career and almost pathologically averse to any type of commitment in a relationship, is suddenly artistically successful and finds true love, both for the first time and both pulling him in opposite directions. Patrick is torn between his love for his religion and ethnic heritage and his love for Susan, his longtime Jewish girlfriend. Ultimately, they are all asked to resist temptation of one sort or another, with various poignant outcomes.</plot></movie><movie><title>Host i paradiset - Gladjekallan 2</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>5.8</rating><plot>Ragnar Persson, a 68-year-old widower, is living at his summer cottage with his son, Mikael, and his son's pregnant girlfriend, Catti. Ragnar falls in love with his neighbour, Vendela, who runs an apple orchard. Mikael is carrying on an affair with Susanne, a childhood friend who is married to Henning, the owner of the local apple juice plant. A great rift in the family opens up when Mikael, who is always broke, accuses Vendela of just trying to get his father's money.</plot></movie><movie><title>Akhareen abadeh</title><category>movie</category><year>1993</year><rating>8.2</rating><plot>A teacher from the Ministry of Education is on his way to bring study books for the children in a remote mountain village, North of Iran. But he is stopped in the snow by a pack of hungry wolves. A boy in the village, busy reading the book "The last village", tries to convince the people of the village to rescue the teacher.</plot></movie><movie><title>Murder in the First</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>7.1</rating><plot>Henri Young stole five dollars from a post office and ended up going to prison - to the most famous, or infamous, prison of them all: Alcatraz. He tried to escape, failed, and spent three years and two months in solitary confinement - in a dungeon, with no light, no heat and no toilet. Milton Glenn, the assistant warden, who was given free reign by his duty-shirking superior, was responsible for Young's treatment. Glenn even took a straight razor and hobbled Young for life. After three years and two months, Young was taken out of solitary confinement and put with the rest of the prisoners. Almost immediately, Young took a spoon and stabbed a fellow prisoner in the neck, killing him. Now, Young is on trial for murder, and if he's convicted he'll go to the gas chamber. An eager and idealistic young attorney, James Stamphill, is given this impossible case, and argues before a shocked courtroom that Young had a co-conspirator. The true murderer, he says, was Alcatraz.</plot></movie><movie><title>Middle of the Moment</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>8.1</rating><plot>The film is a documentary or even a cinepoem which follows the life of nowadays nomads: The Tuareg in North Africa, a circus company and the American philosopher and poet 'Robert Lax'.</plot></movie><movie><title>NoHo</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>7.7</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Red Steel</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>2.3</rating><plot></plot></movie>