<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE glossary>
<glossary><movie><title>Blondes Have More Guns</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>3.7</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Bikini Drive-In</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>2.6</rating><plot>Kim Taylor inherits her grandfather's drive-in theatre. She must raise $25,000 over one weekend or the bank will take the property from her. She also has to deal with pesky capitalist J.B. Winston. This is a fun, not politically correct movie.</plot></movie><movie><title>Voll normaaal</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating>4.4</rating><plot>Tommie works as mechanic in a garage and loves crazy exhausts. But when he steals the exhaust of the procurer Jupp a lot of trouble starts: Jupp gives Tommie an ultimatum to replace the exhaust and to buy a box of "Ramsdorfer Koelsch".</plot></movie><movie><title>Switchcraft</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating>6.5</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Yuan fen xin tian kong</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>White Badge</title><category>movie</category><year>1992</year><rating>7.2</rating><plot>South Korea, 1979. Han Kiju is an alcoholic novelist who has never recovered from his year long tour as a volunteer soldier in Vietnam. When he's asked to write a book about the Korean soldiers who fought in Vietnam he's battered by flashbacks that remind him of the brutality and lies that destroyed his innocence. The serialized novel brings him back in contact with a former soldier who served under him, PFC Pyon Chinsu, the one-time company clown driven mad by the violence of the war and who now looks to Han for some sort of emotional rescue.</plot></movie><movie><title>The Amazing Panda Adventure</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>5.3</rating><plot>Children's action-adventure about a young boy who, while on a visit to China to see his father, tries to save a baby panda from poachers.</plot></movie><movie><title>Amores que matan</title><category>movie</category><year>1996</year><rating>7.2</rating><plot>Consuelo is a bored housewife. Her husband is away on business in Berlin, and her only company would be a mysterious neighbor, a science professor who spends a lot of time gardening (?) One fine morning, Consuelo is compelled to find an excuse to speak with her neighbor. She asks him for some sugar, and then starts discussing gardening. During the rest of the film we find out what may be below the well-manicured flowers, and what secrets involving everyone, these may conceal.</plot></movie><movie><title>Betongraser</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating></rating><plot>The everyday humdrum of two adolescents who live on the outskirts of a big city. People from various countries meet for various reasons. Spies, collaborators, emigrants, players, and others. Their fates interweave, their attempt to look into the future is cut short by the war.</plot></movie><movie><title>Yankee Zulu</title><category>movie</category><year>1993</year><rating>5.8</rating><plot>Two South African boys, one white, one black, go their separate ways. Years later, they meet up again as adults, when one, after living for years in the United States, is now a wanted criminal. The two end up being a part of a madcap chase involving a check for a large amount of money.</plot></movie><movie><title>The Passenger</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating>6.0</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Timecop</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating>5.6</rating><plot>When the ability to travel through time is perfected, a new time of law enforcement agency is formed. It's called Time Enforcement Commission or TEC. A cop Max Walker is assigned to the group. On the day he was chosen, some men attack him and kill his wife. Ten years later Max is still grieving but has become a good agent for the TEC. He tracks down a former co-worker who went into the past to make money. Max brings him back for sentencing but not after telling Max that Senator McComb the man in charge of TEC sent him. Max has his eye on McComb.</plot></movie><movie><title>Toorog</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Thursday Afternoon</title><category>movie</category><year>1998</year><rating>5.5</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Sky Palace</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating>5.8</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Il toro</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating>6.6</rating><plot>Italia, 1994. Franco e Loris are two friends that decide to steal a stud bull. The bull is worth a lot. Their idea is to immediately leave Italy and try to sell the bull in Hungary. But east Europe is not exactly what they were expecting. The troubles, the miseries and the reality of the countries they are crossing change step by step their minds. The new way of thinking will drive them to a new kind of friendships.</plot></movie><movie><title>Wo he chun tian you ge yue hui</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating>7.0</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Welcome II the Terrordome</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>3.3</rating><plot>Spike and his sister Anjela live in the Terrordome, a huge ghetto that all the blacks have been forced to live in. Jodie, Spike's pregnant white girlfriend, ran away from an abusive white boyfriend who, after seeing her with Spike, sets up a trap for her. Spike's 11-year old nephew Hector dies as a result of this trap, and Anjela, finding the body of her son, goes on a police-killing rampage. Her apprehension sets off tension between Spike and his brother-in-law, as a race war broods inside the Terrordome.</plot></movie><movie><title>Dead Man Walking</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>7.7</rating><plot>A convicted murderer on Death Row and the nun who befriends him. Through the portrayal of finely drawn characters and their interactions as the days, hours, and minutes tick down to the condemned man's execution, powerful emotions are unleashed. While Matthew Poncelet and Sister Prejean desperately try to gain a stay of execution from the governor or the courts, scenes are intercut from the brutal crime, gradually revealing the truth about the events that transpired. In addition to her temporal help, the nun also tries to reach out spiritually and assist as a guide to salvation.</plot></movie><movie><title>Dypets ensomhet</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>7.1</rating><plot></plot></movie></glossary>
