<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE glossary>
<glossary><movie><title>Criminal Hearts</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>4.4</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Closet Case</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Final Equinox</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>4.0</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Hubungan jenayah</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating></rating><plot>Ray is a Rambo-like Manila cop who travels to Hong Kong on assignment. He searches for his girl friend Lina, and finds her - addicted to drugs. Heung Lan, his ex-partner, is an undercover Hong Kong cop investigating weapons smuggling. She provokes the smugglers by intercepting several shipments in Hong Kong, leading to several good, although brief fights. The drug smuggler kills Lina, and Ray swears vengeance. The head of the gang then returns to the Philippines, and with him, the action shifts back to the Philippines. The lady cop gets more than what she hoped for.</plot></movie><movie><title>Love Handles</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating>6.2</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Jack &amp; Sarah</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>6.3</rating><plot>Jack always lands on his feet. He lands on his feet when he marries the beautiful Sarah. He lands on his feet when he buys a luxurious new home. However, when Sarah goes into labour, he takes a tumble down the stairs and lands on his head. When he comes around he discovers he is the proud father of a baby girl, but deficient in the spouse department to the tune of 1. The hires the help of a novice nanny, but at the end of the day, it's Jack who's left holding the baby.</plot></movie><movie><title>How to Make an American Quilt</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>5.9</rating><plot>Finn is a young graduate student, finishing a master's thesis, and preparing for marriage to her fiance Sam. But thoughts of the end of the free life, and a potential summer fling, intrude. She goes home to her grandmother, where, over the making of her wedding gift by a group of quilting-bee friends, laughter, bickering, love, and advice lead her toward a more open-eyed examination of her course.</plot></movie><movie><title>Grid Runners</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>3.4</rating><plot>Scientist brings virtual reality characters to life. Two are women from the cybersex game site. The third is a warrior who wants to unleash the rest of the bad guys from the virtual reality underworld. A border cop must defeat the virtual reality warrior while learning to relate to one of the cybersex babes.</plot></movie><movie><title>Lunarcop</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>3.2</rating><plot>A cop from the moon is sent to the Earth, now possessed by motorcycle-riding "Mad Max"-like inhabitants, to stop a serum from being released that he believes is going to destroy the Earth...</plot></movie><movie><title>Pribytiye poyezda</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>7.0</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Ma ma fan fan</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>5.8</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Pulkownik Kwiatkowski</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>6.9</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Richard III</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>7.6</rating><plot>William Shakespeare's classic play is brought into the present with the setting as Great Britian in the 1930s. Civil war has erupted with the House of Lancaster on one side, claiming the right to the British throne and hoping to bring freedom to the country. Opposing is the House of York, commanded by the infamous Richard who rules over a fascist government and hopes to install himself as a dictator monarch.</plot></movie><movie><title>Mallrats</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>7.1</rating><plot>Brodie Bruce, a Sega and comic book obsessed college student, and his best friend, TS Quint, are both dumped by their girlfriends on the same day, and to deal with their loss, they both go to the local mall. Along the way, they meet up with some friends, including Willam, a guy who stares at Magic Eye pictures, desprately trying to see the hidden image; Gwen, one of TS's ex-girlfriends; and Jay &amp; Silent Bob, of Clerks fame. Eventually, they decide to try and win back their significant others, and take care of their respective nemesises (TS's girlfriend's father, and a store clerk who hates the two for not having any shopping agenda).</plot></movie><movie><title>A More Perfect Union</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>5.8</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Ruz-e vagh'e</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>7.0</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Shakuhachi</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Ragazzi della notte</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>3.7</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Showgirls</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>4.1</rating><plot>Nomi Malone, a mysterious young girl with the ambition to dance embarks on a journey to Las Vegas to become a showgirl in a high-class hotel show. There she meets Molly, a seamstress at the Stardust Hotel and the two quickly become good friends. She gets a job as a lap dancer at the seedy Cheetah Club but after a chance meeting with Cristal Connors, the star of Goddess, the current show at the hotel where Molly works, Nomi manages to secure an audition for a spot on the chorus line.However she soon realises that fame comes with a price as her friendships, her morals and her soul are put to the test as she works her way up the ladder and eventually becomes the star of the show, stealing Cristal's part. She begins to wonder if all of her work was for nothing and if she can reclaim her life back before it is too late.</plot></movie><movie><title>Uta Makura</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie>