<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE glossary>
<glossary><movie><title>Le bonheur est dans le pre</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>7.0</rating><plot>Francis, the boss of a small plumbing supply company, is harassed by tax collectors, striking employees, and an impossible wife and daughter. His only joy is sharing lunch with his friend Gerard. Then a TV show called "where are you?" shows a woman from Gers who is searching for her husband who disappeared 28 years ago. The lost husband looks like an identical twin of Francis...</plot></movie><movie><title>Dr. Jekyll and Ms. Hyde</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>4.2</rating><plot>In New York in 1995 Dr. Richard Jacks is a creator of perfumes. Thus he spends his days inventing new colorful and well smelling potions and certainly caring for his girlfriend Sarah Carver. But when he discovers that his greatgrandfather, called Dr. Jekyll, was a scientist with revoluntionary discoveries, he tries to follow the footsteps of his ancestor and creates more and more delicate potions until one of them converts him into a spectacular superwoman: Helen Hyde. Knowing that Richard has no clue of her existence Helen enforces a professional career at the back of her "creator".</plot></movie><movie><title>Book</title><category>movie</category><year>1993</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Feast of July</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>6.3</rating><plot>This romantic story, based on a novel by H.E. Bates and set in late 19th century England, rests on sibling rivalry for the affections of a woman who comes to live with their family by happenstance. In time, she decides to accept the marriage proposal of the youngest of the three sons, to the surprise of all. However, a man whom she had once loved and who had abandoned her (after making false promises) comes back into her life. The appearance of this scoundrel sets into motion a tragic series of events that eventually engulfs everyone.</plot></movie>