<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE glossary>
<glossary><movie><title>Bo li qiang de ai</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>6.3</rating><plot>Simon Yam and Cecilia Yip reteam again in this film. Yam plays a benevolent gangster that is set up by his right hand man and is sent to prison for over ten years. Once released, his wife left him, his daughter doesn't love him any more and he's broke. He falls for Cecilia Yip who plays a business woman that owes the triad a lot of money. Yam goes up to the Boss and says that he'll be responsible for her debt. During there wedding photos Yip tries to commit suicide but Yam saves her and they still wind up posing for the photographs making for some very bloody photos. The man who set up Simon Yam decides to wipe him off of the face of the earth. So Yam decides to go toe to toe with the jerk! Will Simon And Cecilia live happily ever after?</plot></movie><movie><title>Bu dao de de li wu</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>5.5</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Gone to the Dogs</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>The Grotesque</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>5.5</rating><plot>Sir Hugo is more interested in reconstructing dinosaur bones than in paying attention to his wife, Lady Harriet. He's not thrilled when daughter Cleo brings home her betrothed, Sidney, who aspires to be a poet. The new butler, Fledge, provides Lady Harriet with the attention she's been missing and then seduces Sidney. Did he have a role in Sidney's disappearance as well?</plot></movie><movie><title>Ein kleiner Film uber Zeiten des Friedens und der Freiheit</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>No hoi wai lung</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>5.9</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Sinawastingasse 17/Home-Made-Video</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Throwing Down</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>6.1</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Journey on the Plain</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>6.5</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Knodel Clip</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Le nouveau monde</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>6.0</rating><plot>Born in 1943 during German occupation of their French town, Patrick and Marie-José have been best friends; now teens, they experiment with sex, which doesn't seem to bring them closer. Patrick has also taken to American jazz, hanging out at a nearby Army base where he picks up the drums and comes to the attention of a Caberra, a brutish American sergeant who enjoys starting fights with Black soldiers. Caberra gives Patrick a drum kit, talks to him about life, and introduces him around. Patrick meets Trudy, an American teen who loves Buddy Holly. Marie-José is jealous and establishes her own liaison. What of Patrick and Marie-José's pact to be friends forever?</plot></movie><movie><title>Miguel</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Mommy</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>5.2</rating><plot>An unofficial "sequel" to "The Bad Seed", Patty McCormack's "Mommy" is psychotically obsessed with her 12-year-old daughter Jessica Ann -- so much so that when she finds out Jessica didn't get the "Student of the Year" award again, she solves the problem by murdering the teacher who didn't recommend her for it. She dismisses the killing as inconsequential ("a minor accident"), but the homicide detective assigned to the case suspects her immediately, and an insurance investigator who also suspects her tries to get close to Jessica Ann to find out what really happened.</plot></movie><movie><title>Noe beroligende</title><category>movie</category