<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE glossary>
<glossary><movie><title>Breaking Free</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>6.3</rating><plot>When troubled, cynical teen Rick chooses service at a camp for the blind over serving time at a correctional facility, he thinks he's found the easy way out. Instead, it's the way to a new life. Friendship. Step by step, as Rick helps a blinded Gymnast rediscover the joys of competition through equestrian show jumping, they begin to take control of the most important journey of all... a journey called life.</plot></movie><movie><title>The Fear</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>3.1</rating><plot>A weekend group goes to a remote cabin for "fear therapy". While each person is working to conquer their worst fears, they all become terrorized by a living monster made of wood which stalks each of them in turn.</plot></movie><movie><title>Bulan tertusuk ilalang</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>6.2</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>The Final Days</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>England, My England</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>7.4</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Beach Babes 2: Cave Girl Island</title><category>movie</category><year>1998</year><rating>3.7</rating><plot>Xena, Luna, and Sola leave Malibu but return to earth unexpectedly when Xena sneezes and crash lands them on a desert isle. After being threatened by dinosaurs and having a few close encounters with some primitive stud muffins, they tangle with the evil James T. Renford II, who has some sinister profit-making plans for the babes from space.</plot></movie><movie><title>Dadetown</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>6.6</rating><plot>Interviews in the Michael Moore/"Roger and Me" tradition examine life in small-town America, class conflicts and the collapse of an upstate New York community, Dadetown, when the town's once-prosperous factory, reduced to the manufacture of paper clips and staples, finally closes. Facing massive unemployment, the blue-collar Dadetown residents next find yuppies moving into town to staff the local division of a big computer outfit.</plot></movie><movie><title>Go aat sin</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>5.3</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Das Hasen-Signal-Alphabet</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Macumba</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>6.1</rating><plot>Sometimes the camera films of its own volition. Macumba shows an optical tangle in 13 scenes. As a start signal one hears a double hammer blow arising from a black screen, a sound like the nailing shut of a coffin. Macumba develops slowly out of the black. A black porno couple on the telephone in London. Then they meet on a snake in a park and are, together with Kalahari Bushmen mixed to a film matrix which is as incomprehensible as real life. Throughout Macumba the sound of rain can be heard. (Dietmar Brehm)</plot></movie><movie><title>Lagodna</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>6.0</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Peculiarities of the National Hunt</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>7.6</rating><plot>A Finn preparing a work on the Russian hunting traditions and customs, comes to Russia to collect materials and is invited to take part in a hunting party. His flamboyant companions include an Army general, with more than a passing resemblance to Aleksander Lebed, a police detective, local forest ranger (a devotee of Zen Buddhism) and some big-city types from St. Petersburg. Inevitably, their good intentions soon give way to endless drinking, visits to local farm girls and much else besides.</plot></movie><movie><title>The Quick and the Dead</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>6.3</rating><plot>Ellen, an unknown female gunslinger rides into a small, dingy and depressing prairie town with a secret as to her reason for showing up. Shortly after her arrival, a local preacher, Cort, is thrown through the saloon doors while townfolk are signing up for a gun competition. The pot is a huge sum of money and the only rule: that you follow the rules of the man that set up the contest, Herod. Herod is also the owner, leader, and "ruler" of the town. Seems he's arranged this little gun-show-off so that the preacher (who use to be an outlaw and rode with Herod) will have to fight again. Cort refuses to ever use a gun to kill again and Herod, acknowledging Cort as one of the best, is determined to alter this line of thinking ... even if it gets someone killed ...</plot></movie><movie><title>Sound of the Land</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Die Sturzflieger</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>3.2</rating><plot>Rio Kowalski is a merchant and runs a starship along with his cyborg Max. As times aren't well he must take passengers on his freighter. When the undestroyable and multi-million dollar insured starship Titanius is stranded Rio sees his time has come. He would just have to manage to be the first to find the Titanius. However first he has to get rid of his passengers...</plot></movie><movie><title>Ya idu iskat</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Chamane</title><category>movie</category><year>1996</year><rating>7.3</rating><plot>A Yakut shaman and a Muscovite violinist escape a Soviet gulag on horseback. The shaman, Anatolia, promises to guide Dimitri, but Tolia is shot during the escape and dies. His spirit seems to guide Dimitri as the musician begins the arduous journey home across the snowbound taiga. In towns and settlements, Tolia's name seems magic, securing help for Dimitri. The horse, too, becomes savior and companion. When Dimitri finally reaches Irkutsk, he sells the horse to a Gypsy for train fare. While waiting overnight for the train, he meets a woman and they go dancing. After sex, in the dark of a freezing night, Dimitri makes a decision. The music of Tolia's trump is in his soul.</plot></movie><movie><title>Bastard Out of Carolina</title><category>movie</category><year>1996</year><rating>7.3</rating><plot>Difficult tale of poor, struggling South Carolinian mother &amp; daughter, who each face painful choices with their resolve and pride. Bone, the eldest daughter, and Anney her tired mother, grow both closer and farther apart: Anney sees Glen as her last chance.</plot></movie><movie><title>Best-Seller: El premio</title><category>movie</category><year>1996</year><rating>4.3</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Chess Kids</title><category>movie</category><year>1996</year><rating>7.1</rating><plot></plot></movie>