<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE glossary>
<glossary><movie><title>The Brady Bunch Movie</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>5.7</rating><plot>Mike Brady and his wife Carol Brady have just only one week to come up with $20,000 in back taxes or their house is sold and they'll have no choice but to move. And it's up to the Brady kids to secretly raise money and save the homestead before they lose their house to their scheming neighbor Mr. Larry Dittmeyer.</plot></movie><movie><title>Broadcast Bombshells</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>2.8</rating><plot>At WSEX, a local television broadcasting station in New Jersey, Kendall Saranski is the beautiful blond anchorwoman and the object of desire for all men working at the station including the libidos sportscaster Brian Kilgore and the station owner Mr. Buel. But Kendall is only interested in a kind-hearted stage hand named Neil whom is an old friend from her school days. Meanwhile, the conniving and ambitious brunette associate producer Amanda Cross, jealous of Kendall's rising fame, plots to further her career by having her tech boyfriend Gordon plot to bring Kendall and Brian's downfall using her seductive charms to go after Brian and have Gordon videotape it for future leverage against Brian. Other subplots include a mad bomber in the neighborhood blowing up various public places, a legendary grue sponsor named Frank Friendly holding onto his secret "three little words" as his motto, and a climatic fund-raiser telethon which brings all parties together for a final confrontation.</plot></movie><movie><title>Sex &amp; the Other Man</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>4.6</rating><plot>Look What the Wife Dragged Home Tonight! Arthur Wilkins is an unusual prisoner of love in this strangely romantic comedy. When Bill finds his girlfriend in bed with her boss, Bill's excitement goes further than just to his head. What follows is a strange cure for impotence as Bill and Jessica finally get it on while Arthur, their hostage, looks on.</plot></movie><movie><title>Condition Red</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>4.7</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>The Evil Inside Me</title><category>movie</category><year>1993</year><rating>4.6</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Come the Dawn</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>2.1</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>A hetedik testver</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>7.2</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>...kone na betone</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>6.4</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Angel Baby</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>7.0</rating><plot>Two schizophrenics meet during therapy and fall passionately in love. Ahead of them lies the inevitable road to disaster...one they share to the end.</plot></movie><movie><title>Redheads</title><category>movie</category><year>1992</year><rating>4.0</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Ilusiones de radio</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Jeffrey</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>6.2</rating><plot>Jeffery, a young gay man in New York, decides that sex is too much and decided to become celibate. He immediately meets the man of his dreams and must decide whether or not love is worth the danger of a boyfriend dying.</plot></movie><movie><title>Mr. Payback: An Interactive Movie</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>4.4</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Sebastian - When Everybody Knows</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>4.9</rating><plot>16 year old Sebastian behaves strangely. He stays alone in his room for hours thinking and doesn't talk to his parents as he used to. He refuses to explain to them what his problem is. The truth is that he slowly discovers that he feels stangely for his best friend Ulf. Soon he is going to accept his true self - that he is gay and that he is also in love with his best friend Ulf.</plot></movie>