<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE glossary>
<glossary><movie><title>Bowl: The Movie</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>The Champagne Safari</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>6.6</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Fun House Express</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>7.0</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Last Enchantment</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Murdered Innocence</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>5.4</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Poison Ivy II</title><category>movie</category><year>1996</year><rating>4.0</rating><plot>Lily is a sheltered art student from Michigan going to school in California. She finds an apartment and her roommates aren't quite normal. One day she finds a box of items belonging to a girl she's never met before. But in the box are nude pictures of the girl and her diary. Lily begins reading the diary and realizes that she's going to change her life and become a wild woman! She begins dating a guy and at the same time her art instructor begins to lust after her. The struggle begins when her boyfriend thinks she's unfaithful to him and her art teacher becomes obsessed.</plot></movie><movie><title>Al-tasmim</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Restoration</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>6.6</rating><plot>An aspiring young physician, Robert Merivel found himself in the service of King Charles II and saves the life of someone close to the King. Merivel joins the King's court and lives the high life provided to someone of his position. Merivel is ordered to marry his King's mistress in order to divert the queens suspicions. He is given one order by the king and that is not to fall in love. The situation worsens when Merivel finds himself in love with his new wife. Eventually, the King finds out and relieves Merivel of his position and wealth. His fall from grace leaves Merivel where he first started. And through his travels and reunions with an old friend, he rediscovers his love for true medicine and what it really means to be a physician.</plot></movie><movie><title>Mut ohne Befehl - Widerstand und Verfolgung in Stuttgart 1933-1945</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Jesus of Judson</title><category>movie</category><year>1996</year><rating>6.0</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Colpo di luna</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>7.0</rating><plot>Lorenzo, a milanese astrophysicist, has recently inherited a country house in Sicily and has it restored by Salvatore, an introverted carpenter. Salvatore starts his job with the help of his handicapped son. Since work seems to be very slow Lorenzo goes and checks on them and finds out that Salvatore has turned the house into a therapeutic community for troubled people. At first he's very angry but then his good heart prevails.</plot></movie><movie><title>Another Froggy Evening</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>7.3</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>All Men Are Liars</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>5.9</rating><plot>Mick's father, Barry, sells the family piano, causing Mick's mother, Irene to leave. In order to raise enough money to buy the piano back, Mick dresses in his mother's clothes and becomes Michelle to join an all-girl band that has come into town for the annual harvest festival. Angela, the leader of the band, starts to question her sexuality when she begins to fall in love with Mick/Michelle.</plot></movie><movie><title>Tom &amp; Viv</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating>6.6</rating><plot>In 1915, T.S. (Tom) Eliot and Vivienne Haigh-Wood elope, but her longstanding gynecological and emotional problems disrupt their planned honeymoon. Her father is angry because Tom's poetry doesn't bring in enough to live on, but her mother is happy Viv has found a tender and discreet husband.</plot></movie><movie><title>Serp i molot</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating>6.6</rating><plot>This is an interesting yet bizarre little tale of a fictional (as far as I know, anyway) experiment performed during the Stalin-controlled years in the USSR. The main character is changed from a woman into a man. This is part of a larger plan to change more women into men and have a stronger work-force/army, etc. It's a very in-depth character study of the main character, who tries to fit into a world that she (now 'he') doesn't really understand, especially since she's now a man ... Stalin dislikes the results of the experiments and has the scientist killed. The main character then goes off to live a life as a simple, unknown everyday Soviet, but is inexplicably drawn into larger and larger schemes (somewhat reminiscent of "Forrest Gump" in that way). (s)He has run-ins with different important characters, including his ex-boyfriend from his days of being a woman, as well as going on a demented quest for the nurse with whom he possibly fell in love after the operation... However, he is trapped in his life as an important Soviet married man, and in the end makes a huge sacrifice for his country (unwillingly), and the movie goes from there to an ending that is possibly happy, yet still somehow incredibly depressing.</plot></movie><movie><title>Vaterland</title><category>movie</category><year>1992</year><rating>6.3</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Trollsyn</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating>7.1</rating><plot>Maren, a young girl, is the sole survivor of the Black Death in her Norwegian village. Using instincts, folklore, luck, and the clairvoyant powers granted her by being born with a "Victory Cap," Maren survives on her own, waiting for other people to discover her plight. Painstaking recreations of medieval customs and settings dominate the film.</plot></movie><movie><title>Afraid to Love</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>War of the Buttons</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating>7.1</rating><plot>The children of Ballydowse and Carrickdowse engage in battles where they cut of the buttons, shoe-laces and underwear of their captured opponents. This is to get the boys in trouble with their parents. They go to battle in mass groups of dozens, throwing stones and cutting off their opponents buttons etc. And sometimes they go to battle completely naked and exposed. In one such scene about 30 boys return from a battle to celebrate victory at a barn-house only to find some girls waiting for them and they get very embarrassed at losing their privacy.</plot></movie><movie><title>Blood &amp; Donuts</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>5.9</rating><plot>In 1994, in Toronto, the vampire Boya awakens from his twenty-five years of sleep in a basement hit by a golf ball. He takes a cab to the local cemetery, retrieves his belongings from a grave and lodges in a low budget hotel nearby an all-night donut shop. Boya does not drink human blood anymore but rats and pigeons blood instead. While in the donut shop, Boya befriends and protects the taxi driver Earl, who is having trouble with two criminals, and falls in love for the waitress Molly. Meanwhile, his former passion of 1969, Rita, who misses her lost youth, is trying to locate him.</plot></movie></glossary>
