<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE glossary>
<glossary><movie><title>Book of Knives</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Deadly Embrace: Nicaragua, the World Bank and the International Monetary Fund</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Eno nakano bokuno mura</title><category>movie</category><year>1996</year><rating>7.0</rating><plot>Tells of the childhood of two nine-year-old twins in a rural village in Japan after World War 2. Includes the boys relationships with their schoolteacher mother, civil servant father, elderly landlord, a rough new boy at the school, and three mysterious spirits in the form of old women.</plot></movie><movie><title>Catwalk</title><category>movie</category><year>1996</year><rating>6.1</rating><plot>A camera follows model Christy Turlington through the spring fashion shows in Milan, Paris, and New York one year in the early 1990s, probably 1992. She and others dash from one designer's unveilings to another. Extended footage looks at Versace and Armani in Milan, Galliano, Gaultier, and Langerfeld in Paris, and Isaac Mizrahi in New York. With Kate Moss, Naomi Campbell, and Turlington, we see the nature of friendships among models. With the engaging Mizrahi in particular, there's some exploration of the relationship between designer and models.</plot></movie><movie><title>Cachito</title><category>movie</category><year>1996</year><rating>5.7</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>La Ceremonie</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>7.6</rating><plot>Sophie, a quiet and shy maid working for the upper-class family Lelievre, hides her illiteracy under the cloak of a perfect household and obedience. She finds a friend in the energetic and uncompromising postmaster Jeanne, who encourages her to stand up against her bourgeois employers. Things start to escalate as the Lelievres find out that Sophie can't read and has brought Jeanne into their house against their wish.</plot></movie><movie><title>Change the Frame</title><category>movie</category><year>1996</year><rating></rating><plot>Angela, is a college graduate working a fast food cart. She has put her career on hold while waiting for her girlfriend Rachel to finish graduate school. The status quo for this lesbian couple living in a small college town in the Colorado Rockies is upset when a flirtatious singer from San Francisco shows up and becomes interested in Angela.</plot></movie><movie><title>Bred vdvoyom</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Bunte Hunde</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>5.9</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Desert Winds</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>6.1</rating><plot>Jackie and Eugene are joined by a mystical wind tunnel which enables them to speak across a 500-mile desert. Believed by the Indians to be an omen of good luck, the wind inspires both characters to face their fears and follow their hearts.</plot></movie><movie><title>Gospa</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>5.2</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Jonssonligans storsta kupp</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>4.3</rating><plot>When Vanheden and Dynamit-Harry tries to break doctor Busé out of jail, they get Herman Melvin instead. He has been working at the Swedish Mint and the doctor, who has started to think like Sickan, has written a plan for making a burglary there, on Melvin's back. However, something goes wrong. They don't get a lot of Deutsch-marks as they planned but instead, they end up on a ship going to Poland, together with bunches and bunches of Polish Zlotys (the Polish currency). In Poland, they discover that the mafia are very interested in that money and Wall-Enberg is working with the mafia.</plot></movie><movie><title>Nico Icon</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>7.0</rating><plot>A look into the many lives of Christa Päffgen, otherwise known as Nico; from cutie German mädchen to the first of the supermodels, to glamorous diva of the Velvet Underground, to cult item, junkie and hag. Many faces for the same woman, whom, you realize, just couldn't bring herself to care enough to live.</plot></movie><movie><title>Peach</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>3.0</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>El provocador</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Rude</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>6.3</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>The Nature of the Beast</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>6.2</rating><plot>Jack meets Adrian out in Nevada. Adrian latches on to Jack, and won't go away. Jack tries to lose Adrian, but Adrian informs Jack not to mess with him, or he'll call the police because he knows Jack's secret. In the meantime, the car radio keeps blaring news reports of a serial killer in the area called "The Hatchet Man", as well as a theft of a huge sum of money from a local casino. Jack is concealing a briefcase, and wherever he and Adrian go, "The Hatchet Man" seems to strike within the vicinity!</plot></movie><movie><title>Mushrooms</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>7.3</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Ged</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Halleluja</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie>