<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE glossary>
<glossary><movie><title>Die Wurzel der Dummheit</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Hikayatul jawahiri thalath</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>6.7</rating><plot>A Palestinian boy becomes entranced with a beautiful Gypsy girl and a fairy tale world she weaves amidst conflict in Gaza. The children explore nature, mysticism and what their future holds, while learning to live with the surrounding brutality c. 1990. Yusef's family scrapes by in a seaside camp while his father's in prison and his heavily-armed brother's on the run, parrying with Israeli troops. Salah, Yusef's schoolmate from a well-off Arab family strives faithfully to assist them, while Yusef helps an elderly, blind neighbor escape from his lonely abandonment into the North American dreamworld he's waited so long for.</plot></movie><movie><title>Rhytm</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Tollbooth</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating>4.8</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Undefeatable</title><category>movie</category><year>1993</year><rating>3.7</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Spivachka Zhosefina i myshachyy narod</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating>5.0</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Time Is Money</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating>4.5</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>The Shawshank Redemption</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating>9.2</rating><plot>Andy Dufresne is a young and successful banker whose life changes drastically when he is convicted and sentenced to life imprisonment for the murder of his wife and her lover. Set in the 1940's, the film shows how Andy, with the help of his friend Red, the prison entrepreneur, turns out to be a most unconventional prisoner.</plot></movie><movie><title>Stories of Chide the Wind: The Soul Investigator</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Ponchada</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating>8.8</rating><plot>A car with a flat tire in the middle of a lonely road. A chain-smoking woman is waiting in the driver's seat. Suddenly, a car approaches. The driver (a somber menacing man) offers to help her. The woman refuses but he insists. She suspects he wants something more.</plot></movie><movie><title>Mutter</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>The Lion King</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating>8.2</rating><plot>A young lion prince is born in Africa, thus making his uncle Scar the second in line to the throne. Scar plots with the hyenas to kill King Mufasa and Prince Simba, thus making himself King. The King is killed and Simba is led to believe by Scar that it was his fault, and so flees the kingdom in shame. After years of exile he is persuaded to return home to overthrow the usurper and claim the kingdom as his own thus completing the "Circle of Life".</plot></movie><movie><title>Pass</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Radio dans est pour</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Sherlock: Undercover Dog</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating>2.0</rating><plot>Billy, 10, a dreamer, wants to be taken seriously so he can live with his toy-designer father on Catalina Island. Billy's plans get seriously spoilt when Sherlock, a talking police dog, demands his help to rescue his police detective handler kidnaped by smugglers. But Sherlock likes to keep his talking a closely-guarded secret. So now no one will take Billy seriously until he rescues the kidnaped detective and catches the smugglers...</plot></movie><movie><title>Time &amp; Again</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating>6.8</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Eine Wienerin im wilden Osten</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Olfilm</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Le vent du Wyoming</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating>6.6</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Xiang Gang qi an: Zhi xi xue gui li wang</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating>6.6</rating><plot></plot></movie>