<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE glossary>
<glossary><movie><title>Bye Bye Love</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>5.8</rating><plot>This is a story about the breakup of the family. In particular, it focuses on the lifestyle of three divorced men. The film is presented from their perspective and it reveals their relationship with their children, ex-wives, girl friends, male friendships, and their identities as divorced men. In addition to dealing with divorce, the film touches on spousal loss and young adult homelessness. The film can be considered a social commentary that is both comical and emotional.</plot></movie><movie><title>The Aristocratic Peasant Girl</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>5.9</rating><plot>Based on a famous short story by Pushkin, this film tells of a youthful, innocent and pure love story that begins as a girlish joke. Liza is eager to get to know her young neighbour but cannot do so as their fathers are not on speaking terms. Her response is simple and direct. With the help of her loyal servant Nastia, she dresses up as a peasant girl and goes pick mushrooms in the nearby woods....</plot></movie><movie><title>Brylcream Boulevard</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>5.6</rating><plot>In this sequel to Blueberry Hill, the boys of the Catholic metal working-class, who are now all working, decide to take revenge on the hated former principal Verbiest, after the sanctimonious 'pillar of society' assaulted one of their girls. Since he is now a close collaborator of the Belgian minister of education, planning to launch his own political career by showing off a fund-raising telethon on Flemish TV, where one of the boys works as a technician, they decide to expose him on the air.</plot></movie><movie><title>Angel Hearts</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>5.3</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Decoy</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>4.6</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Audacious</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>5.3</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>La croisade d'Anne Buridan</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>7.6</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Butterfly</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>The City of Lost Children</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>7.7</rating><plot>Krank (</plot></movie><movie><title>1/2 8</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Az aldozat</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating>7.8</rating><plot>Mail author for translation. Az 1956-os forradalom napjaiban a Péterffy Sándor utcai kórház nagyon fontos szerepet játszott a sebesültek mentésében és kellátásában. Mivel az országos mentöszolgálat nem volt képes feladatának ellátására, a kórház fiatal orvostanhallgatói, orvosai önkéntes mentöszolgálatot alalkitottak, amelynek vezetö személyisége Péch Géza volt. Hihetetlen önfeláldozással végezték munkájukat, többen közülük a harcok szinhelyein vesztették életüket. forradalmat követö megtorlás során Péch Gézát államellenes szervezkedés vezetése és hütlenség vádjával halálra itélték és 1958 áprilisában kivégezték.</plot></movie><movie><title>And Many Happy Returns</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>1.7</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Yalla yaana</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Tief oben</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating>6.3</rating><plot>In the 16th century, young men took a very high risk to seek for mysterious crystals "tief oben" ("high above") in the tunnel of the Styrian Erzberg. Many of them never returned from the search for this symbol of perfect love. In the 20th century, a young student investigates the legend of her home town.</plot></movie><movie><title>Se jiang II zhi xie mei gui</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating>4.7</rating><plot>An evil witch in Thailand is kidnaping and brainwashing beautiful women into joining her cult. A man and his girlfriend, searching for her missing sister, join forces with a priest and a local cop to fight the cult.</plot></movie>