<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE glossary>
<glossary><movie><title>Anglagard - andra sommaren</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating>5.2</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Un taxi pour Aouzou</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Trista let spustya</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating>5.2</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Stace</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Syrup</title><category>movie</category><year>1993</year><rating>6.1</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Qing feng xia</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating>3.7</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>In the Army Now</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating>4.2</rating><plot>Two misguided youths join the reserves to make some money for their entrepreneurial dreams. No sooner than they finish basic training are they called up to do their part to save the free world.</plot></movie><movie><title>A Gnome Named Gnorm</title><category>movie</category><year>1990</year><rating>4.0</rating><plot>Gnorm is just an average Gnome. But he wants to impress the lady Gnomes by doing something heroic. So he steals the Gnome's magic stones to expose them to sunlight to recharge them. When he gets to the surface, (Gnome's live deep underground) he witnesses a murder, and the killer ends up with his stones. Detective Casey, who was working a sting operation with the murdered man, (another detective) is blamed for botching the sting, and causing the death. Wanting to catch the killer to clear his name, he teams up with Gnorm, who he accidentally discovers. He is going to need Samantha's help, but she thinks he is a nut. You see, no one else knows about Gnorm.</plot></movie><movie><title>Di xia cai jue</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>CIA II: Target Alexa</title><category>movie</category><year>1993</year><rating>3.4</rating><plot>Alexa is one of the best, but her handiwork is done for terrorists. When she is finally captured, it is up to CIA agent Graver to turn her against her latest employer who has diplomatic immunity. Graver is one of the best at the CIA, but since the chip has been stolen, he has to use Alexa to find it. Alexa is too tough to turn on her own, so Graver must find the key to unlock her conviction. While he is working on Alexa, his boss is working on Graver.</plot></movie><movie><title>Dark Side of Genius</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating>3.5</rating><plot>Julian Jons is a talented but troubled young artist. He has just been released from an asylum, where he has spent the last seven years for the murder of Anna, his girlfriend/model. Attempting to start painting again, he is pursued by journalist Jennifer Cole, who is intrigued by this complex, brooding man. Against the backdrop of the modern art world, she begins to dig into the past, fully aware that it holds painful memories for Julian, and perhaps danger for herself.</plot></movie><movie><title>Glenda and Camille Do Downtown</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Beg!</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating>4.8</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>The Stream</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating></rating><plot>A young mother has been forced to flee her home carrying her husband's aged mother on her back. The old woman cannot walk. In addition, there are three small children to care for. There is no food in the middle of winter in the Bosnian mountains. Somehow she must get through the isolated mountain pass to a safe village. She cannot carry the old woman and the two smallest children as well. The young woman is faced with a terrible choice - either she sacrifices the old woman, or her children will die. We see that the old woman realizes this herself, and indicates to the daughter-in-law that she accepts her fate. The young woman then drowns the old woman in a mountain stream. The last image of the film is hopeful. We see the young woman, now carrying the children, arriving at a village. She knocks on the door of a house.</plot></movie><movie><title>Bu wen nu xue tang</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating>6.4</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Jian ren shi jia</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Milk Money</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating>5.2</rating><plot>Young Frank and his pals get an idea for the ultimate in excitement. They decide to pool their savings, bicycle to the nearby Big City, and hire some woman of the streets to strip for them. Things do not work out that simply, but they do meet V, a Hooker With A Heart Of Gold, who ends up giving them a ride home. Soon she is living in Frank's treehouse, unbeknownst to Frank's widowed father Tom, who thinks she is one of Frank's teachers. Soon, however, the evil Waltzer comes looking for V.</plot></movie><movie><title>La hija del Puma</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating>5.4</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Lazarus</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating>4.4</rating><plot>This unusual drama with a message, set in England and filmed entirely in English, concerns a wealthy British couple of Polish descent who adopt a son because they are unable to have children. However the illegal adoption process they go through involves paying an exorbitant fee to an underground broker, and the child they receive is not the Latin American infant promised, but a strangely hardened 10-year-old from Mozambique. Desperately disappointed with their "purchase," the new parents nonetheless make fumbling efforts to make the child Lazar feel at home. But Lazar is not receptive, and behaves more like a threatened and hunted animal each day in his affluent surroundings. In time, the couple are able to communicate with the boy to discover that he saw his family die and was forced to accompany the army, where along with other children he was trained to execute prisoners in mass killings. Lazar ultimately develops the will to try to become a child again, but he feels constantly endangered by the wealthy new world around him. One day he runs away, stealing a weapon from his favorite new grandfather. When police rounds up of him, it looks like the boy tries to defend himself.</plot></movie><movie><title>Hong mei gui bai mei gui</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating>7.0</rating><plot>Chronicles the love life of a man, Zhenbao. He has a steamy fling with the wife of a friend, the saucy and exciting Red Rose. Even though he feels happy with her, he knows he will not end up with her. To maintain his reputation, he marries an antiseptic, frigid but classy lady of a prim and proper background (White rose). Dissonance abound when he finds his bride irritating.</plot></movie></glossary>
