<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE glossary>
<glossary><movie><title>Akwarium</title><category>movie</category><year>1996</year><rating>6.5</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Une bonne journee</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Sparprogramm</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Uttoran</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating>7.9</rating><plot>Sen Gupta, a doctor who only treats upper-class patients, is forced to confront his own moral and medical beliefs as he discovers rural India during an unexpected stop at a village. He finds a breathless man lying on the side of the road. With little sympathy, the doctor sends him back to his own village for treatment. When Dr. Gupta discovers that the villages wants a witch doctor to treat the man, he attends the exorcism and is shocked. A transformation of the cold city man then follows.</plot></movie><movie><title>Sin palabras... Jujuy</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Tropical Fish</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Az utazas</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Stills</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Stargate</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating>6.7</rating><plot>A small group of US troups and an Egyptologist use an ancient device found in 1920s Egypt to transport themselves to a distant planet. There they discover .. err, well any more plot would be considered a spoiler.</plot></movie><movie><title>The School</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Music for the Movies: Toru Takemitsu</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating>7.5</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Remembrance of Things Fast: True Stories Visual Lies</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating>6.9</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>The Secret of Roan Inish</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating>7.4</rating><plot>10-year-old Fiona is sent to live with her grandparents in a small fishing village in Donegal, Ireland. She soon learns the local legend that an ancestor of hers married a Selkie - a seal who can turn into a human. Years earlier, her baby brother washed out to sea in a cradle shaped like a boat; someone in the family believes the boy is being raised by the seals. Then Fiona catches sight of a naked little boy on the abandoned Isle of Roan Inish and takes an active role in uncovering The Secret of Roan Inish. Written by John Oswalt.</plot></movie><movie><title>Zadoc et le bonheur</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>4.0</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Shaolin Popey</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating>5.1</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Stickfighter</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating>1.9</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Unishe April</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating>8.0</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Sea Life</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Poussieres de vie</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>6.0</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Separate Lives</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>4.7</rating><plot>The e-cop Tom Beckwith has just quit his police job in order to study psychology. But his professor, Lauren Porter, is more interested in his criminology abilities than in his progress in psychology. Because of traumatic circumstances during her childhood she is suffering from schizophrenia, and it looks like her other ego has just killed somebody. So Tom Beckwith tries to help her by observing her, combining his professional abilities as an ex-cop and his recently gained knowledge of psychology.</plot></movie>