<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE glossary>
<glossary><movie><title>Denise Calls Up</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>6.7</rating><plot>A group of friends in New York, working away at their PCs and laptops, keep in touch exclusively by phone and fax. They are all too busy to meet face to face. Gale plays matchmaker, by phone, to Jerry and Barbara who, in turn, hit it off beautifully...via phone and fax. Martin gets a telephone call from someone he's never met. It's Denise, with some extraordinary news. Tapping away at his computer all the while, he develops a sort of friendship with Denise...via phone. And so it goes as the friends, tap, tap, tapping away, share news, hopes, and dreams...via phone and fax. Finally Gale has an unfortunate encounter with a phone, Denise has some more news for Martin, and Frank plans a gala New Year's Eve party, but will he answer the door?</plot></movie><movie><title>The Day of the Beast</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>7.5</rating><plot>A basque priest finds by means of a cabalistic study of the bible that the anti-christ is going to be born on Christmas day in Madrid. Helped by a heavy-metal fan and by the showman of a TV esoteric program, he will try to invoke the devil to find out the place of birth and kill the baby.</plot></movie><movie><title>Captured Alive</title><title>Apollo 13</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>7.5</rating><plot>Based on the true story of the ill-fated 13th Apollo mission bound for the moon. Astronauts Lovell, Haise and Swigert were scheduled to fly Apollo 14, but are moved up to 13. It's 1970, and America have already achieved their lunar landing goal, so there's little interest in this "routine" flight.. until that is, things go very wrong, and prospects of a safe return fade.</plot></movie><movie><title>Eat Drink Man Woman</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating>7.7</rating><plot>Senior Master Chef Chu lives in a large house in Taipei with his three unmarried daughters, Jia-Jen, a chemistry teacher converted to Christianity, Jia-Chien, an airline executive, and Jia-Ning, a student who also works in a fast food restaurant. Life in the house revolves around the ritual of an elaborate dinner each Sunday, and the love lives of all the family members.</plot></movie><movie><movie><title>Antonia</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>7.4</rating><plot>In an anonymous Dutch village, a sturdy, strong-willed matriarch looks back upon her life, the generations of family and friends gathered around her table, and ponders the cyclical nature of time.</plot></movie><movie><title>Words Upon the Window Pane</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating>5.8</rating><plot>This film is based on the one act play by W B Yeats and concerns another great figure from Irish literature, Jonathan Swift, whose spirit, with those of his two livers, Stella and Vanessa, emergrs in a series of seances held in Dublin in 1928. Their passion, Swift's torment and ultimately Stella's revenge are enacted. Thrown together by the crisis, those attending the seance are forced to confront the truths of their own lives ....</plot></movie><movie><title>Boy Crazy, Girl Crazier</title><category>movie</category><year>1996</year><rating>6.3</rating><plot>Celena and Charlie live together in L.A., and both of them want to make it in the movies. At a Hollywood party, Charlie manages to grab himself a part in a film, and he does it by stealing material from Celena. Then he discards her, like a used tissue. Not only does she get mad, she gets even.</plot></movie><movie><title>Croce e delizia</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>5.3</rating><plot>A Parigi una troupe italiana sta girando in economia un film sulla Traviata. A Rosa, la sarta del primo attore Alberto Sanna, piace molto il personaggio di Violetta, tanto da piangere ogni volta che ? in scena. Alcuni colleghi allora, guidati da Animamorta, decidono di farle uno scherzo e con l'aiuto di Harriette inscenano una finta seduta spiritica in cui rosa viene identificata da uno spirito come la reincarnazione di Violetta. Il film intanto, tra una serie di incidenti e l'altra, va lentamente avanti, mentre Rosa racconta a tratti la sua vita a Barbara, compagna di camera. Ogni tanto poi vede una donna misteriosa vestita in abiti ottocenteschi che poi scompare. Alberto intanto si trova un'amica, Juliette, della quale Rosa ? gelosa. E arriva il finale, dell'opera e del film.</plot></movie><movie><title>Cyber Vengeance</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>4.0</rating><plot>The year is 2005. The prison system is run by the private sector. Business tycoon R.D. Crowley, has created a virtual reality prison. The prisoner's bodies are locked in suspended animation while their minds traverse the lethal labyrinth of games Crowley designed for them. Crowley allows wealthy sportsmen to participate, for a price, in deadly VR combat with the prisoners. Will breaks into the prison and attempts to eradicate the VR technology. Seduced by his VR girlfriend he becomes addicted to VR. Will is caught and thrown into the lethal time-traveling web of Crowley's virtual hunt. With their lives at stake, Will and the prisoners must escape certain death, and destroy the VR prison.</plot></movie><movie><title>Gordy</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>3.6</rating><plot>This is the story of a talking cute piglet named Gordy, who gets involved in a big quest to save his family from the slaughterhouse, where no pigs have ever returned. And it's all up to Gordy to find and save his family before they turned into sausage!</plot></movie><movie><title>Jin yu man tang</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>6.9</rating><plot>Kit is a gangster looking to start a new life as a chef in Canada, so he can be closer to his girlfriend. But in his struggle to learn the fine art of cuisine, he runs across a red-headed beauty who will change his plans, and soon finds himself off in search of the retired master who can teach him how to win in the ultimate cooking challenge.</plot></movie>
