<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE glossary>
<glossary><movie><title>Blue in the Face</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>6.5</rating><plot>Wayne Wang's follow-up movie to Smoke presents a series of improvisational situations strung together to form a pastiche of Brooklyn's diverse ethnicity, offbeat humor, and essential humanity. Many of the same characters inhabiting Auggie Wren's Brooklyn Cigar Store in Smoke return here to expound on their philosophy of smoking, relationships, baseball, New York, and Belgian Waffles. Most of all, this is a movie about living life, off-the-cuff.</plot></movie><movie><title>The Cloud Door</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating>6.0</rating><plot>A very clever parrot lives in a hindu palace, surrounded by many beautiful girls, but the parrot escapes, and is trapped far from the palace. One day, when it's new owner is sleeping, the bird convinces a young boy to open the cage door. In return, it shows the boy a secret passage to get into the palace.</plot></movie><movie><title>Barsaat</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>5.8</rating><plot>Badal (Bobby Deol) is a naive but intelligent young man who comes from a small village to the big city. He is introduced to city life by Damru (Harish Patel) who now calls himself Danny. When Badal attends college, he meets with pretty and percocious, Tina Oberoi (Twinkle Khanna), and after a few misunderstanding and misadventures, both fall in love. This is not taken well by Tina's dad, (Raj Babbar), who hopes to marry Tina with his friend's (Bharat Kapoor) son. Tina's dad complains to the college principal (Vijay Kashyap), but Tina testifies in favour of Badal. Tina's dad then asks a corrupt cop, Neghi, who is the city's Assistant Commissioner of Police, for assistance. Neghi arrests Badal on trumped up charges and imprisons him. Badal's dad (Mukesh Khanna) also comes to the big city to try and make sense of why Badal ended up in prison. Tina's dad gives a contract to Neghi to have Badal killed, to which Neghi agrees and hires a gang of ruthless outlaws to hunt and kill Badal. He also pressurizes Tina not to acknowledge and meet Badal anymore, and Tina reluctantly agrees. Will Badal survive? Will Tina and Badal's love be fated to end tragically?</plot></movie><movie><title>Barlach-Kantate - Es geht ein kraftiges Atmen</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating></rating><plot>A musical film based on Michael Baumgartl's cantata for solo tenor, chorus and instruments after texts by Ernst Barlach. The cantata is the foundation of a two-part film work that fits into no single genre. The first part documents the rehearsals of the cantata at the Luebeck musik academy. The second part leads with the music into a world of images that circles around Barlach's works and thoughts and relates them to the town of Guestrow and the Mecklenburg countryside where Barlach spent most of his life.</plot></movie><movie><title>Beyond Bob</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>7.8</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Caged Heat 3000</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>3.8</rating><plot>It's the year 3000 AD. The world's most dangerous women are banished to a remote asteroid 45 million light years from earth. Kira Murphy doesn't belong; wrongfully accused of a crime she did not commit, she's thrown in this interplanetary prison and left to her own defenses. But Kira's a fighter, and soon she finds herself in the middle of a female gang war; where everyone wants a piece of the action... and a piece of her! "Caged Heat 3000" takes the Women-in-Prison genre to a whole new level... and a whole new galaxy!</plot></movie><movie><title>Boomerang</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>5.7</rating><plot>Two university researchers claim the existence of serious police brutality in Bergen, Norway, in the early 1980s. The film follows the public reactions to these allegations, the victimization of the researchers and the legal persecution of their informants.</plot></movie><movie><title>Madame Petlet's True Story</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>3.3</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Ausgeraumt</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Frank and Ollie</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>7.8</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Eight O'Clock, at Your Place</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>3.1</rating><plot>Javiera and Antonio are a young couple with two daughters and another on the way. But beneath the superficial tranquillity of their marriage hides a passionate relationship between Antonio and his wife's sister, Antonieta. The love triangle begins to lose its delicate balance when Antonieta loses her purse. A mysterious voice on the telephone extorts the lovers, moving them to take unusual actions and to confront one another with blame and doubt, ultimately forcing them to explore the true value of their relationship.</plot></movie><movie><title>Chuang zha ma mi</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>5.4</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Aurora: Operation Intercept</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>3.3</rating><plot>There have been two mysterious plane crashes in only 48 hours. The aircraft suddenly lose control and crash, killing everyone aboard. A woman of Russian descent, Francesca Zaborszin, the daughter of a slain Federal investigator, claims responsibility for the crashes. She believes her father was killed by the FBI as part of a cover-up operation and wishes to avenge his death by threatening to down more aircraft using the same electromagnetic pulse method. She also intends to crash a stolen military jet into the White House. There's no time to ground the planes: just enough time to try to stop her.</plot></movie><movie><title>Dalmatinischer Hund</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Baja</title><category>movie</category><year>1996</year><rating>5.4</rating><plot>Alex and Bebe are camped out in Baja California, Mexico, after their disastrous first attempt at a drug deal. Impatiently awaiting forged passports, they are unaware that Bebe's father has convinced her estranged husband Michael to find her. Michael soon arrives in Baja California, where it appears he isn't the only foreigner trying to find Alex and Bebe.</plot></movie><movie><title>Wariko, le gros lot</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating></rating><plot>In the Ivory Coast, Ali (Toure) is a poor policeman who struggles to make ends meet for his wife, Awa (Kabore) and three children. Ali is excited and giddy When he learns that the lottery ticket that Awa bought him is a 3,000,000 winner. But after an extended, frantic search he cannot find the ticket anywhere and he starts to neglect his work. As his family and neighbors learn of his good fortune, they start to come to him with their hands out, and Ali is seen as a mark by others who learn of his winnings. When Ali at last finds the ticket, he realizes that he cannot meet everyone's wishes, even with ten Jackpots.</plot></movie><movie><title>Untitled II</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>World's Best Commercials 1994</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Speechless</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating>5.6</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Pigalle</title><category>movie</category><year>1992</year><rating>5.6</rating><plot>In the seedy neon-lit underworld of the Pigalle district of Paris, animalistic survival obscures all moral codes. Rival drug dealers use three minor figures as pawns in their murderous manoeuvres. Divine is a transexual, a performer in a club, the lover of Fifi, a man who's a street hustler and petty thief. Fifi, in turn, loves Divine but flirts with Véra, a striptease dancer and peep show attraction. When Divine is bullied into giving information to one drug dealer, the opposition uses Véra as bait to enlist Fifi as a hitman.</plot></movie></glossary>
