<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE glossary>
<glossary><movie><title>Teenage Exorcist</title><category>movie</category><year>1991</year><rating>5.1</rating><plot>Diane, a repressed, neurotic grad student, moves into a cursed mansion and is possessed by the house's demonic master.Transformed into a raven-haired, leather and lingerie-clad seductress, Diane seeks a virgin sacrifice for her master while her sister, brother-in-law, a priest, and a pizza boy try to rescue her and avoid his wrath.</plot></movie><movie><title>Teresa's Tattoo</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating>4.7</rating><plot>Mathematician Teresa just wanted to study during the College spring break. But her friends, who want her to live a little, drag her out to parties. The next thing she knows, she has been drugged, kidnapped, made a redhead, tattooed, and wearing leather?!? Her captors seem to be the most inept crooks ever. They seem to have a plan, if only she could figure out why it involves her.</plot></movie><movie><title>What's Going On, Frank?</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating>5.2</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Waati</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>7.1</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Warriors</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating>3.8</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Baby Face Nelson</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>5.6</rating><plot>Bonnie and Clyde were no match for Depression Era gangster George "Babyface" Nelson and his moll Helen Womack. Constantly on the lam from the law and from Chicago's biggest crime lord Al Capone, Babyface and his female accomplice leave a trail of blood and bullets in their path towards making history.</plot></movie><movie><title>Black Rose of Harlem</title><category>movie</category><year>1996</year><rating>4.7</rating><plot>A tragic love story set against the turbulent backdrop of the 1920's Chicago jazz clubs. Georgia, a beautiful black singer catches the eye of mobster Johnny Varona. But Johnny is betrothed to the daughter of mob boss Costanza, a man you don't say no to... and live! Can Johnny and Georgia find a way to fulfill their love -and- stay alive? Or will the mob prove to be an insurmountable force.</plot></movie><movie><title>Adios, tiburon</title><category>movie</category><year>1996</year><rating>4.4</rating><plot>The discouraging adventures of a bank clerk at the stock exchange who looses all of his money on one bad day by making only one wrong financial decision.</plot></movie><movie><title>Solo, de wet van de favela</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating>6.7</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Passage</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating>7.7</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Candide</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating>4.5</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Lurking Fear</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating>4.7</rating><plot>The town of Leffert's Corners has been plagued by unearthly beings for decades, and now there is only a few people left, including the local priest and a woman traumatised by the death of her sister. But when John Martense turns up to claim his illicit family fortune, with bad guys in pursuit, the last stand had become a lot more complicated. Supposedly based on the writings of H P Lovecraft.</plot></movie><movie><title>Kadotettu paratiisi</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Stories from the Kronen</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>6.1</rating><plot>Carlos is a young student, just 21. Nice or annoying as he likes, enjoys provoking and transgreding. In the night he goes out to meet his friends in the Kronen, a bar. Every situation can be taken a little farther. There are no limits, no accepted barriers. And more each time, each adventure is chained to the next, as if it were a continuous night. A long description of people: grandfather, parents, sister, girlfriend, friends. And, among that, the obscure will of living every minute as if it were the last one. But something which happens puts Carlos and his friend against a reality they have been trying to ignore.</plot></movie><movie><title>Gospel According to Harry</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating>5.6</rating><plot>The film is a biblical soap-opera whose action unfolds in the Californian desert. Karen and Wes's marriage is crumbling apart - like a sandcastle. Karen can't even make love to her husband any more - the sand has managed to get everywhere. Harry, a tax collector, is a witness to this marriage falling apart. As a civil servant he hears Wes confession. However he isn't able to help him. The omnipotent eye of television glitters above the desert - that raw allegory of America where neither the white nor the black have it good. If Samuel Beckett and Joan Collins had a romance, then their child would look like this film.</plot></movie><movie><title>Greetings from Africa</title><category>movie</category><year>1996</year><rating>7.7</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Hole in One</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Don't Pave Main Street: Carmel's Heritage</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating>7.1</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Insomnia</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating>5.5</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Genesi: La creazione e il diluvio</title><category>movie</category><year>1994</year><rating>5.3</rating><plot>An all-enveloping darkness. Suddenly, a child's voice, frightened, questioning, pierces the darkness... The first flickering rays of light begin to sculpt mysterious shapes out of the darkness ... Among them, a very old man. He reassures the child, exhorting him to see the wonders of the earth. And it is with this child's eyes that we will witness the creation of the world. Nature comes to life at the first light of dawn, recreating the seven days of the Creation. Adam appears, and is soon joined by Eve. Paradise could be theirs, but as time goes by, they grow restless, inquisitive... They approach the Tree of Knowledge - and discover pain, suffering and mortality. Their sons Cain and Abel play out a story that will continue to darken the Creation until the end of time. And angered by the corruption of Cain's progeny, by the lust and greed ruling the cities, God vows to wipe away his creatures and begin anew. With Noah and his family. The ark is built, the animals led into their pens, and the rain begins beating on the timbers, flooding the land, bringing fear and death. When the rains have devastated the world, the waters recede, the ark touches ground, and the dove sent out by Noah returns with an olive branch - the sign of new life and of a new pact with God.</plot></movie>