<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE glossary>
<glossary><movie><title>First Person Plural: The Electronic Diaries</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Frankenstein's Planet of Monsters!</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>3.4</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Er nannte sich Surava</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating></rating><plot>Erich Hirsch aka Surava was a journalist. He wrote about the deportation of French jews, and the Swiss government chased him because the Swiss government was Nazi-friendly. The Swiss intelligence service (Bundespolizei) knew him as a "communist jew". In fact, he worked for a left newspaper, but he wasn't a jew. Surava took his courage to write about the "censored" inhumanity in Europe.</plot></movie><movie><title>Florentino y el diablo</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>7.5</rating><plot>Florentino is a young horseman and singer, a free spirit living in the open world without restrictions, in the Venezuelan plains. He confronts the devil in a duel of improvised verses. As time passes, these unspoilt plains start to change. Through Florentino's voice and actions, the plains cannot be conquered. Its culture defies the devil in the eternal fight between good and evil, between life and death.</plot></movie><movie><title>Die Hard: With a Vengeance</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>7.5</rating><plot>John McClane is now almost a full-blown alcoholic and is suspended from the NYPD. But when a bomb goes off in the Bonwit Teller Department Store the police go insane trying to figure out what's going on. Soon, a man named Simon calls and asks for McClane. Simon tells Inspector Walter Cobb that McClane is going to play a game called "Simon Says". He says that McClane is going to do the tasks he assigns him. If not, he'll blow off another bomb. With the help of a Harlem electrician, John McClane must race all over New York trying to figure out the frustrating puzzles that the crafty terrorist gives him. But when a bomb goes off in a subway station right by the Federal Reserve (the biggest gold storage in the world) things start to get heated up.</plot></movie><movie><title>Midaq Alley</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>7.5</rating><plot>Based on the Nobel Prize Winner's novel, the Egyptian Naguib Mahfouz. The story, translated from El Cairo to Mexico City's downtown, narrates the life of the members of the neighbourhood and the connection between them Don Ru, the owner of the local pub; Eusebia, his wife; Chava, his son and Abel his friend, who emigrate to USA in search of fortune; Susanita, the single landtender always dreaming to marry a good man; Guicho, the pub's employee, who extracts the money when Don Ru is not there and finally marries Susanita; Alma, the very good looking girl, the Abel's dream, who becomes a luxury prostitute while he's away; Jimmy, the handsome young man Don Ru becomes infatuated with, etc. This movie won the Ariel (the Mexican Oscar) as best movie in 1995.</plot></movie><movie><title>Beim nachsten Kuss knall ich ihn nieder</title><category>movie</category><year>1996</year><rating>6.8</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Crying Freeman</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>6.4</rating><plot>A lethal assassin for a secret Chinese organisation, who sheds tears of regret each time he kills, is seen swiftly and mercilessly executing three Yakuza gangsters by a beautiful artist. She is captivated by the grace of his kill and later falls in love with him. An intense power struggle for the leadership of the Yakuza Clans ensues as they seek vengeance for the death of their leader. They soon realise the fatal mistake of underestimating the deadly skills of the Crying Freeman.</plot></movie><movie><title>L'assassino e quello con le scarpe gialle</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>7.0</rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Ab Insaf Hoga</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>3.7</rating><plot>Janki lives a poor lifestyle in a small village consisting of her dad, Bhervi Prasad and her mom. She meets and falls in love with her school-teacher, Ramcharan, and both want to get married. Ramcharan's brother is opposed to this marriage as Bhervi is unable to pay any dowry, nevertheless the marriage does take place, but the couple are turned out of Kalicharan's house, and instead go to live with Ramcharan's friend, Ashok Mishra. Ashok attempts to molest Janki, and a fight breaks out between Ramsharan and Ashok, and they move back to Janki's village where she finds that her parents have killed themselves. They decide to live in the village where Janki gives birth to a baby, Khusboo. Ramcharan is then assaulted by Ashok and receives a head injury that leaves him paralyzed. Janki takes him to Bombay, finds a job as a laborer, and takes Ramcharan to see a doctor. The doctor informs her that he must be treated immediately, however, it will cost her a lot of money. She approaches her employer, Girdharilal, who is willing to pay the entire cost of her husband's treatment provided she sleeps with him, when she refuses, she does not get any money and is instead molested. Ramcharan does recover a little, and goes to confront Girdharilal, but gets killed. The police refuse to register any complaint against Girdharilal. Alone, traumatized, and devastated Janki and Khusboo wander aimlessly. She gets into an accident with a car that belongs to Gaurishankar, a local gangster with a good heart, who wants to be a Muncipal Councillor. With Janki's help he does become a Councillor and both entrap Girdharilal, and then subsequently Ashok and Kalicharan, get them arrested on a variety of criminal charges and jailed. What Janki and Gaurishankar do not know is that the trio have gotten together in prison and have planned a devious scheme that will ensure that Janki gets killed - without implicating any one of them.</plot></movie><movie><title>Filthy Rich</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Hollow Reed</title><category>movie</category><year>1996</year><rating>7.5</rating><plot>Following the break-up of his marriage after revealing his homosexuality, GP Martin Wyatt loses custody of his son Oliver to his now ex-wife Hannah and her new partner Frank. It is not long, however, until Oliver appears at the house of Martin and his new lover Tom claiming to have been beaten up by boys in the park. After another incident, Martin puts two and two together and comes to the conclusion that Frank has been beating Oliver without Hannah's knowledge. Martin then begins a long courtroom custody battle to win back his son.</plot></movie><movie><title>Epilog</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating></rating><plot></plot></movie><movie><title>Cyborg 3: The Creation</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>3.1</rating><plot>Prepare yourself for the all too deadly future. Cash, the heroine of Cyborg 2, is living safe in the free zone. But not for long. Biomechanical problems are taking down her systems and a visit to a doctor in Silica confirms her worst fears. She is more then a marvel of cyborg technology. She is the first of her kind to become a creator-she is pregnant.</plot></movie><movie><title>Devil in a Blue Dress</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>6.6</rating><plot>It is 1948 in LA and Ezikeal "Easy" Rawlins, an African-American World War II veteran, is looking for work. At his friend's bar, he is introduced to a white man, DeWitt Albright, who is looking for someone to help him find a missing white woman assumed to be hiding somewhere in LA's Black community. This woman, Daphane Monet, happens to be the fiancée of a wealthy "blue blood," Todd Carter, who is currently the favorite in the city's mayoralty race. Daphane Monet is known to frequent the Black jazz clubs in LA. Easy, innocently, accepts Albright's offer; however, he quickly finds himself amidst murder, crooked cops, ruthless politicians, and brutalizing hoodlums. This is a Chandler-esque "who-done-it" with an African-American theme.</plot></movie><movie><title>How to Make Love to a Woman</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>6.7</rating><plot>An animated look at the 11 essential steps to make the pilgrim's progess from finding a woman to making love to her. Along the way, our prototypical man gets advice about her eyes, her hair, her neck, her nostrils (and how they will flare as she becomes excited), the kiss, disrobing her (be subtle yet have authority), the hug, her nipples, and kinky accessories. At every turn, even as the exultant strains of Handel's Hallelujah Chorus signal that success is upon him, there are dangers and pitfalls. The journey requires steely resolve.</plot></movie><movie><title>Love Dance</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>5.8</rating><plot>After becoming engaged to Emily, Gabe finds himself watching a graceful pair of dancers in a dance studio window. Hoping to learn to dance for his upcoming wedding, Gabe enters the studio to take lessons. While interested in his dance teacher, he finds that he is still looking forward to his wedding, but things change when he has Emily comes in for her lessons.</plot></movie><movie><title>Full Throttle</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>6.7</rating><plot>One of Hong Kong's top motorcycle racers is forced to reevaluate his entire way of life after a serious accident and the loss of a close friend. Andy Lau plays a champion motorcycle racer who is forced to question his entire lifestyle after he and some close friends are seriously injured in motorcycle accidents. He subsequently struggles to maintain his identity as a risk-taker; and fights to maintain and redefine his relationships with his fiancée, his friends, and his estranged father. A compelling tale of a man's pride and the emotional catharses of himself and those he loves</plot></movie><movie><title>Kivenpyorittajan kyla</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>6.8</rating><plot>Pekka returns to his native village to attend a wedding. The village has lost its younger generations, and the movie tells the story of the last wedding in the village.</plot></movie><movie><title>Das geschriebene Gesicht</title><category>movie</category><year>1995</year><rating>5.1</rating><plot></plot></movie>